<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-26T16:10:03.819Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>054ab52e36a50c36</seriesId>
  <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>Spring has come at last in Aomori Prefecture, at the northernmost tip of Honshu. In May, buds are blooming and the countryside is turning lushly green. Our cyclist takes a ride from the ocean to the mountainside. Scallops are cultivated in the rich spring ocean and apple trees are blooming in the vast plane. Locals love the soulful melody played with Tsugaru Shamisen, a traditional musical instrument. They endure long severe winters and bring up the spirit of fortitude. Join us on a trip through nature and experience traditions of northern Japan!</content>
    <description>Spring has come at last in Aomori, at the northernmost tip of Honshu. In May, the countryside is turning lushly green. Come with us on a four-day cycle ride through this beautiful northern land.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/nwlEjTAD#hgNSOCK68LVcZNIqgWAHjg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T15:00:28.161Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-19T14:29:20.136Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>ac91d6dacc2e62cb8554a94e93deb32c1fadbcf4ad203c25a001c4b35530e842</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-19T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Aomori - A Spirit of Fortitude</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:39:36.502Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/PNMRUCrC#yCrbF9kJ85GeLveeSWupTw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>If you're a thrill seeker, we recommend the steep roads of Aizu, in the Fukushima mountains. Our cyclist heads deep into the woods where autumn colors decorate the forest. He finds a village stuck in time where locals gladly share their traditions. He learns about a style of hand weaving called, Karamushi and explores 300-year-old storehouses where sake is brewed. We'll also be exposed to an education system from the samurai era for girls that remains unchanged. This 300km ride provides a glimpse into the lives of proud locals with a resilient culture.</content>
    <description>Our rider heads to Aizu, high in the Fukushima mountains where autumn has arrived. He steps back in time when he visits an old village steeped in tradition. Join us on our 300-kilometer journey!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KotmWRSb#4KSY7EZr9MwdI-y5EIYx-A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T15:00:33.635Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T14:29:20.086Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>9d1301ed92389213819d933039f14a8c9dc87c41dc464bb32475ed92449ec44f</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Aizu - A Tapestry of Tradition</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:39:05.286Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/khtFQSzA#KwKqZQeiL_e9VigrSjUDJA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>016</airingId>
    <content>In spring, cherry trees are full blooming in the Noto Peninsula, extending into the Sea of Japan. We explore the rich culture of this land cultivated by its history. We will start our trip from Kanazawa where people enjoying cherry blossom, to Rokko Saki, the northernmost tip of the peninsula. You can enjoy beach cycling in the west coast. In the mountain side, locals enjoy newly sprouting mountain vegetables. This peninsula is full of rich nature and culture such as the lacquer-making town of Wajima. Come along on 230km ride with us.</content>
    <description>In spring, cherry trees are full blooming in the Noto Peninsula, extending into the Sea of Japan. We explore the rich culture of this land cultivated by its history. Come along on 230km ride with us.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T21:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/F91G0JQS#c6uUatldME3ShjWKBo2XoQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T21:00:26.726Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T20:29:20.097Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>aa77bbe36bec98d2b658860d629a9d5911f3968cd6568ee78f9cb1d9767e9eac</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T20:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Noto Peninsula - Life in All its Richness</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:50:44.095Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Vd1UCS5C#sM0jo8Y69iQX0fFbxxoSRw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>017</airingId>
    <content>Summer, when Hokkaido Prefecture's flowers are in full bloom, is the best season to visit the most northerly of Japan's major islands. On this 530km cycle trip, Zac Reynolds from Australia discovers the history of Hokkaido's early pioneering farmers, and explores the culture of the island's indigenous Ainu people.</content>
    <description>Hokkaido is the best place for cycling in summer. We'll see the history of its early pioneering farmers and the indigenous people, Ainu. Come with us on a 530km ride to the northernmost tip of Japan.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/oJgB3IwQ#NQruh-PJNw0fK8BIVeepxQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T15:00:27.910Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T14:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>6727b61a1ac6a8b7798bdf0e63ae47619d32160da4044cf8156ae15e66970545</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hokkaido - Journey to The Far North</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:30:10.292Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oxdxlSRA#G5ECJk22m4W5dGDg029-JQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>The area around "Jingu," the Grand Shrine of Ise, was lively even during the Edo period, bustling with activity and entertainment while the shrine itself served as a sacred place for worshippers. This created a distinct culture. The complex terrain led to unique customs which are still cherished today. A traditional shellfish female diver "ama" who enters the water without any breathing gear is born from necessity. Discover the local culture and other traditions on our journey through Mie Prefecture.</content>
    <description>This time, our cyclist rides through Mie Prefecture,known as the home of sacred shrine Ise Jingu, complex terrain, and people who continue to live lives of tradition, including "ama" abalone divers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/R8EBwajA#RRnqBmfhIl2r-wtkuPjiRA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T15:00:28.200Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T14:29:22.367Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>8305c5fdd563dbe222f27d1785dc2b100fe148bdc9138c60781de85fb4e267ae</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mie - A Summer Dream</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T19:13:26.353Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Bs1VUAjB#JVJk5_Rl2zNtiezjEostuQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>Blue skies, tranquil sea, and warm people are what our rider encounters as he travels through Kochi Prefecture. First, to a scenic coastline popular among cyclists where he enjoys seared Katsuo, a local specialty. In the mountains, he meets friendly people playing field games in mud! And a washi paper craftsman demonstrates the beauty of mountain living. After riding along the Shimanto River, he gets a feel for an old pilgrimage known as the Henro. Join us on our journey through Kochi.</content>
    <description>In Kochi Prefecture, our traveler rides along a shimmering stream, the Shimanto River and a vast plateau under the summer sky and samples seared Katsuo, a local favorite, during his journey.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-07T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/eV1wzYyI#bIAEj6VrHP0EXNi8d4Y6bA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-07T15:00:40.384Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-07T14:29:20.071Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>a2b65c48641f07b30ed79e5e9f6169f0eafc05e8475a4b7377d95e9d4a01cf04</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-07T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kochi - Beneath Blue Skies</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-07T15:43:54.211Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OBEwWRYD#2xKxOLOSarzpOCpTyP25nA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>020</airingId>
    <content>Historically known as Satsuma, Kagoshima Prefecture was a region famed for producing warrior heroes. This 290km ride takes us via its beautiful coastlines to the active volcano of Sakurajima. On a detour into the mountains, we meet a woman who singlehandedly revived the unique regional craft of Satsuma button making. We also visit modern day swordsmen who train in a tradition directly handed down from the samurai.</content>
    <description>Discover the samurai spirit in Kagoshima, named Satsuma in ancient times. In contrast to stoic ways of warriors, arts also blossomed here. Join us on a 290km trip as we experience culture of samurai.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-14T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4VMi3ZwK#G_Wk4jCHvOXm9MHto_-NAw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-14T15:00:43.476Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-14T14:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>3aba5e8654f003f8f0f0ae5107f350767ea2b7b3d5b43973d320c90c7c016c7d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-14T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kagoshima - Legacy of Determination</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-14T17:05:32.790Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/kM1gwQYZ#tdVxyuPW6kyrUyrKL-oXoQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>021</airingId>
    <content>Hyogo Prefecture is known for its capital and port, Kobe, but inland it has many other distinct areas, each proud of its culture and history. On this 300-km trip we cross the autumn mountains to encounter fascinating characters such as a farming couple who rescued a rare, historical variety of bean, and the lone artisan still plying a famous wicker trunk craft tradition. We'll ride the far coastline with a local cycling team, and visit a tiny country smokehouse run by a husband and wife.</content>
    <description>From the port of Kobe, we cycle across the fall mountains to explore the inland side of Hyogo pref., an area where people treasure their unique cultural traditions as a legacy for generations to come.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-21T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/j7ZmAbzD#xN_RfQdafDqPtzJU67Nf4g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-21T15:00:34.309Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-21T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>23260111471331c56d852e694415f909e25dd52713ed4a06cf7e935d4a063cae</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-21T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hyogo - A Legacy for the Future</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-21T15:46:24.517Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3jAyALxB#-iZTy71mgZSTVBzOWm-g5Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>022</airingId>
    <content>This time, we take in the tropical breeze and blue ocean while cycling around the Miyako Islands in Okinawa Prefecture. Our cyclist samples local specialties including a kind of tofu made with seawater and gets a look at the Sanshin, a traditional instrument for playing folk songs loved by locals. He also chows down on local cuisine, discovers amazing white sand beaches, and marvels at a more relaxed, traditional way of life. Come with us to these beautiful southern islands.</content>
    <description>Take in the ocean breeze while cycling around Okinawa's Miyako Islands. Our rider discovers traditional folk instruments, chows down on local cuisine, and discovers life at a more relaxed pace.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-04T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/BfhjwQyB#NgMZUg8zt2CAtnadxAmM-g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-04T15:00:34.342Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-04T14:29:20.117Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>7cda73086fab5af1aee1ab00a999d2838f96045202fd6cc32964748fc1d04e30</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-04T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miyako Islands - Riding the Ocean Breeze</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-04T23:34:18.971Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/lJUQlTiT#yJXGrgB4gGKKl2cBLT8sJQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>023</airingId>
    <content>A ride through the high mountains of Yamagata Prefecture, northern Japan, with a cyclist on his first long road trip. An interest in Eastern philosophy has drawn him to the 3 Mountains of Dewa, a legendary abode of kami deities. We begin by cycling among cherry trees and meeting a veteran artisan of Japanese chess pieces. On Mt. Haguro, we're guided up the sacred peak by a Yamabushi mountain ascetic. Finally, we help a free-spirited falconer train his bird of prey in the snowy wilderness.</content>
    <description>This time, the northern mountains of Yamagata, and a ride through the abode of deities, remote peaks that attract ascetics seeking enlightenment and free spirits wanting a life close to nature.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-11T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tMY2xBiB#L-jcNxhwRdWyVOZMs9y8Ng</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-11T15:00:24.769Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-11T14:29:22.736Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>bcf0551326df514239d2580cc3b462ba0bad949965a444800400cc5ebf45ea4f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-11T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yamagata - Call of The Wild</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T13:39:16.536Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/QYp1UAzQ#V4KiNl2uxwdkrl1Ip3ZDuw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>024</airingId>
    <content>This time, we ride south from Narita Airport for a vibrant spring ride through the Boso Peninsula. It's April, and the cherry blossom trees are in full bloom! First, we ride along Japan's second-longest river, which makes the peninsula a great place for farming, and see a festival created to pray for a good harvest. We also visit a secluded inn and try dishes made with freshly picked bamboo shoots. Our ride ends near the coast, where we learn about the unique spirit of some chic fishermen!</content>
    <description>This time, we take a spring ride through the Boso Peninsula, right next to Tokyo. Discover the history surrounding a giant river and learn about the spirit of fishermen blessed by plentiful seas!</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-18T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/okcyBRAa#o-TlLMi9c6hGl1RnQKW76Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-18T15:00:25.088Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-18T14:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>b3ee552f6c9819a16d8b907a25b9d7505971b7da55f967a59b820b4143eb3bf2</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-18T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Boso Peninsula - A Vibrant Spring Journey</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-18T16:11:58.211Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/EZQ01bgZ#rT8OWvW7AzMSafit5DfHBA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>025</airingId>
    <content>Our New Zealand cyclist begins his ride through Tottori Prefecture with a fat bike tour of its spectacular 16-km long sand dunes. In the mountains, he drops in to a high school calligraphy club where he is hugely impressed by the way these young girls have created a powerful performance using traditional brush calligraphy and music. Returning to the coast, he's amazed by hearing from farmers how their ancestors' hard work and inventiveness produced techniques for growing food in sand. Join us, and discover this unique part of Japan.</content>
    <description>Starting with a fat bike tour of Tottori's famous sand dunes, we ride through this beautiful part of western Japan, discovering a unique spirit of inventiveness and a gutsy approach to life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-04T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/O8MFmKqY#07HQIOJidPK4WK_UMRbVHg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-04T15:00:35.680Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-04T14:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>c60d00c9fb09086abb724e42f1f5e2dd8fc8af9327c240e2042f1ede27f14c3d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-04T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tottori - Grit and Grace</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-04T15:52:33.424Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W1d0iLQI#VbZvCdhdIeAp2vopNrT7MA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>026</airingId>
    <content>Oita Prefecture has been known since ancient times as the "Land of Plenty." But why? Cyclist James Hobbs looks for answers on a 3 day, 350km ride through this southern region. His route through Oita's majestic mountains brings him in touch with a doctor carefully looking after the region's aged residents. He also visits an island of just 18 inhabitants and learns how those inhabitants are working to keep their traditions alive for the future. All that and more on this ride through the Land of Plenty!</content>
    <description>Since ancient times, this region has always been known to the Japanese as the Land of Plenty. We discover why on a 350km cycle ride exploring Oita, its mountains, sea and islands.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-19T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PVdAQTKa#HVFRjh5UEThZ6bahQd1AOQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-19T05:00:25.928Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-19T04:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>e4379efb3b591ecb8bcb3862ecd7becdaa53e53c9c48f4a7f95a9ab2d9d62d41</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-19T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Oita - Land of Plenty</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-19T05:48:37.351Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ytZgGLIC#Uz8R5Cj7MEM0k5GOn5PLnw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>027</airingId>
    <content>Our cyclist begins on Tanegashima with a ride down its beautiful coast and a quick dip in its hot rock-heated pools. Next, he cycles past stones carved by the ocean into fantastic shapes to Japan's biggest space center. Local schools here host children from all over the country for a year to learn about space and experience island life. Finally, he crosses to legendary Yakushima to explore its millennia-old forests and discover how nature inspires its islanders.</content>
    <description>A ride around two of Japan's southern islands: Tanegashima, with Japan's biggest space center, and Yakushima, with its ancient forests, discovering the island way of coexisting with nature.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-18T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/up5lQKzQ#pUocJtifViIY-HlwM2vosw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-18T15:00:35.039Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-18T14:29:20.064Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>b8829a3c9f180bd8d233ee24aa3537a3fdc1056d93c41244dedf989399fc351e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-18T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tanegashima and Yakushima - Inspired by Nature</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T04:10:31.132Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/u51XWaBD#Jh03034QS9Vk2sZFHIR-1A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>028</airingId>
    <content>Miyagi Prefecture is a beautiful part of Japan, and in autumn its seas and mountains are at their most scenic. Towns along this coast that were devastated by the great tsunami in 2011 are now almost totally restored. During this 300km cycle adventure, we'll encounter the irrepressible spirit of people who overcame disaster and the loss of loved ones to rebuild their lives, as we visit a workshop making salt the ancient way and a local festival that kept spirits high when times were tough.</content>
    <description>On a 300km autumn trip through Miyagi, one of Japan's most beautiful regions, we visit coastal towns that have rebuilt their way of life in the time since the devastating 2011 earthquake.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-11T21:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QG4ySA4K#Gs046dhZf7pXEycjq5OUpw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-11T21:00:26.928Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-11T20:29:22.739Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>23fbd8b37497ab855695c5e0bb260a5f5efac52371b6f4c7d20b8723233d97bb</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-11T20:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miyagi - An Unshaken Spirit</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-11T21:59:15.455Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/seB0Gb6Q#COv-A0TW1lhT--HANdLOvg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>029</airingId>
    <content>This three-day, 360km trip takes us from lowland Gifu Prefecture and its blossoming cherry trees north into the snow-covered central mountains. We'll visit a traditional swordsmith to watch him forge katana blades from living flame, a hillside town built on water and some of Japan's most iconic thatched-roof homes. A final adventure involves our cyclist in a 200-year old tradition of amateur village kabuki, one of the many ways people have found to enjoy life in the remote mountains.</content>
    <description>Join us on a trip to Gifu, located near the center of Japan's main island, and experience its blossoming cherry trees, its snow-covered central mountains, and its inspiring people and traditions.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Ng9jQYSY#uwn6zRjgavSH9MOkIX8KdQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T15:00:29.141Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T14:29:20.074Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>b17309a3569ed2b61dcbed8612be09b3be94f4518e2a031bbc691262068d6b68</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Gifu - The Joys of Mountain Life</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:24:27.385Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/mZtAyZDa#60tAA0WIi2aVRWp1SBXaKQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>030</airingId>
    <content>Our ironman cyclist Michael sets off from Osaka. Leaving the giant city, he tackles the challenge of Japan's steepest road on his way to historic Nara Prefecture, site of the capital 1,300 years ago. As he rides through this tranquil countryside, he dives into a world of myth -- from Nara's sacred forest, brilliant with the colors of fall, he travels south to a land teeming with prehistoric burial mounds. Here, where ancient rulers slept for millennia, the old wisdom still shows us how to live in harmony with nature.</content>
    <description>This ride through Nara, site of Japan's ancient capital, takes us through historic locations bright with the colors of fall, a tranquil countryside brimming with the wisdom of the old days.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AVkw1YCT#Ile6Q_GoQjBvJSZqyQ5wgQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T15:00:27.461Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T14:29:23.994Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>56621ec514a647234ec4f06c153ec265a1ef8e55fb7074ccf86ed6ee8275154e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nara - Discovering Ancient Ways</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T22:41:28.471Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/O1EFGara#l1KWm6jfbEavcKNhdBkzFw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>031</airingId>
    <content>Facing the Seto Inland Sea, sunny Kagawa Prefecture historically overcame a lack of natural resources and water through skill and hard work. Despite no local bamboo or paper, Kagawa artisans created paper fans famed for their quality. We get a look at how those fans are made. Then, after sampling Wasanbon sweets, prized for centuries for their delicate sweetness, we cross to a small island to sample soy sauce made the traditional way. A trip of tough but rewarding climbs, reflecting the spirit of Kagawa.</content>
    <description>A ride from one edge to the other of Japan's smallest prefecture, where a relative scarcity of natural resources has been historically offset by an unrelenting drive to create outstanding quality.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-28T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OnhADDpa#NHCRBqKXEv_erwPCOsDYBg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-28T15:00:32.745Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-28T14:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>790f203d2017524abea202019f4d91692dbb1b1006af7e31032febe35b0befce</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-28T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kagawa - The Pursuit of Excellence</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-28T17:12:45.731Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/rJtUXIqT#ptP84Rb6B9WbHVC0lwNiOg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>032</airingId>
    <content>This time, we cycle through Toyama Prefecture, which has both a bountiful sea and 3,000-meter mountains that feed its fields with rich waters. First, we sample some rare seafood unique to the area. We then discover the culture and way of life created by the strong winds that blow here all year. That includes a traditional festival meant to calm disasters caused by the winds, plus a beautiful style of wood carving. Join us on a 250-kilometer cycling trip through the winds of Toyama.</content>
    <description>This time, we cycle Toyama at the end of summer. The strong winds that blow here all year have created a unique culture and way of life. As the season turns, let's ride and learn more.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-25T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/T59QjBDR#ejgLcyRDqRwNj7f-T0H3vg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-25T15:00:35.793Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-25T14:29:20.092Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>aec6860d72767b739be3fe748a64f9aa7a8a9f0650f3a94f6b794418c5541675</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-25T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Toyama - Riding with the Wind</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-25T16:18:42.285Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/pp5mVCoA#Q3Lka2odX3f4s9_tRh63_A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>033</airingId>
    <content>This time we ride through the colorful autumn scenery of Hokkaido Prefecture. Our journey begins in Asahikawa and takes us through the Tokachi Plain, before we arrive at the Shiretoko Peninsula on the eastern coast. Along the way, we harvest soybeans, and meet the indigenous Ainu, who have long lived in harmony with nature. We encounter deer and bears, and an endangered species of owl. The trip showcases a way of life that coexists with the natural world.</content>
    <description>This time, we ride through Hokkaido in autumn. Along the way, we see the animals in its majestic landscape, and meet the indigenous Ainu, who have long lived in harmony with nature.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-25T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/apEnAYIJ#JZfxJ4tdYQsH2mrLWpW8-Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-25T15:00:29.865Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-25T14:29:20.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>27659548aa26e3029e2dc86875218d2a8d46a1ef9c47c50d497edd68cbbe63e1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-25T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hokkaido in Autumn: Living with Nature</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-29T11:55:59.209Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/n9hkFCYZ#LZ6XQQmhXiSkYB8hFW3nHQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>034</airingId>
    <content>This 400km winter cycle trip takes us through Ibaraki Prefecture. At Lake Kasumigaura, our cyclist plunges into freezing water to help a husband and wife harvest lotus roots. After hill climbing on Mt. Tsukuba, he visits a historic kendo hall, and a workshop where 2 brothers make fine armor the traditional way. Then he meets hotel brothers experimenting with fishermen's cuisine. Ibaraki families know the value of working together.</content>
    <description>On a winter ride through Ibaraki, we explore a famous lake, go hill climbing, feel the samurai spirit in a kendo hall, and enjoy the fishermen's cuisine hotel brothers are keeping alive.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-26T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0yJgmR6B#R8tlLCn8-2FlLGj_I-8yOA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-26T05:00:28.858Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-26T04:29:20.088Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2070</seriesId>
    <sha256>ed306cfdc2507c0dbabe8534020265fb632355ab0a7b1938f99dd72bcb0b2f27</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-26T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ibaraki - Where Family Matters</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN  Highlights</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-26T06:01:16.359Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/k7oAGA4B#5oggNWRbmaeYHSWtNQxOGQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>