<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-06-03T01:45:03.622Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>08575bba6e407a35</seriesId>
  <title>A Century on Film</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>001</airingId>
    <content>A Century on Film looks back at a world-changing century of human drama and tragedy through rare and precious archival footage. Episode 1 begins with the World War I, including moving scenes from the world's first full-length war documentary, "The Battle of the Somme." It was filmed by British army cameraman, Geoffrey Malins, who wrote, "What a record. …When this devastating war was over, people would be able to view all over again the fearful shells bursting, killing and maiming…" A wealth of other historical footage and testimonies bring the Great War to life in a dramatic opening to this fascinating series.</content>
    <description>World War I, Part 1 brings the Great War to life with a wealth of historical footage, including moving scenes from the world's first full-length war documentary, The Battle of the Somme.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-24T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/mhwngCBC#a8lb51GiQpf-D4ebFqUWHw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-24T05:40:28.551Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-24T05:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2055</seriesId>
    <sha256>1cbf456e70c682ed1d44074240fdfe1c9a1c563993a0e1e14657766481be933d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-24T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>World War I Part 1: A World Turned Upside Down</subtitle>
    <title>A Century on Film</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-24T07:18:49.860Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IRtnGKSC#XKK83Dnzp-ZMwfBP6erJ1Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>002</airingId>
    <content>A Century on Film looks back at a world-changing century of human drama and tragedy through rare and precious archival footage. In the second installment covering World War I, we feature German scientific genius, Fritz Haber, who developed the world's first chemical weapons. The story of his scientist wife's response reflects the differing views of scientific progress in a human drama that plays out with tragic consequences. Images of the destructiveness of war, the heroes it created, and the roots of our modern world are also explored in rich and moving detail.</content>
    <description>World War I, Part 2 features German scientific genius, Fritz Haber, who developed the world's first chemical weapons. The heroes the war created and the roots of our modern world are also explored.</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-22T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HNglyaoa#Dg6eFHa1ioAfoLiHNdqg_w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-22T05:40:34.250Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-22T05:09:20.163Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2055</seriesId>
    <sha256>c522bbe545b8c9821ee8b5e4f95f3da705f978de2389a12c246d545d0a4a8f74</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-22T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>World War I Part 2: The Fate of Heroes</subtitle>
    <title>A Century on Film</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-22T23:55:39.727Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/vAZjVCwD#kg7V2g7N9p1tmDnejfUbnQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>