<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-28T20:00:03.257Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>0fc6cd6b02dc8d5f</seriesId>
  <title>Anime Supernova</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>042</airingId>
    <content>A creator from Hokkaido Prefecture, Japan who specializes in rhythmical animation with illustrations and figures that move to music. He was commissioned by the Foundation for Ainu Culture to create an animation about the Ainu. The purpose of the foundation is to preserve the stories and myths passed down orally by the non-literate Ainu through music, language and animation. This episode explores the appeal of Ishiguro's portrayal of the Ainu culture, which has slowly been disappearing year by year.</content>
    <description>A creator from Hokkaido, Japan who specializes in rhythmical animation about the Ainu. We explore Ishiguro's portrayal of the indigenous culture, which has slowly been disappearing year by year.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/dA40VBDA#8bIFk3e9HWcY-ovJW4mJ3A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T00:25:28.841Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T00:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>ca66a5d7862d6129af951d2b3ddc853d23306a2141396e1dedc6545af68b3c54</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Portraying Ethnic Lore Through Animation</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:31:48.470Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/n5U1VIyb#yaNfzEFuw4AB8wQ5-3nsBA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>043</airingId>
    <content>Mainly works as a director on live-action commercials. At 43, he began working on original stop-motion animated works. In addition to writing and directing, he also works with art, animation, puppet-modeling and more. He's a nature-loving Akita Prefecture-born creator who currently lives in Karuizawa. He aims to create textured visuals unique only to stop-motion animation.</content>
    <description>Yashiro began creating stop-motion films at 43 while working as a CM director. The nature-loving Akita-born creator currently lives in Karuizawa, also working with art, puppet-modeling, and more.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OksygYhB#2un-Uf2glFxUJ1bCF8_a5A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T00:25:30.990Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T00:09:20.067Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>6beef5069f2f425f6bcc8de748ba47f5061255a6c43cc4282aac681a91aa5467</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Stop-Motion Fantasy Full of Nature</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T09:10:49.715Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/iollHQZR#rG4E2E_fli85vxQ619VIMw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>044</airingId>
    <content>The up-and-coming creator has made the cover art for various novels, created music videos, and put together image boards for animated shows, all while attending university. Okada has gained the attention of international animation fans because of the detailed, beautiful worlds he creates and his ability to tell a story in every single cut. Watch and find out why the animation world has high expectations for this young 20-something creator.</content>
    <description>Up-and-coming student creator Okada Shogo is known for his wide variety of work and detailed, beautiful worlds. Find out why the animation world has high expectations for this young artist.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3gNCiZAI#CXNaRn4ifDuLu2-qTeBamw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T00:25:28.927Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T00:09:20.139Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>c3ccab348b9f17af6ee081f8300f6a062975dba8be95532eb8a1c2421bf3d0a5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Student Creator With a Bright Future</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T17:00:29.883Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/H0czGCSI#tl-VD0OnMuqo4dHDyQ6JwQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>