<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-18T03:50:03.705Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>0fc6cd6b02dc8d5f</seriesId>
  <title>Anime Supernova</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>Kouhei Nakama is a computer animator who is in high demand around the world. From ultra-realistic abstract objects to beautiful depictions of the human body, Nakama focuses on imagery that catches the eye, as well as on a sense of liveliness -- every detail is given its own set of movements.</content>
    <description>Kouhei Nakama is a computer animator who is in high demand around the world. He focuses on imagery that catches the eye, as well as on a sense of liveliness--every detail has its own set of movements.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-27T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/P45STILQ#JbLAVC2CcX9jDaiFhdVpUQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-27T00:25:31.085Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-27T00:09:26.761Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>32179f6f321efe77c2cbfc692063936eabba376082ce5e3a419e8398338a6fd6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-27T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Creating Graceful Motion with CGI</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-28T10:58:44.312Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/q0YClRRI#PIDO2XvG5kldbglN4oIhUg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>Keisuke Matsumoto has a passionate online fan base thanks to his 2 ongoing web animated series. His works are known for their cute characters and comic dialogue, which is inspired by a Japanese two-person comedy routine known as Manzai.</content>
    <description>Keisuke Matsumoto has taken Japan by storm with his 2 ongoing web animated series, which feature cute characters and comic dialogue inspired by a Japanese two-person comedy routine known as Manzai.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-17T02:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RI9hlaQK#zEDK_fLDS4dJiXfVhmM2vA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-17T02:25:34.682Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-17T02:09:20.022Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>3eda7a2dc59d44423d0fd91f4c8e8f7a5af00a64de8705059060d09675d2dfda</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-17T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Comical Shenanigans on the Web</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-17T03:08:41.530Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qsp1SQSS#8mJTJ2-P-hdzHhjdAqHU_A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>Tomoki Misato is a young up-and-coming animator who has already won numerous awards at festivals around the world. He creates stop-motion animations featuring colorfully designed puppets and stories with plenty of twists and turns.</content>
    <description>Tomoki Misato is an up-and-coming animator who has won numerous awards at festivals around the world for his short works, which feature colorfully designed puppets and stories with plenty of twists.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-20T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xI5WRR4R#AFRCKqUTtQPq16kFSDNeqw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-20T00:25:26.820Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-20T00:09:20.113Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>85e4ffe88f20a66cc3e6f7859e9d5522fe00a7a5e3adf9b3d085ac476fed7a98</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-20T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Creator of Imaginative Stop-Motion Worlds</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T01:31:07.777Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qQcWlD5K#K_9W_K4kj8GZ6Y2HaAruMg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>042</airingId>
    <content>A creator from Hokkaido Prefecture, Japan who specializes in rhythmical animation with illustrations and figures that move to music. He was commissioned by the Foundation for Ainu Culture to create an animation about the Ainu. The purpose of the foundation is to preserve the stories and myths passed down orally by the non-literate Ainu through music, language and animation. This episode explores the appeal of Ishiguro's portrayal of the Ainu culture, which has slowly been disappearing year by year.</content>
    <description>A creator from Hokkaido, Japan who specializes in rhythmical animation about the Ainu. We explore Ishiguro's portrayal of the indigenous culture, which has slowly been disappearing year by year.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/dA40VBDA#8bIFk3e9HWcY-ovJW4mJ3A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T00:25:28.841Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T00:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>ca66a5d7862d6129af951d2b3ddc853d23306a2141396e1dedc6545af68b3c54</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Portraying Ethnic Lore Through Animation</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:31:48.470Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/n5U1VIyb#yaNfzEFuw4AB8wQ5-3nsBA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>043</airingId>
    <content>Mainly works as a director on live-action commercials. At 43, he began working on original stop-motion animated works. In addition to writing and directing, he also works with art, animation, puppet-modeling and more. He's a nature-loving Akita Prefecture-born creator who currently lives in Karuizawa. He aims to create textured visuals unique only to stop-motion animation.</content>
    <description>Yashiro began creating stop-motion films at 43 while working as a CM director. The nature-loving Akita-born creator currently lives in Karuizawa, also working with art, puppet-modeling, and more.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OksygYhB#2un-Uf2glFxUJ1bCF8_a5A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T00:25:30.990Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T00:09:20.067Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>6beef5069f2f425f6bcc8de748ba47f5061255a6c43cc4282aac681a91aa5467</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Stop-Motion Fantasy Full of Nature</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T09:10:49.715Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/iollHQZR#rG4E2E_fli85vxQ619VIMw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>044</airingId>
    <content>The up-and-coming creator has made the cover art for various novels, created music videos, and put together image boards for animated shows, all while attending university. Okada has gained the attention of international animation fans because of the detailed, beautiful worlds he creates and his ability to tell a story in every single cut. Watch and find out why the animation world has high expectations for this young 20-something creator.</content>
    <description>Up-and-coming student creator Okada Shogo is known for his wide variety of work and detailed, beautiful worlds. Find out why the animation world has high expectations for this young artist.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3gNCiZAI#CXNaRn4ifDuLu2-qTeBamw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T00:25:28.927Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T00:09:20.139Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>c3ccab348b9f17af6ee081f8300f6a062975dba8be95532eb8a1c2421bf3d0a5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Student Creator With a Bright Future</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T17:00:29.883Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/H0czGCSI#tl-VD0OnMuqo4dHDyQ6JwQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>045</airingId>
    <content>Coming from a live-action film background, Iwaisawa is almost entirely self-taught in animation production. He continues to move up in the animation world and separate himself from other animators through self-developed techniques. Iwaisawa specializes in rotoscope, an animation technique that is based on tracing over live-action footage. The painstaking work leads to highly detailed images that come to life in ways not seen in traditional animation. We will introduce you to the one-of-a-kind, internationally-acclaimed world of Iwaisawa Kenji.</content>
    <description>Iwaisawa Kenji is a self-taught creator who uses a technique called rotoscoping to produce one-of-a-kind animated works. Watch and get lost in the fantastical worlds of a visionary creator.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zgMUGLLb#WwW2rqfrjek4fknN7S1G7g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T00:26:01.373Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T00:09:23.019Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>009a0951c49aa774ecc71104d9aa7ae8bb2b27640644f8bb816499d35a232619</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Aiming for an Academy Award! A Creator Taking on Unprecedented Challenges</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T16:02:39.880Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jQlywQbT#BIo_jxBdg7PRg76DllkZbQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>046</airingId>
    <content>Tomioka currently heads the 3DCG studio Canavan Graphics. His job encompasses directing, writing and producing, all while managing his company. The talented creator is well-known for his original comedic animation style. He has also turned his original characters into multi-faceted businesses that include goods, video games and other ventures. In this episode, we find out what drives Tomioka's creativity and how he has become a master of comical 3DCG animation.</content>
    <description>Tomioka Satoshi is a director, writer, producer, and CEO known for his unique comedic style and multi-faceted business ventures. Watch and find out how this renaissance man mastered 3DCG animation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-23T00:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/EdwwEIzJ#Scn7SzcsicEtmakFOw6VSQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-23T00:25:29.564Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-23T00:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>576866cdea11d9f3a0447389a798ed7a71391b06ff609617638bc585cc03b944</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-23T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Master of Comical 3DCG Animation</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-23T02:03:57.782Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HrAyEZLb#_oyjS17Z-rB48L4SBJeBzQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>047</airingId>
    <content>Yokoshima Toshihisa is a creator who honed his skills at Kamikazedouga, the production company behind international hits like "Ninja Batman." Although he works in 3DCG, he maintains a hand-drawn feel through his use of lines and coloring. His detailed depiction of his characters and the science fiction settings have made him a highly acclaimed animator.</content>
    <description>Yokoshima Toshihisa honed his skills at Kamikazedouga, the company behind hits like "Ninja Batman." His detailed character depictions and science fiction settings have made him highly acclaimed.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-24T02:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZEUiDDaL#wV_MWj-1M6t0qW991GB5zQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-24T02:25:32.277Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-24T02:09:20.052Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>e9909c24d1981f7dbde02097ead8661342b2d465cbbd5dd2f26a3bd310707764</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-24T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Sci-Fi Animator Pushing the Boundaries of 3DCG</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-24T04:07:15.242Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/v9B2SBCa#-zDUawLxTrlYiplXIl51YQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>049</airingId>
    <content>Murata Tomoyasu is a highly-acclaimed stop-motion animation artist known for his warm puppets and elaborate productions. The "life and death" of humans has been a focus in Murata's work ever since he was a student. This time, we bring the entirety of "A Branch of a Pine Is Tied Up," Murata's masterpiece based on the Great East Japan Earthquake.</content>
    <description>Acclaimed stop-motion animator Murata Tomoyasu is known for his warm puppet designs. Enjoy the entirety of "A Branch of Pine Is Tied Up," Murata's masterpiece based on the Great East Japan Earthquake.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-12T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LphSzTpa#Wf5wcTuhmlusQLLAhwR7TQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-12T16:00:28.636Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-12T15:29:22.758Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>d81028f9c96518e4ab0be62fac3e74896126f6300e5e9078fa2fe1d555b659b7</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-12T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Watch Murata Tomoyasu's "A Branch of a Pine Is Tied Up" in Full!</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-12T17:47:53.731Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/v95UGSLR#EhiDVBSPwHs5peOUsV9jSA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>050</airingId>
    <content>Yashiro Takeshi mainly works as a director for live-action commercials. At 43, he began working on original stop-motion animated works. He is involved in every aspect of his works, from writing and directing to art, animation, and puppet-modeling. The nature-loving creator from Akita Prefecture currently lives in Karuizawa, where he continues to pursue stop-motion animation that uses textured visuals unique to the medium.</content>
    <description>Yashiro Takeshi is a commercial director who also creates stop-motion animation. From writing to puppetry, he is part of the entire process. Enjoy "Norman the Snowman -The Northern Lights-" in full.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-26T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/r9wQGLZT#FXG0wSIRtMwc3xtnqwKfow</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-26T16:00:29.382Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-26T15:29:23.958Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2065</seriesId>
    <sha256>917d601a3139c21410934927257eeca1004366cbd0c45287bd99711664cd406b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-26T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Watch Yashiro Takeshi's "Norman the Snowman - The Northern Lights -" in Full!</subtitle>
    <title>Anime Supernova</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-29T15:52:19.706Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yA1lWaTb#xNRT78YJH-tfdBWCPmQnwQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>