<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-30T03:55:04.052Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>1315496c5871b57d</seriesId>
  <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>Kagoshima Prefecture, known as the land of brave samurai, was called Satsuma in ancient days. Our cyclist takes in scenic views on his ride along the sea and an active volcano. He discovers jars filled with a local specialty, fermented black vinegar, which make a tart and powerful beverage. In the mountains, he meets a craftswoman who revives old, beautiful buttons. He then finds a secret martial art inherited from samurai. Discover the spirit of this historic land on our 290km ride through Satsuma.</content>
    <description>Discover the samurai spirit in Kagoshima, named Satsuma in ancient times. In contrast to stoic ways of warriors, arts also blossomed here. Join us on a 290 km trip as we experience culture of samurai.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-09T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QWxQAZCR#pTHRGKVy78XvWjML7I6aJw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-09T01:00:21.645Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-09T00:09:20.031Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2066</seriesId>
    <sha256>7e3c8f0e951cfca1f6c3ad35340c297aaaa83a14f4557ad5cb027d087bc11cae</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-09T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kagoshima - Legacy of Determination</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T23:12:41.637Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Hl0GXaDQ#38VaDlnNSGNulmmPRL2G1A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>020</airingId>
    <content>Take in the crisp air as we make our way around Mt. Fuji and surrounding lakes for a perfect winter bike ride. Our cyclist Michael picks the best trails on this challenging journey, which includes crossing a steep mountain to get scenic views of Japan's tallest peak. He also takes a fat bike tour through snowy mountains. Finally, he is rewarded with local lessons on the importance of preserving old ways and the environment. Join us on this 230-kilometer winter ride.</content>
    <description>Join us on a 230-kilometer winter adventure as our cyclist makes his way around a snow-covered Mt. Fuji and nearby scenic lakes. We'll also try out fat bikes made for snowy trails on a special course.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-16T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rRdUARTC#KAi7Y5MDwhtrZZz5IJggqg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-16T01:00:25.098Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-16T00:09:20.082Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2066</seriesId>
    <sha256>d026916f3411f7e5b188d9edb0305c5847d01a8ee18834160ca4b2413dbd5d0d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-16T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fuji and the Highlands - A Winter Ride</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T09:07:51.863Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3xl21LpQ#FUaQs29_FXHo4Y9DqI-nJg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>039</airingId>
    <content>The mountain ranges known as the Japanese Alps are a spectacular backdrop to our ride across Nagano Prefecture, its forests glowing with the late autumn colors. With many 3,000m peaks, Nagano is popular with climbers and we're given a brief taste by a world-class mountain guide. We'll meet people drawn to live here by the forests, including a man who left a top cabinet making career in Tokyo to craft uniquely distinctive furniture from these wild trees, and a group of friends who devote their spare time to caring for the woods.</content>
    <description>A 320-km ride through Nagano, with its magnificent mountain scenery and forests bright with late autumn colors, meeting some distinctive characters drawn to live here by their love of nature.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-13T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/yw4k2LYS#aJpDTqT3wIwaBGyeaAKLeQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-13T07:00:28.287Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-13T06:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2066</seriesId>
    <sha256>f377902243132495f92ea5a0403f52061564063105b06256a7887ddc533b3224</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-13T06:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nagano - Life in the Mountains</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T08:13:23.598Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/lAxSTR5B#zVeiU5IBlEK58oJSZCom6w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>040</airingId>
    <content>In the city of Hiroshima we visit a community where the families who survived the devastation of the atomic bomb in the Second World War managed to revive their traditional farming specialty. In the islands to the south, we meet a potter uniquely making glazes from cast-off oyster shells, and in the mountains, a farmer tells of his passion for making animals happy. The last individual we encounter who has stuck to his own path in life is a carver of traditional instruments seeking the perfect sound.</content>
    <description>We discover how people live today in the city and prefecture of Hiroshima, where society has long since returned to normal after the devastation of the atomic bombing more than 75 years ago.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-13T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/v8QQ1TTT#YL9wXtAl9erx6VHpFI_LOw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-13T01:00:26.481Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-13T00:09:20.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2066</seriesId>
    <sha256>88c0e73831917af91bb9ceea8c2bd583f478bd27a72971c05488cc4eac9ec553</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-13T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hiroshima - Going it Alone</subtitle>
    <title>CYCLE AROUND JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T20:17:53.562Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/G9wAUBSb#xKcKlM4qsX-b41vHsTAeuA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>