<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-28T16:10:03.010Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>156d54897e343840</seriesId>
  <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>058</airingId>
    <content>Plastic pollution litters the world's oceans. It's damaging marine wildlife and ecosystems. A war on plastic is breaking out. In part 1 of this 2-part series, we meet Dutch young pioneer Boyan Slat's team working to clear plastic from the Great Pacific Garbage Patch. They have developed a system based on a 600-meter long floating tube. We also look at how microplastics affect living creatures and explore a shocking study that shows how plastic is contributing to rising levels of greenhouse gases.</content>
    <description>Plastic pollution litters the world's oceans. A war on plastic is breaking out. Part 1 introduces Dutch young pioneer Boyan Slat's team working to clear plastic from the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T12:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/s4F2GJSD#m6KGA0gi8VCb3ACFRaA30Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T12:01:15.645Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-21T11:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>2c7b4ca8433c531344475a9726637a9a23fb31b5a4522bb425bf3fbbe34ffa27</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-21T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>No More Plastic: In Search of a Sustainable Future - Part 1: Clearing Plastic from the Ocean</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:45:24.081Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oRUmybIK#VNHd0v3bC__w50KsHJHTWw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>059</airingId>
    <content>Plastic pollution litters the world's oceans. The move away from the use of plastic is currently gaining steam around the globe. In part 2 of this series, we look at business trends leading us away from a world of plastic and towards circular economies. One example is a Japanese startup hoping to sell its proprietary recycling technology abroad. And also we look at disposable plastics regulation strategies in France and New York City. Can we find ways to leave our plastic civilization behind?</content>
    <description>Plastic pollution litters the world's oceans. A war on plastic is breaking out and the goal is a circular economy. Part 2 looks at the latest business trends leading us away from a world of plastic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T12:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fk9Q3J7R#jyRD9XCsaj6not3NlLTCWg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T12:00:26.371Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T11:09:22.468Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>28c2f44924a0cfcec18781b47ab383691e999d1de35821bf73d881bd5326b4c3</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>No More Plastic: In Search of a Sustainable Future - Part 2: Frontlines of Global Business</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T01:00:47.371Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/L10yAQbB#lUNZkeKZ8tXqz4DDwR_zHA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>060</airingId>
    <content>Castle design evolved in 17th century Japan with stone walls as a key feature. Sakamoto in Shiga Prefecture became famous for its mason's expert techniques for dry-stacking. They traveled across Japan to complete their commissions. But when feudalism ended 150 years ago, many castles were destroyed. While most of the masons lost their jobs, one family in Sakamoto survived by refurbishing old ruins. But the 15th-generation master Suminori Awata is worried about the future. One day he receives an unexpected request to build a castle-style wall in Texas. Awata's journey begins.</content>
    <description>Samurai lords used to live in castles with majestic stone walls. Today only a handful of craftsmen can build walls in the traditional way. One such crafstman is working in an unusual place - the U.S.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KoF03DZD#mGBL_4QUjf4bJSUXiMntug</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T02:00:26.602Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T01:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>9cfdae6f4264d1c53bd16d6587ece8faa2c4c500a700e86f313f8956b8897be2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>SAMURAI WALL</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:45:43.577Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/uk9UQLaQ#mLftUzkkCx9RuGb-njGkMQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>083</airingId>
    <content>75 years ago, Japan and the US each developed chemical weapons and trained their troops to use them. Near the end of the Pacific War, the Imperial Japanese Army stockpiled vast amounts of poison gas for use as a last resort. The US military, meanwhile, drew up chemical weapons plans that would have devastated Japan. After the war, both the US and Japan concealed the truth concerning these weapons. But newly unearthed documents and personal accounts shed light on this dark legacy.</content>
    <description>At the end of WWII, both Japan and the US were prepared to use chemical weapons on each other. Newly unearthed documents and personal accounts have finally cast light on this dark legacy.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-20T20:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/gZ4VjahT#2Gsgt5rPwJpbaiBt7Urgcw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-20T20:50:25.525Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-20T19:59:20.034Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>c1ce4f7f94111036c51200ec0dbc3d2d92695d53e2a50fb7da8fbdb784565a9b</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-20T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Poisonous Secrets: What did Japan and the US bury?</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:04:02.801Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wU9mWYQI#LoiV3Ae1FH8jBcvMXqcFUw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>NHK is collaborating with 12 public broadcasters around the world to promote a project called "FACES" to tackle against bullying. FACES is a vast collection of 2 minutes testimony from people who have experienced being bullied. By using the network of partnership in FACES, this special edition aims to share specific efforts to tackle with bullying. Also dialogue between cross-country protagonists using online meeting, we deepen mutual understanding, be considerate, and follow in detail until we find a solution together.</content>
    <description>FACES is a campaign where people who have experienced bullying raise their voices. Through dialogue with each other, protagonist face their past through and cast hope for an inclusive future.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T08:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/cs0EFAAJ#bC0khONeperMzTcy9xm57Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T08:00:29.344Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T07:09:22.618Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>6b1503321024e48e3f905154a5078949760548bc640ec935d627c5351247e2fb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T07:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>FACES the Special - Voices of Hope for an Inclusive Future -</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T18:56:47.915Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>085</airingId>
    <content>A historic music pub reopened in Koza, Okinawa Prefecture, near Kadena Air Base, in 2019. The owner, rock musician Miyanaga Eiichi, performed for American soldiers who were en route to the front lines during the Vietnam War. Now he tells audiences about how the music expressed soldiers' desires for peace, and recounts the history of the base town. Others whose paths crossed in Koza include a resident whose family home was seized for the air base, a former worker at bars catering to US soldiers, and a US veteran who joined the antiwar movement while in Okinawa. The complex history of a base town is explored.</content>
    <description>A historic music pub reopened in Koza, Okinawa, near Kadena Air Base. To the sound of 70s rock, memories of US soldiers heading off to war and stories of surviving life in an American base town.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/NZ0CmArS#uSQhbLxL_iN7JH6Y4PkzbQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T02:00:27.000Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T01:09:22.876Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>3b9894b2d3f27103f5497ec522132efc7617ad5ba50b40d74cea31dbfeae0e54</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Koza, Okinawa: Base Town Blues</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:32:15.405Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/s0l1TITL#W_XVUy6lMDlwACRy1AdBDg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>086</airingId>
    <content>The final stages of World War II... The islands of Okinawa turned into a theater of war the United States military called "hell." The Battle of Okinawa claimed the lives of at least 120,000 islanders. Women and girls were forced in as army cooks or nurses, boys in their mid-teens molded into soldiers... and sent to the frontline. As most records were lost, families are still wondering how their loved ones were mobilized... and what became of them. But recently discovered documents reveal their unknown stories.</content>
    <description>UNTOLD STORIES OF THE BATTLE OF OKINAWA: Women and Teens on the Frontline. 75 years after the battle that claimed the lives of over 120,000 locals, recently discovered documents reveal untold stories.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AZlk0T7T#maHuMN_HHV7ZEdQNCBUjHg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T02:00:24.200Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T01:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>f5b1344e145dcafb025f9b56c89276543ecf362276b3a357455fb999d311ade0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>UNTOLD STORIES OF THE BATTLE OF OKINAWA: Women and Teens on the Frontline</subtitle>
    <title>NHK WORLD PRIME</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T10:34:34.320Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HU10nLwQ#2ziCpHyJKpc4xmw0_saD7Q</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>