<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T05:35:02.622Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>206e7d7b56906c70</seriesId>
  <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>054</airingId>
    <content>Kirishima, a group of 20 mountains in the south of Kyushu. It is a volcanic area that was a central location in Japan's creation myth. Its name, meaning "fog island," refers to the way that the peaks look like an island rising above the clouds. Its high rate of rainfall creates springs and hot springs for the towns around it, and the volcanic ash it releases helps grow sweet potatoes that have fostered a shochu alcohol culture. As they receive the bounty of the mountains, the people there have created their own unique customs, and carved out their own way of living in harmony with an unforgiving environment. An old mountain guide struggles with volcanic ash as he seeks to reopen the area for tourism and mountain climbing. The people here's love for the region has no limits. Even though there are few jobs for the younger generation, they don't want to leave, and even those who do tend to come back. We will show you the strong, dynamic lifestyle of the people who live together with the Kirishima peaks.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Kirishima: A Town thriving on Volcanic Mountains.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PMlAyZoS#uL7eK8qoQzqQmZzpe8DcLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T00:00:28.617Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-13T23:29:23.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>a63580715cabc64e0765bfecc0911b9fc5f59eca8309a6cb126f1c0578758bc5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-13T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kirishima: A Town Thriving on Volcanic Mountains</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:37:26.309Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ytlCVJTI#zG06REziEu2lQ64wlDxVmA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>Dewa Sanzan is located in the center of Yamagata Prefecture, in the Tohoku region of Japan. Mt. Haguro, Mt. Gassan and Mt. Yudono. Collectively, these 3 mountains are called Dewa Sanzan. The pilgrimage of Dewa Sanzan symbolizes the death and rebirth of a person. It is believed that something important can be obtained by climbing the mountains.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Dewa Sanzan, Mystic Mountains of Prayers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qY8iSSBY#sY9KSVVpE5ws5iW82g063w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T00:01:01.318Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T23:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0179738530d16b10f5cd526ed219e98b8381bdce27a6aec1f7580e1b469c223a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dewa Sanzan: Mystic Mountains of Prayers</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:30:07.683Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6IEyULTC#4WNfofw8PD71ZQXdvf7NcQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>096</airingId>
    <content>Mount Tsukuba is located in Ibaraki Prefecture, about 70 km northeast from Tokyo. The Japanese have revered the mountain since ancient times, as a sacred mountain akin to Mount Fuji. The mountain has a height of 877 meters. Mount Tsukuba, called Tsukuba-san in Japanese, is popular with visitors as anyone can easily climb it. More than 2 million people visit a year. From the old days, it has been believed that a mysterious force dwells in this mountain. In this episode, we present the story of Mount Tsukuba, a sacred mountain rich in mysterious charm.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Mount Tsukuba; The Mysterious Twin Peaks.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OwskDIyJ#abZEOKOp-8C1FZtKRcV9yw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T00:00:28.585Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T23:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>ebf68ceade988d09f845f5029b008c390aecc2184d53a8de284e938a1ae0c1a6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mount Tsukuba: The Mysterious Twin Peaks</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T04:29:14.630Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OksVQaQZ#TSqV-1QAAoTJ4F51gRpAaw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>116</airingId>
    <content>Japanese people have a long history of eating tofu, a filling food that always goes well with a drink. It is made simply by grinding and cooking soybeans, before extracting and solidifying the soymilk. In the mountains, unique varieties of tofu emerged as a result of efforts to avoid wasting the precious beans. In an area of heavy winter snowfall, tofu plays an important part in an annual religious ceremony. We explore the secrets of tofu from across the islands of Japan.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wNdnhCoJ#flnwGMpOQsW1_JRXgTFt9A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T00:00:28.689Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>e06792a7783de0276d03ed51648aa4509d4d65c05c377a1102757ff4d9a4d4cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Secrets of Tofu across Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:09:44.461Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W41QBD5C#UllkKI0RsaA4dB2TVnLaLA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>