<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-28T23:45:03.432Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>206e7d7b56906c70</seriesId>
  <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>032</airingId>
    <content>At the center of Naha City lies Kokusai Street, a symbol of modern Okinawa Prefecture as it was one of the first areas to reemerge after the grueling battles of the war. Stretching for 1.6km, the street was in fact once called "The Miracle Mile." Originally a black market bordering the American-occupied zone, it became Okinawa's busiest shopping street, with 500 souvenir shops and restaurants. This episode focuses on the street's history and source of its prosperity: the diversity and dynamism of Okinawa.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: The Miracle Mile - Kokusai Street, Okinawa.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tc9XAQQb#NWOdDiBZCLlAOHt38Ix-iw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-16T00:00:29.631Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>bd08dc68c4b978a9c11bf2f751f9c2d26197e54e6f37e4b254dd0e410dceee7d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Miracle Mile - Kokusai Street, Okinawa</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:03:36.647Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>054</airingId>
    <content>Kirishima, a group of 20 mountains in the south of Kyushu. It is a volcanic area that was a central location in Japan's creation myth. Its name, meaning "fog island," refers to the way that the peaks look like an island rising above the clouds. Its high rate of rainfall creates springs and hot springs for the towns around it, and the volcanic ash it releases helps grow sweet potatoes that have fostered a shochu alcohol culture. As they receive the bounty of the mountains, the people there have created their own unique customs, and carved out their own way of living in harmony with an unforgiving environment. An old mountain guide struggles with volcanic ash as he seeks to reopen the area for tourism and mountain climbing. The people here's love for the region has no limits. Even though there are few jobs for the younger generation, they don't want to leave, and even those who do tend to come back. We will show you the strong, dynamic lifestyle of the people who live together with the Kirishima peaks.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Kirishima: A Town thriving on Volcanic Mountains.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PMlAyZoS#uL7eK8qoQzqQmZzpe8DcLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T00:00:28.617Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-13T23:29:23.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>a63580715cabc64e0765bfecc0911b9fc5f59eca8309a6cb126f1c0578758bc5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-13T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kirishima: A Town Thriving on Volcanic Mountains</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:37:26.309Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ytlCVJTI#zG06REziEu2lQ64wlDxVmA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>Dewa Sanzan is located in the center of Yamagata Prefecture, in the Tohoku region of Japan. Mt. Haguro, Mt. Gassan and Mt. Yudono. Collectively, these 3 mountains are called Dewa Sanzan. The pilgrimage of Dewa Sanzan symbolizes the death and rebirth of a person. It is believed that something important can be obtained by climbing the mountains.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Dewa Sanzan, Mystic Mountains of Prayers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qY8iSSBY#sY9KSVVpE5ws5iW82g063w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T00:01:01.318Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T23:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0179738530d16b10f5cd526ed219e98b8381bdce27a6aec1f7580e1b469c223a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dewa Sanzan: Mystic Mountains of Prayers</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:30:07.683Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6IEyULTC#4WNfofw8PD71ZQXdvf7NcQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>094</airingId>
    <content>Located in the mountains of Gifu Prefecture, Shirakawa-go is a village full of old-fashioned houses with thatched roofs - and a registered World Heritage Site. The roofs are steeply slanted, products of a building technique called Gassho-zukuri, which was born of the knowledge built up by surviving in an extraordinarily snowy region. The scenery in the 300-year-old town hasn't changed. Even now, time moves slowly. This is the story of the villagers of Shirakawa-go living hand-in-hand.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Shirakawa-go, Thatched-Roofed World Heritage Site.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VdoTXKSJ#KzjbeqUNMXQ4zWzJ1bPZXw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-30T00:00:27.627Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0dd088bba4b33dd78ab74694465f3f080ba90a21dbc19c4b112b2061e1590377</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shirakawa-go: Thatched-Roofed World Heritage Site</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:43:06.651Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ohciHD7I#ZEE4C2gsB9gsJosH_nWtFw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>116</airingId>
    <content>Japanese people have a long history of eating tofu, a filling food that always goes well with a drink. It is made simply by grinding and cooking soybeans, before extracting and solidifying the soymilk. In the mountains, unique varieties of tofu emerged as a result of efforts to avoid wasting the precious beans. In an area of heavy winter snowfall, tofu plays an important part in an annual religious ceremony. We explore the secrets of tofu from across the islands of Japan.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wNdnhCoJ#flnwGMpOQsW1_JRXgTFt9A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T00:00:28.689Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>e06792a7783de0276d03ed51648aa4509d4d65c05c377a1102757ff4d9a4d4cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Secrets of Tofu across Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:09:44.461Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W41QBD5C#UllkKI0RsaA4dB2TVnLaLA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>