<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-10T08:05:03.818Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>206e7d7b56906c70</seriesId>
  <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>032</airingId>
    <content>At the center of Naha City lies Kokusai Street, a symbol of modern Okinawa Prefecture as it was one of the first areas to reemerge after the grueling battles of the war. Stretching for 1.6km, the street was in fact once called "The Miracle Mile." Originally a black market bordering the American-occupied zone, it became Okinawa's busiest shopping street, with 500 souvenir shops and restaurants. This episode focuses on the street's history and source of its prosperity: the diversity and dynamism of Okinawa.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: The Miracle Mile - Kokusai Street, Okinawa.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-16T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tc9XAQQb#NWOdDiBZCLlAOHt38Ix-iw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-16T00:00:29.631Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>bd08dc68c4b978a9c11bf2f751f9c2d26197e54e6f37e4b254dd0e410dceee7d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Miracle Mile - Kokusai Street, Okinawa</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:03:36.647Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SxEBDIZK#3ZwGbzblXHhkSIvKOQC0rQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>050</airingId>
    <content>The people of Tohoku have carved out their livelihoods, quietly enduring frigid, harsh winters. This is doubtlessly because the promise of spring awaits. The winter is the time spent waiting patiently for spring. They wait for the blocked roads to reappear. They wait for the melted snow to glisten. They wait for the flowers to go into full bloom and for the birds and insects to come dancing out for nectar. With these signals, the people begin their daily routines to live. We give thanks for the long-awaited season of warm water, are gladdened by the blooming flowers, and tour spring in Tohoku.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Spring in Tohoku.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-05T03:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2oRC0BqK#IlpWs8gyjCmOs49FxVQVBw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-05T03:00:26.797Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-05T02:29:22.635Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>700197e2742e45374db599a77dee26cf6218e0d70a1c265a560fd81f0b185a89</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-05T02:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Spring in Tohoku</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-05T04:12:58.470Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TlYEATzS#8R4kcMx39greWQePFYZVEQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>054</airingId>
    <content>Kirishima, a group of 20 mountains in the south of Kyushu. It is a volcanic area that was a central location in Japan's creation myth. Its name, meaning "fog island," refers to the way that the peaks look like an island rising above the clouds. Its high rate of rainfall creates springs and hot springs for the towns around it, and the volcanic ash it releases helps grow sweet potatoes that have fostered a shochu alcohol culture. As they receive the bounty of the mountains, the people there have created their own unique customs, and carved out their own way of living in harmony with an unforgiving environment. An old mountain guide struggles with volcanic ash as he seeks to reopen the area for tourism and mountain climbing. The people here's love for the region has no limits. Even though there are few jobs for the younger generation, they don't want to leave, and even those who do tend to come back. We will show you the strong, dynamic lifestyle of the people who live together with the Kirishima peaks.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Kirishima: A Town thriving on Volcanic Mountains.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PMlAyZoS#uL7eK8qoQzqQmZzpe8DcLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T00:00:28.617Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-13T23:29:23.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>a63580715cabc64e0765bfecc0911b9fc5f59eca8309a6cb126f1c0578758bc5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-13T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kirishima: A Town Thriving on Volcanic Mountains</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:37:26.309Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ytlCVJTI#zG06REziEu2lQ64wlDxVmA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>081</airingId>
    <content>The Sanriku Railway in Iwate Prefecture is a lifeline, playing an important role in the local community. The train goes up and down the line, and the arrival of the train is part of the rhythm of life. In March 2011, the railway was completely destroyed by the tsunami that followed the Great East Japan Earthquake. The road to recovery was a difficult one, and at one point, there was even talk of abolishing the line. The railway is now back on track, having finally resumed full service. We look back on the slow but steady restoration of the Sanriku Railway, over a period of 3 years.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Sanriku Railway, Back from the Brink.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/kFo2nDTS#c3JEHC1mnwok8HPo0ArtIw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-15T00:00:26.572Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-14T23:29:20.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>7c83554db047995166924645a73eab77ad4956657c39bfa44bb3523dccc8fb8b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-14T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sanriku Railway: Back from the Brink</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T02:49:57.131Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/q1gHwKbK#P8btZpEKSwDp4sCpt51N2w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>083</airingId>
    <content>1,200 years ago, Kukai, a well-known Japanese monk, made a pilgrimage through 88 sacred sites in the Japanese island of Shikoku. The route through all 88 sites is 1,400 kilometers long and loops around the island. Pilgrim's still come, with both anxiety and hope, to follow in Kukai's footsteps. Kukai told his followers that enlightenment knows one's own heart. The Shikoku Pilgrimage is a journey to find oneself, shedding one's spiritual baggage simply by walking. The pilgrim's journey around Shikoku brings unexpected encounters and lifelong memories.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: The Shikoku Pilgrimage.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/MIxUgJhB#uaWmqNERqWcecw4jA6yGOQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-25T00:00:28.578Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-24T23:29:24.041Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>ef6870ee43dc82000f63fa9a644b233b87f9d2004e7111d2a032c4f8b87804af</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-24T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Shikoku Pilgrimage</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-25T00:43:38.106Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IyxkXbID#aSpjL332r-D1vVGPQuyUsA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>Dewa Sanzan is located in the center of Yamagata Prefecture, in the Tohoku region of Japan. Mt. Haguro, Mt. Gassan and Mt. Yudono. Collectively, these 3 mountains are called Dewa Sanzan. The pilgrimage of Dewa Sanzan symbolizes the death and rebirth of a person. It is believed that something important can be obtained by climbing the mountains.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Dewa Sanzan, Mystic Mountains of Prayers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qY8iSSBY#sY9KSVVpE5ws5iW82g063w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T00:01:01.318Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T23:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0179738530d16b10f5cd526ed219e98b8381bdce27a6aec1f7580e1b469c223a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dewa Sanzan: Mystic Mountains of Prayers</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:30:07.683Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6IEyULTC#4WNfofw8PD71ZQXdvf7NcQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>090</airingId>
    <content>Tsukemono is a simple food made by pickling vegetables and other ingredients in seasonings such as salt and vinegar. It started as a preserved food, and some are made by fermentation. It is never the main dish, but is an essential part of the Japanese diet. Every region has its own special tsukemono. Tsukemono can be enjoyed not only for its taste, but also for its flavor, color and the sound it makes when chewed. We take a journey of tsukemono around Japan.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Tsukemono: Japan's Pickled Soul Food.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/jc9xiSgZ#G52P2eSQ7FohLwrKdet0RA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-18T00:00:31.358Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-17T23:29:20.125Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>79a87e84427cb6482a6a3e24ea371845626a64e7376b85f88784af5faa80b287</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-17T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tsukemono: Japan's Pickled Soul Food</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T03:25:29.990Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/CJ9z2CgA#UI3r8_t5a84XbvhJ425aow</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>091</airingId>
    <content>Kanazawa is in Ishikawa Prefecture, facing the Sea of Japan in the north. Here, far from Kyoto Prefecture and Tokyo, a great city was built in the age of the samurai, boasting 300 years of history. The first lord of this vast land, Maeda Toshiie, spared no effort in promoting culture such as crafts and the performing arts. This policy was carried on by his successors, and a small farming town transformed into a flourishing city of culture. An obsession with beauty has always thrived here. Hospitality that gratifies all the senses awaits you.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today, Kanazawa: An Eternal Love of Beauty and Culture.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZUUXESoa#Qs0AW6-gnTncJfnjNc1ZmA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-22T00:00:33.896Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-21T23:29:20.039Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>7d4dae3b610a9192abfa71d29fab0c77bb68191c01a25d47de0c4d4a939fb02a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-21T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kanazawa: An Eternal Love of Beauty and Culture</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-22T03:45:57.636Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/fQMHCKDD#uS3fj5DQRDbgET6PMqBAmA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>Kinosaki Onsen is a small town faces the Sea of Japan to its north, and is spread out between mountains. It is a hot springs, or an "onsen" resort in Hyogo Prefecture. About 100 "ryokan" or traditional Japanese inns line a 1-kilometer street, which are visited by 1 million tourists a year. The way to enjoy the hot springs here is to visit all of the 7 public baths in the town. A sparkling otherworldly thermal utopia built in the mountains. In this episode of Seasoning the Seasons, we visit a small hot springs resort that relaxes the body and mind.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Kinosaki Onsen - A Town of Hot Springs.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/juIDXI4Q#J_A6jvPdCRa_QjGrUg0Mbg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-01T00:00:30.540Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-31T23:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>769b0ee9e08aaaa67242d1038e3e183d46a470a411b6d10b4efc4431a71d7c9e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-31T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kinosaki Onsen: A Town of Hot Springs</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-01T01:41:19.785Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/13RCCJxQ#kyY9LkOklfiMvsE4YFzZ1Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>094</airingId>
    <content>Located in the mountains of Gifu Prefecture, Shirakawa-go is a village full of old-fashioned houses with thatched roofs - and a registered World Heritage Site. The roofs are steeply slanted, products of a building technique called Gassho-zukuri, which was born of the knowledge built up by surviving in an extraordinarily snowy region. The scenery in the 300-year-old town hasn't changed. Even now, time moves slowly. This is the story of the villagers of Shirakawa-go living hand-in-hand.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Shirakawa-go, Thatched-Roofed World Heritage Site.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-30T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VdoTXKSJ#KzjbeqUNMXQ4zWzJ1bPZXw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-30T00:00:27.627Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0dd088bba4b33dd78ab74694465f3f080ba90a21dbc19c4b112b2061e1590377</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shirakawa-go: Thatched-Roofed World Heritage Site</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:43:06.651Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ohciHD7I#ZEE4C2gsB9gsJosH_nWtFw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>095</airingId>
    <content>Otaru is a city in Hokkaido Prefecture with a canal flowing by the harbor. It was once a center of commerce where goods from all over Hokkaido were traded. People flocked to the city in search of prosperity and success, and the canal has kept the city flourishing. Here in Otaru, there are many old buildings with over 100 years of history. Though located in Asia, the city scenery is reminiscent of Europe. Over 100,000 foreign tourists arrive each year. This is the story of Otaru, a city that's grown together with its canal.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Otaru, Classic Canal City.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-15T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/65JzwCKR#tRZmTIQSko2Anr4p988CgQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-15T00:00:28.203Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-14T23:29:20.125Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>d6473080e279335e7059fa6cbc1679b4a6fbb492520213e68624b15474e4bb62</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-14T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Otaru: Classic Canal City</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T05:54:03.252Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/fpEWBT5Z#1aW3zRp280b2CU4Y3cR0pQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>096</airingId>
    <content>Mount Tsukuba is located in Ibaraki Prefecture, about 70 km northeast from Tokyo. The Japanese have revered the mountain since ancient times, as a sacred mountain akin to Mount Fuji. The mountain has a height of 877 meters. Mount Tsukuba, called Tsukuba-san in Japanese, is popular with visitors as anyone can easily climb it. More than 2 million people visit a year. From the old days, it has been believed that a mysterious force dwells in this mountain. In this episode, we present the story of Mount Tsukuba, a sacred mountain rich in mysterious charm.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today: Mount Tsukuba; The Mysterious Twin Peaks.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OwskDIyJ#abZEOKOp-8C1FZtKRcV9yw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T00:00:28.585Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T23:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>ebf68ceade988d09f845f5029b008c390aecc2184d53a8de284e938a1ae0c1a6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mount Tsukuba: The Mysterious Twin Peaks</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T04:29:14.630Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OksVQaQZ#TSqV-1QAAoTJ4F51gRpAaw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>097</airingId>
    <content>The town of Miharu in Fukushima Prefecture, eastern Japan, is renowned for its cherry blossoms. Once the long winter has passed and the cherry blossoms bloom, many tourists come to visit the usually quiet countryside. The main tourist attraction is a tree designated as a national natural monument, the Takizakura, meaning Waterfall Cherry Tree. There are more than 10,000 cherry trees all around the town.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today, Cherry Blossoms will Bloom: Miharu, Fukushima.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-29T08:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/h8wiXCLA#DuYc3VyZfNfqScrLTIUNqw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-29T08:00:28.969Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-29T07:29:23.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>7c347213d5a82b2007045db481162c8de5493f4b89bcd362c1620004cc4a5224</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-29T07:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Cherry Blossoms will Bloom: Miharu, Fukushima</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-29T12:57:44.688Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/s1hmERJI#7HCDIazpQK__yeFm5Kbqkg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>106</airingId>
    <content>Kobe was founded about 150 years ago as an international trading port. Various cultures from around the world have gathered here over the decades. Japan's first tailor-made men's clothing store was opened in Kobe. The custom of eating foreign cuisine in Japan also started here more than 100 years ago. Kobe is a city where various cultures co-exist like a mosaic painting. This is a story of people who live a hardy life in a beautiful harbor city.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today, Kobe: A City of Cultural Mosaic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-11T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/kdNkVTJS#daq_wcUkHcUE7k3Vpz6LvQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-11T00:00:38.629Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-10T23:29:20.018Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>a84c4198ee5f153e01fcbf1ae7f97f5dcfa14d2ac71332ff838e8bcbf8f17a2e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-10T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kobe: A City of Cultural Mosaic</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T10:40:14.702Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qJtm0QIb#kvH6gTzkk6kKf8wPqVQ5dQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>107</airingId>
    <content>The district of Maana in Ehime Prefecture is a leading center for mikan cultivation. Mikan is the Japanese name for the fruit Citrus unshiu, a type of mandarin, which is popular among Japanese people for its health benefits and sweet, fruity taste. The Maana mikan are known for a delicate balance between sweetness and tanginess. In Maana, around 180 farming families grow mikan. All of the farmers produce the same high-quality mikan which is known under the Maana Brand.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history. Today, Mikan: Japan's Favorite Citrus Fruit.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/k9YmSDQb#6tC92qZKmSjApR5lCkzawA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-08T00:00:27.419Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-07T23:29:20.127Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>24609a086691b435c01df60ab4e7224f94d790e1f1e3679812b87e69cf26fe18</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-07T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mikan: Japan's Favorite Citrus Fruit</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-09T11:13:30.391Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/zI0ADLhC#qnA1e2XcYKLDIv--5u8Tkw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>111</airingId>
    <content>The Tsugaru Strait is a rough sea between the Japanese island of Honshu and Hokkaido to the north. At its narrowest point, it is just 18.7km across. The other side is far yet near, near yet far. For many years, people have traveled across the waters. This is the story of people who live life to the full either side of the Tsugaru Strait.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HhJEGDzZ#gQU-O4LE1gHqHGHgWi5aFA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-22T00:00:30.541Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-21T23:29:20.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>0c286f5c47bdb4b0b76cd12048a88cfd5a4768f72a3ddc451fe1453f4cba9780</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-21T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tsugaru Strait: Life Stories of Crossing the Rough Seas</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-30T13:52:50.420Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7hoEQbBI#qp7sj7mpFV4YfJ8BOsyJlQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>116</airingId>
    <content>Japanese people have a long history of eating tofu, a filling food that always goes well with a drink. It is made simply by grinding and cooking soybeans, before extracting and solidifying the soymilk. In the mountains, unique varieties of tofu emerged as a result of efforts to avoid wasting the precious beans. In an area of heavy winter snowfall, tofu plays an important part in an annual religious ceremony. We explore the secrets of tofu from across the islands of Japan.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wNdnhCoJ#flnwGMpOQsW1_JRXgTFt9A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T00:00:28.689Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>e06792a7783de0276d03ed51648aa4509d4d65c05c377a1102757ff4d9a4d4cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Secrets of Tofu across Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:09:44.461Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W41QBD5C#UllkKI0RsaA4dB2TVnLaLA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>119</airingId>
    <content>Soba noodles made from buckwheat flour have been a part of the Japanese diet even longer than rice. Today, we will take a journey across Japan to sample soba. In the past, soba repeatedly saved people from starvation as buckwheat grows in poor soil and can be harvested in just 75 days. Soba has long remained a familiar part of Japanese cuisine and culture. Even if you're low on cash, or having trouble getting along with others, a simple bowl of soba can help you feel better.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PgVRjKiB#6uswqfwZkCpQWDYQn2RRrA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-07T00:00:35.982Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-06T23:29:20.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>bb8371f2dad7284f6efb60659ca8649ff61f8700649ee8a1140942f6e94042a0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-06T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Soba: Japan's Beloved Noodle</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:15:47.293Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SoVU3JjZ#t53hG0GVe_EnAyGAobZ9lw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>121</airingId>
    <content>Kamaishi, in Iwate Prefecture in northeastern Japan is home to a steelworks with a history of 130 years, and is known as a "city of steel." Before the end of World War II, Kamaishi suffered a direct attack by the Allied Forces because of its steelworks. Then came the Great East Japan Earthquake in 2011. This is the story of Kamaishi, a city that has experienced many adversities, but has managed to rise above them.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IXYXFAgI#HsUBUTlW6uoejMyiY2LHVg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-08T00:00:28.866Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-07T23:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>e3633d9bf4eb4413204261f74c4a752f26b28c7f8212bd4d82324eaf6f7f75e1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-07T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kamaishi: The Resilient City of Steel</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-08T01:14:05.049Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gDJxwSSQ#vHtgJ5OtGc2qhxB2_efNpA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>133</airingId>
    <content>A classic winter cuisine in Japan that is popular in the colder months is "nabe," or hot pot. The pot is usually placed in the middle of the dining table, and everyone takes from it. Every region in Japan has hot pots and broths that locals are proud of. There're always smiles around the hot pot. In this episode of Seasoning the Seasons, we go up and down the Japanese islands in search of stories of happiness surrounding the hot pot.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/n9MhiKTL#HaVO3sJO641YkmIF7gNITw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-04T00:00:34.544Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-03T23:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>cb981cc641d1f9924d107eb672704e0cfbd22045b09544e44ced5fc63fa9b0bb</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-03T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sharing Happiness: Hot Pots in Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T10:32:24.499Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/NAJDBASS#QUW7RjsZDhK610ImAFVsfA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>134</airingId>
    <content>Mount Iwate is a mountain that the people of Iwate always look up to. Standing at 2,038 meters above sea level, the locals are proud of this beautiful sight. Mount Iwate is an active volcano that has been erupting repeatedly for 700,000 years, and has undergone 7 major sector collapses to reach its current form. The large amount of volcanic ash and rocks that fell created vast foothills of the mountain. In this episode, we take a look at people living in the embrace of Mount Iwate.</content>
    <description>This program visits places across Japan to introduce the charms of their local daily life and festivals fostered by the nation's long history.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/q1pVwKyR#fJL2E9PmXYVY7D1ycbEqTA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-01T00:00:32.889Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-28T23:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2024</seriesId>
    <sha256>d49c0105c93bbf1f2c146f3f1608e8aa6be015ddab26322b747dc36df07fa0ad</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-28T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mount Iwate: Guardian of the Homeland</subtitle>
    <title>Seasoning the Seasons</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-01T01:04:46.244Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yxsBySJB#61nwBAw-MzDWqvHbQCGD6Q</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>