<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-01T01:45:04.083Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>2ac7100c81ee10d6</seriesId>
  <title>Lunch ON!</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>124</airingId>
    <content>Lunch for Rie Tamakoshi, a ward office employee in Shizuoka Prefecture, is far from conventional. She eats rice balls on the run! She's too busy balancing work and raising her kids to sit down and enjoy lunch. During her lunch break, she runs home while she eats, and once at her house, she does the laundry, cleans, and preps dinner before running back to her office again.
In another segment, we visit the southernmost prefecture of Okinawa to meet a public health nurse who has a surprising lunch of her own.</content>
    <description>Lunch for Rie Tamakoshi, a ward office employee in Shizuoka, is far from conventional, because she eats rice balls on the run! She's too busy balancing work and raising her kids to be enjoying lunch.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T08:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7ZliyCaa#V8wUrCPPi8T9fBDrNxkCvg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T08:55:26.792Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T08:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>e4c2b59cc1e66969faecd4ca74dcd63a33875a77feaae9e68c3d90006eabf721</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T08:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch on the Run</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T21:20:30.521Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JRpwgAgR#STjcGnTfFgE6YW-nyIwl3g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>141</airingId>
    <content>We go to Toyama Prefecture, central Japan to visit a factory that makes fishcake called "kamaboko." Although "kamaboko" is eaten all across Japan, those made here are especially decorative, as the local culture is to give them to guests who come to weddings and other celebratory occasions. Fresh fish is ground down to paste at 5 in the morning, and the product is shipped out in the evening. As the workers start so early, lunchtime comes at around 8. We look at the bento lunches of the fishcake makers.</content>
    <description>We go to a factory in central Japan that makes fishcake called "kamaboko." Kamaboko made here are decorative, as the local culture is to give them to guests who come to celebratory occasions.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vp8GhTIA#L-y2Hti_GtniP5iL3wbFqA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T04:55:21.229Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T04:29:22.768Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>2ffa389ad65d79fd5bd99825f6942585a02247239edf7392b57316267e8de2a6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch at the Fishcake Factory</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:58:55.288Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6V8GxCzB#kWoDwxJRZcegycJ6EivTAQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>142</airingId>
    <content>We go to Shizuoka Prefecture, central Japan to visit a helicopter life flight team. The team consists of doctors, nurses, pilots, mechanics and dispatchers. They stand by at all times, ready to provide emergency care to patients in remote areas. For them, there's not a single second that can be wasted when a call comes in about a life that needs to be saved. When it comes to lunch, they eat when they can, but as soon as that call comes in, they jump right back into action.</content>
    <description>We go to central Japan to visit a helicopter life flight team that consists of doctors, nurses, pilots, mechanics and dispatchers. They stand by at all times, ready to save people in remote areas.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ylEilTyT#zn65_-ByNnLDo8y8RKGQrQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T04:55:24.480Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T04:29:20.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>56c39d52b0225114aaf22c5717dbb69fcc6ab5a9f7000c6d6588753f8249a434</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunchtime for the Life Flight Team</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:37:55.705Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OlVQQbzQ#35mFkpAWUIvYJD7d9oNlNQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>143</airingId>
    <content>We visit an ironworks situated in Yamagata Prefecture, northern Japan. At the factory, there is a monthly lunch day wherein the staff take turns cooking soups from other countries. The task wouldn't be that difficult if they were allowed to use a recipe and have access to the right ingredients, but since the aim of this lunch tradition is to train the workers' ability to use their imagination to make things, the staff do just that, improvising as they go along.</content>
    <description>We visit an ironworks situated in Yamagata Pref., northern Japan. At the factory, there is a monthly lunch day wherein the staff take turns cooking soups from other countries.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-11T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fpkkFYxD#vYxenyZWtSaaNuuEqFhZzA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-11T04:55:30.290Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-11T04:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>b4bf317fb88ff0fa911365801479c70837ee496f64d31cab8759b033582044a5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-11T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Soups of the World</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T14:08:30.652Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SptgBI7I#dqbQ3jkAVHhvNb9btW5kwA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>144</airingId>
    <content>We visit a coffee plantation in Okinawa, Japan's southernmost prefecture. The plantation is run by a family, and what is surprising is that they only recently began growing coffee. They used to mainly grow flowers, but after suffering much damage from a typhoon, the father decided the switch on his own, without even running the numbers! To stay afloat, the son has to work hard, but he has no complaints because the coffee they make tastes great, and his father is having the time of his life!</content>
    <description>We visit a coffee plantation in Okinawa, Japan's southernmost prefecture. The plantation is run by a family, and what is surprising is that they only recently switched from growing flowers to coffee.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-18T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HxcQFBaJ#h0Iod0ZuTVsyAMP2PR95mQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-18T04:55:29.140Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-18T04:29:22.625Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>7636c51aa803e63aebc10bab3462f9aab42512af16f2240f23e474952baff1cc</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-18T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch at the Coffee Plantation</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-18T06:18:52.229Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/usFwnTYA#1okVVVXwWwgItI9lB1Mh6w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>148</airingId>
    <content>We go to Hyogo Prefecture, western Japan to visit a factory that handcrafts scissors for hairstylists. Scissors for cutting hair have to cut extremely well, and the process to customize scissors so that they can do just that demands unthinkable exactness. At this factory, they even handle repairs of scissors that are decades old, but that task can only be carried out by the best, most experienced technicians. Tune in to find out the detailed work of scissor crafters and also what they do for lunch.</content>
    <description>We go to Hyogo, western Japan to visit a factory that handcrafts professional scissors for hairstylists. Tune in to find out the detailed work of scissor crafters and also what they do for lunch.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-25T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xWg3gI7J#tVcK2miOvqBquuhuwvdaPg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-25T04:55:25.486Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-25T04:29:23.351Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>31d71a1f0db4c5db3aca3e5dc0f701b8c68244941c922cbff0a2fae47dfe0a84</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-25T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunchtime for the Scissor Makers</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-25T07:04:26.061Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/QJ9DGQpK#yf5sk0xGQ0KKNUeWRnN-TA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>155</airingId>
    <content>Mt. Fuji is the highest mountain in Japan, and at its summit, there is a shrine. The man who cooks for the shrine priests 3 times a day is actually a total amateur. However, he does have a lot of experience as a mountaineer, and that's what landed him the job. And it's okay that he's not the most experienced chef, because he is armed with recipes written by his beloved wife. Plus, if even that is not enough, he can always call her to ask for emergency cooking advice!</content>
    <description>At the summit of Mt. Fuji, the highest mountain in Japan, there is a shrine. The man who cooks for the priests three times a day is an amateur, but he gets the job done with the help of his wife!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AAtWULKL#b3yWmuHE8N6x7BxNStKnhw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T04:55:24.566Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T04:29:20.042Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>c619fb718abfd865893df98512b25c222cf5d8c10651b1ded345e76ffda33e54</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch at the Shrine atop Mt. Fuji</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:56:15.332Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TktTUKxA#r88QfpmISL_F7ziTHgQRSQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>156</airingId>
    <content>We visit Chiba, the prefecture that neighbors Tokyo, to go to one of Japan's largest mushroom farms. At the farm, they grow massive amounts of mushrooms but surprisingly, each mushroom is harvested by hand. To feed their hard-working employees, the farm renovated what was formerly the home economics room of a school to set up their very own bento kitchen. At the kitchen, they cook up delicious dishes that feature a whole lot of mushrooms, every day!</content>
    <description>We visit Chiba, the prefecture that neighbors Tokyo, to go to one of Japan's largest mushroom farms. Every day for lunch, the workers have mushroom bento cooked in the farm's very own kitchen!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xBIR2QRb#qaDqqS_K0VduWjcYiqIitQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T04:55:30.767Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T04:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>3e01796286af8221f62b579cb2a814fdd86d4c1f7d0de2340d8148156a55984b</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch at the Mushroom Farm</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:13:22.173Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cc1yRCZa#XXwAgL-b0WeLhaGliTyKFg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>157</airingId>
    <content>The Shinshu Buddhist Otani-ha Sect Namba Betsuin Temple in Osaka Prefecture, western Japan, has been loved by the local people since it was founded in 1595. Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the local people had been unable to go to their beloved temple during spring this year, but in summer, the temple decided to hold memorial services for the local people during the Obon Festival, a period when Japanese people honor the spirits of their ancestors. Behind the scenes, one of the senior monks cooks up a filling vegetable curry so that the hard-chanting monks can charge up on energy!</content>
    <description>Namba Betsuin, a Buddhist temple in Osaka, western Japan, has been loved by the local people since 1595. For lunch, a senior monk cooks up some delicious-looking vegetable curry for the other monks.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T08:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FIR21LAR#oYAjV208T3HLQSB_Z6oI4Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T08:55:36.452Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T08:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>b66329e52a65beada28a968adcccf06485c7c3e29fc9c3faf14b4f7fc8e967f3</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T08:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lunch at the Buddhist Temple</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T09:30:00.232Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cYU0GJaA#4FaUr2oXAVDz3vmLB8MrZw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>158</airingId>
    <content>We set up a video camera in the cafeteria of a company in Tokyo that makes all kinds of educational products. With the camera, equipped with a mic and speakers, we remotely interview the workers who sit down to eat lunch. First, we talk with a group of ladies who work from home a few days a week. Then, we talk with a man who used to travel across the country all the time for work. Since the pandemic, he's been unable to travel at all, so he eats an Okinawan dish to at least travel in spirit!</content>
    <description>We set up a video camera in the cafeteria of a company in Tokyo that makes all kinds of educational products. With the camera, we conduct remote interviews of the workers who sit down to eat lunch.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-07T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2ElWmbyQ#PVtzsFoWqKeyZcGfs5nmQw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-07T04:55:29.235Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-07T04:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>a5016dcf9e2139306dc22779ec669addd5f0cb89f92177f258b0077ae8fa444b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-07T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Remote Camera Interview in the Cafeteria</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-07T05:56:31.777Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jRV0lDaC#OSSrJsbYzoH0dunXD7PUzQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>159</airingId>
    <content>In the district of Tomonoura, Hiroshima Prefecture, there is a company that offers a golf cart taxi service. Even though the carts are slow, they have many advantages: their small size allows easy passage through narrow alleyways, and since there are no windows, it's easy to greet neighbors when passing them by on the street. We follow a man who drives this taxi, and discover where he always has delicious lunch.</content>
    <description>In the district of Tomonoura, Hiroshima, there is a company that offers a golf cart taxi service. We follow a man who drives this taxi, and discover where he always has delicious lunch.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-28T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/jvZnVYJC#HGu98LicP313LzcGXXW5pw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-28T04:55:28.204Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-28T04:29:22.748Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>2c342fe7e7314a0d01e2a0a4fb0c1b99db4dc2b1929ce93b0bf2e8626bab7a25</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-28T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Next-Generation Taxi in Hiroshima</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-28T05:34:39.475Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Uqg2DTZS#IDa9vn8fxevmkUZ35_Rcmg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>160</airingId>
    <content>Echizen Railway is a third-sector train company in Fukui Prefecture, a prefecture located on the coast of the Sea of Japan. Since with limited funds, it is difficult to rebuild stations and trains to make them more accessible, or make new facilities, the attendant program was introduced. Yamazaki Nanami is an attendant fresh out of high school, and even though the work is tough, she gets through it all with a smile thanks to the tasty bento her grandmother cooks for her every day.</content>
    <description>Nanami works in Fukui Prefecture, helping customers as a train attendant. The work is tough, but she gets through it all with a smile thanks to the bento her grandmother cooks for her every day.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-04T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wbwhXSSb#taRR5TMjJHrHeXBjRkdw2A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-04T04:55:30.547Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-04T04:29:20.125Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4023</seriesId>
    <sha256>fe4d5938fbc2034b649b12d32a7aab2af7cc937c609764622323c0e1e773857c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-04T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Rookie Train Attendant</subtitle>
    <title>Lunch ON!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-04T23:29:17.623Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/lax12KaC#qgmOC-eeMSdvaTJ0gj8O1Q</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>