<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-12T17:10:05.355Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>2db080459cbd9d82</seriesId>
  <title>GATTEN!</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>001</airingId>
    <content>Eating, talking, laughing ... all actions made possible by your jaw. You simply can't live without it. But a surprising number of people have tightness or pain in their jaw -- 19 million in Japan alone. And if this issue gets worse, it can lead to depression, loss of appetite and more. In 2018, the 1st guidelines for this "tight jaw" condition were released in Japan, including some simple treatment methods you can do yourself. An expert shows us how to loosen our jaw muscles by stretching and massaging them. Do this once in the morning and once at night, and you could see amazing results!</content>
    <description>Eating, talking, laughing...all made possible by your jaw. But 19 million people in Japan alone have tightness in their jaw that could lead to more serious issues. We learn how to combat "tight jaw."</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-01T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/uIJGmDLA#DyCVPe7VoeYoV0A0Bq7Y8Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-01T04:55:30.127Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-01T04:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4031</seriesId>
    <sha256>1a986c54208509f4f02045df34cf2cb75e267a89fc9b2144123df5a0c7f4277c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-01T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Mystery of the Tight Jaw!</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-01T06:17:13.930Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/RbBAiBLS#V6TMxfQMbBqGUD60BkhBJQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>005</airingId>
    <content>The number one problem that seniors have with urination is nocturia --frequent nighttime urination. Getting up to use the toilet several times a night can disrupt your sleep and even lead to depression or serious injury. Many people think nocturia is an inevitable part of getting old, but we now know that most cases have a specific cause: the water you consume during the day is being stored up in a certain part of your body ... and it's not your bladder. However, with some easy methods anyone can do, you can reduce your nocturia!</content>
    <description>You might think that frequent nighttime urination is an inevitable part of getting older, but we know now it usually has a specific cause that some easy methods can help to prevent!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Mw02gYTY#Q-I1RwrSqifHHpSVN-84rA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T04:55:25.273Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T04:09:20.122Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4031</seriesId>
    <sha256>f096d43f8f4809fc45f09ee61f6fed3444ae1cb6b1c9bb12a1fa5b05270d0f00</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ending Nighttime Urination</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T05:15:45.953Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/eVcUyBJY#bdkBYEbx0a3AKYU4jIaHJA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>006</airingId>
    <content>Video calling has existed for a while, but in the face of COVID-19, it's become more vital than ever to our daily lives. Using a device like a computer or a smartphone, you can connect with other people remotely, seeing and hearing them live. It's easy and extremely convenient. But why do video calls sometimes feel awkward or listless? We found a surprising pitfall ... and a simple action you can do to avoid it! Follow our advice, and everyone on your call will feel engaged and in sync!</content>
    <description>Video calls are more vital than ever to our daily lives, but they can sometimes feel awkward or listless. We reveal a simple action that will have everyone on your call feeling engaged and in sync!</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-06T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/I9sUmKAZ#cmGP3Ep_rtHzp62LCu2QxA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-06T04:55:23.660Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-06T04:09:20.121Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4031</seriesId>
    <sha256>69563490a69fa6651cd3e36dd6cc87d79e6814db9b3b248ae46300900a170be7</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-06T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How to Have Better Video Calls</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T21:45:01.544Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/poVnQAYK#DrToGTKV7Qt-s5kfDDp7uQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>007</airingId>
    <content>It is estimated that 1 in 6 people in Japan suffer from dry eye. Your eyes become uncomfortable, itchy and painful, making it hard to concentrate on your work ... or do to work at all for very long. Typically, tears cover and protect the cornea, the important surface layer of the eye that sits over the iris and pupil. But if your eyes are dry, your corneas can end up exposed, and ultimately damaged. And although dry eye often stems from a lack of tears, there is another possible cause! We cover the latest dry eye research, and offer techniques to remedy dry eye that you can try at home!</content>
    <description>Uncomfortable, painful, dry eyes can make work and day-to-day life more difficult. We investigate the causes of dry eye. For some people it is a lack of tears but for some people it's something else.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-03T11:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rRoQjDLB#FYhGdBFgKxHKsg4V2ilCcA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-03T11:55:25.507Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-03T11:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4031</seriesId>
    <sha256>c53c6af93f027443e3aa6361d54c163f365f53a35316f715bcb6e423928ea728</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-03T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Remedy for Dry Eye</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-03T15:06:14.967Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/PZZXzCrB#V4gMYtXKwxUw2YHpoFSAgA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>