<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-28T01:20:03.649Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>31851bb3dfae7f8a</seriesId>
  <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>114</airingId>
    <content>"Sauce." In Japan, this word refers to a rich, dark, bottled sauce sold in a number of varieties. Used on deep-fried foods like pork cutlets and Japanese croquettes, plus savory okonomiyaki pancakes, yakisoba noodles and more, this viscous sauce is an essential part of Japanese comfort cooking. But what is sauce made of? Even many Japanese people don't know! This time, we explore a sauce so essential, it's simply known as "sauce"!</content>
    <description>"Sauce." In Japan, this word refers to a rich, dark, bottled sauce used on deep-fried foods,savory okonomiyaki pancakes, yakisoba noodles and more. Learn more about Japan's essential sauce.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OtMi0LDZ#5wQps4_gA1tpAmP5hNmpfA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T14:59:23.353Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T14:29:20.121Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>13a1f699fe10a2465fb13d759249f4e25ce304ec3f1b4aa2848c7f6c1da75fe5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>SAUCE</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:50:37.176Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/EMVhFAyS#_6xEUfZbzwWayAic5v-zRQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>115</airingId>
    <content>Honey -- the world's oldest sweetener. Japan being home to both the Western honey bee and the native honey bee makes for numerous honey varieties. Concerned about the decline in global bee populations, urbanites take on rooftop beekeeping in Japan's capital. Also visit beekeeping sites responsible for precious honey varieties that are increasingly at risk. Fly around and discover infinite flavors born of differing environments and flower varieties.</content>
    <description>Our focus this time is honey. Innovations like urban beekeeping are born of a global bee crisis. Differing flowers and environments offer infinite flavors in this fascinating world of honey.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/H5tgCJzZ#eMthWFHx1Ut55K-laygtDA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T15:00:31.572Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>1462689939c9eee9407e4b4c6b6b90530ceda72dd2f3f108beb0f4edbdc4ac21</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>HONEY</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:59:47.439Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/f4ElVQSB#JSaqm4tPTciEzJUFaptSKA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>116</airingId>
    <content>Japanese pears are large, round, juicy and have a great crunch. Chiba Prefecture, which neighbors Tokyo, is known as Japan's largest pear producer. Every autumn, its so-called "Pear Street" fills up with farmers hawking their wares. Those farmers have thought up clever ways to make large, sweet pears, like growing branches across horizontal trellises that match the farmer's height. That lets the pears get plenty of sunlight and makes harvesting easier. Join us as we bite into Japan's world of pears!</content>
    <description>Japanese pears are large, round, juicy and have a great crunch. We visit Chiba, Japan's largest producer, to discover the ingenuity and effort behind Japan's giant sweet pears.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AFEXzQoD#KU0IZ8Zd4D-DlEDV8xn-PQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T15:00:31.959Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T14:29:22.743Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>d95842cbefa97112f4dd7bba3ae79374a1125d29c18b49257f1691f90f512d20</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>PEAR</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-23T23:43:24.100Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5IZwlTpJ#lpMLT3980-5SV0TfQ4GHjQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>117</airingId>
    <content>Sato-imo, eaten in Japan for some 3,000 years, is a type of taro, a root vegetable that grows in the tropics of Asia. Coming into season in autumn, Sato-imo have been used in sacred rites and other traditional rituals since ages past, and deeply rooted in Japanese culture. We learn how their unique, sticky texture and al dente mouthfeel make them essential for Japanese cuisine. Join us as we take a bite into healthy, low-calorie Sato-imo.</content>
    <description>Sato-imo: a type of taro eaten in Japan for some 3,000 years. Used in traditional rituals, they're deeply rooted in Japanese culture. Learn how their sticky texture is enjoyed in Japanese cuisine.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-13T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3lI1VI6A#1bHR4ORxe0dtTru5sDIDdw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-13T15:01:28.168Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-13T14:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>bbb448fc17c27ee387e1ce7853d0a25d0e19fcda6e9f731f778958797d7b7b40</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-13T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>SATO-IMO</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T20:49:04.035Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/fMMxwQBI#M7gQgeoUZbkH1nQPKOl7TQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>118</airingId>
    <content>Our focus this time is sesame. It's an indispensable part of Japanese cuisine, making the country a leading consumer. Whether used as-is, roasted, ground, or processed into oil, the Japanese have developed numerous ways to enjoy the savory aroma and texture of sesame seeds. They're also a key ingredient in Shojin Ryori, or vegetarian meals prepared for Buddhist monks. Discover the large role that tiny sesame seeds play.</content>
    <description>Our focus today is sesame. The seeds are widely used in Japan, making the country a main consumer. They're also a key part of the Buddhist vegetarian diet. Enter the large world of tiny sesame seeds.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-20T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HMdWlZjC#beoy7ehkLFc8BDBNos_c5w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-20T15:00:28.110Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-20T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>ab996dbc67c2b614daaa403d9ca69f5b668d9e4b766d02b9bd102d352c6c6bb8</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-20T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>SESAME</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-20T16:04:14.969Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/BSIikJqZ#6PNs3tnxOw3ZvUVAu7OuOg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>119</airingId>
    <content>Our focus this time is wasabi, the fiery root that is a pillar of Japanese foods like sushi and sashimi. Visit a traditional wasabi field in Shizuoka Prefecture recognized as one of the world's Globally Important Agricultural Heritage Systems, try futuristic wasabi dishes, and find out why you most likely need a new wasabi grater! (Reporter: Kyle Card)</content>
    <description>Our focus this time is wasabi. Visit a culturally significant paddy field, try a unique grater that offers stronger pungency, and learn more about the cultivation history of Japan's fiery root.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T21:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RU4hAKwZ#iaMZDJVOcAAsgPY8bHS90Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T21:00:27.884Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T20:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>90210278dc6e4b067ad93abd1608f0e6887dfbbdf8a8de1b59f24059357d851a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T20:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>WASABI</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T15:58:33.272Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HBU3HAxA#5Dmp6Rj8kdy__n1N2J-ncg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>120</airingId>
    <content>In Japan, peanuts are often eaten as-is, without flavoring or processing. That's because consumers want to taste the peanuts' own sweet, aromatic flavor. This time, we visit Japan's largest peanut production area, Chiba Prefecture, and learn about a traditional, machine-free drying method that gets the most sweetness out of the peanuts. We also sample a variety of local peanut dishes, meet scientists who spend some 15 years perfecting each new variety, and even try peanut ramen! (Reporter: Jason Hancock)</content>
    <description>Peanuts are often eaten as-is in Japan: consumers want the peanuts' own sweet, aromatic flavor. We visit Japan's largest production area to see how sweet peanuts are made and sample local dishes.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-09T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/BIlGgTRJ#--ZBosQKaNXw8mqWALBEbw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-09T15:00:25.375Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-09T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>1d7f1817d80ef0a25c2a64742bfd91aeeaaf3934b9e2fa48e18ead3dcc24222e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-09T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>PEANUTS</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:43:15.970Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/bBkBiYKK#NVZM0UzvB5QcZgYrG7NMaQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>121</airingId>
    <content>Some 200 varieties of Togarashi peppers are cultivated in Japan, most of which are dried and used as spices. We visited the largest production site to lend a hand in the fiery red fields and discovered special techniques for enhancing pungency and umami. "Super-spicy" foods ranging from snacks to full meals are a recent craze in Japan. Find out more as our reporter stands up to the challenge! (Reporter: Janni Olsson)</content>
    <description>Our focus today is togarashi peppers. Some 200 varieties are grown in Japan, providing a kick to both classic dishes and "super-spicy" cuisine, a recent craze. Feel the heat of Japan's pepper world.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sdwUxJTS#3D9A-9L4rPdeX_TGXtse6Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T15:00:25.064Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T14:29:20.172Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>29dd4ad1fe52788917eb8d25b3b1cd3fe4cc57ee34591b45dd67dba3a3a6f2f3</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>TOGARASHI PEPPER</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:46:14.933Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jolj1A7Q#uSI8rzEV3g3t_SnsoA1WKQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>122</airingId>
    <content>Our focus today is cutlassfish. This shiny samurai sword of the sea has no scales and swims vertically. Our reporter visits the fishing port that receives the largest haul, where 1,000 trailer trolleys and the family members of fishermen eagerly await to race the fish to market. Also, feast your eyes on savory tempura of minced cutlassfish meat containing its bones, curry featuring a 40-centimeter-long deep-fried cutlassfish, and a sushi bento that holds a unique place in Japanese history. (Reporter: Janni Olsson)</content>
    <description>Our focus today is cutlassfish. Join fisherman and their entire families in hauling 1,000 trailer trolleys of the fish. Also see it fried whole with its bones, and discover a traditional sushi bento.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-30T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/BJ0wTJLA#ithkCXArrFTF1q58jx8osg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-30T15:00:34.365Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-30T14:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>72a63a3db0ab38168876317220341ac12f852c9cc901366b1dee7112a0776677</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-30T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>CUTLASSFISH</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-30T18:56:32.227Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/pUsmETDD#bVoB22xTnURLPgCpefL5HA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>123</airingId>
    <content>Azuki beans are often sweetened, simmered and used in Japanese sweets. Their red color is said to ward off evil, and they're key at celebrations too. We visit an area in Hyogo Prefecture known for growing high-quality Azuki, and learn how artisans in Kyoto Prefecture put their skills to work making beautiful sweets that incorporate the beans. Learn all about Azuki beans, grown, eaten and beloved for over 5,000 years in Japan. (Reporter: Saskia Thoelen)</content>
    <description>Azuki beans are sweetened, simmered and used in Japanese sweets. Their red color is said to ward off evil, and they're key at celebrations. Learn all about azuki, grown for over 5,000 years in Japan.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fclSABhK#slMoGUxzOUpFFaHtHoKdUA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T15:00:30.332Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T14:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>2dbb4835ed7f33746a39563bbd3b8588264dfc6cf4c6d6a948352bdacf5631e6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>AZUKI BEAN</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T16:36:56.355Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gV9mFQJb#v73omLl9gD7sS52XQYCwtw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>124</airingId>
    <content>Our focus today is fugu, or pufferfish. As one of Japan's great winter delicacies, it is eaten as nearly-transparent slices of sashimi, or in umami-packed hot pots. Even in seafood-loving Japan, fugu is a special treat that is among the most expensive fish. It's also known for containing lethal amounts of poison, requiring chefs to obtain a special license in order to prepare it. Dive in to learn more about the various methods devised to provide quality flavor while also ensuring safety. (Reporter: Kyle Card)</content>
    <description>Fugu - a Japanese winter delicacy. Handling the highly poisonous fish requires a special license. Discover several methods devised to ensure quality flavor, and above all, your safety.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-27T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AHJmCRyI#AFn40q4U24vvPpp-J7d11g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-27T15:00:28.979Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-27T14:29:20.064Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>0677699940bc6c86665444bcb47a0d73b6979ea63d32e96d95da00c675163b87</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-27T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>FUGU</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-27T16:18:56.813Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wyZECZSL#cZqlNfr6PWwf_GRZkEpLyg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>125</airingId>
    <content>Daikon, Japanese radishes, are often over 30cm long, large and white, but there are also colorful types ranging from pink to green. They're an essential ingredient used in stews, salads, miso soup and more. We visit the Miura Peninsula, where half the daikon eaten in the Tokyo region are grown. There, we discover a "curtain" of thousands of daikon drying on a beach, soil supplemented with ground tuna, and the skills of those involved in daikon production. (Reporter: Jason Hancock)</content>
    <description>Daikon, Japanese radishes, are often over 30cm long, large and white. They're used in stews, salads, miso soup and more. We visit the Miura Peninsula, where half the daikon eaten in Tokyo are grown.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-03T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VEtkzagI#C9avjUzKKmoAe3vgtvsJ5w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-03T15:00:28.758Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-03T14:29:20.122Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2054</seriesId>
    <sha256>08b156ae947d5d0cdfa1324ccc17c90b0bf259f3599fd36434a33f41edac00e4</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-03T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>DAIKON</subtitle>
    <title>Trails to Oishii Tokyo</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-05T23:47:06.401Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1Zo0nDBY#k-z5-8tPMD74m8rwBdRQKQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>