<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T03:40:02.572Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>328f69455964a591</seriesId>
  <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>007</airingId>
    <content>COVID-19 poses a higher risk of serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Recent studies show that heart patients particularly have a high mortality rate. People with heart failure, a form of heart disease, have symptoms similar to COVID-19 and this can lead to late detection of the infection. What are the signs to look out for? How can heart patients prevent serious illness? Find out tips on what people with heart conditions can do in their daily lives.</content>
    <description>COVID-19 poses a higher risk of serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Heart patients particularly have a high mortality rate. Find out what they can do to protect themselves.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-08T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HwNW2J5b#VRxmokvwBE_EWDo7QqllKg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-08T04:55:23.530Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-08T04:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>d928261e44a7f7cf4ee0ac68a44beb04d1e3757669ffafa5be02145723811cce</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-08T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #1: Heart Disease</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T19:16:48.908Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>009</airingId>
    <content>Underlying health conditions are said to increase the risk for severe COVID-19. People with COPD (chronic obstructive pulmonary disease) mainly caused by smoking need to be especially careful. They are more susceptible to the novel coronavirus and to infection in general. This is due to the impaired function of the "cilia" in the airway that protects us from viruses. It's crucial to quit smoking and avoid becoming infected. Find out the precautions COPD patients should take to protect themselves.</content>
    <description>Underlying health conditions are said to increase the risk for severe COVID-19. Smokers and COPD patients need to be especially careful. Find out what COPD patients need to know about COVID-19.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/K1Nz1QqI#YZ7_h-ufGcNg6qf9IZN6nQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T04:55:27.822Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T04:44:20.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>f27b4db4e4f7ed87795abd948c3da5ffa7e9b688289f12d6cf6ad8eab3645884</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #3: COPD</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T06:51:17.777Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TYlCkB5B#MhPOw9QqLRZa3uqwN5ht4Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>017</airingId>
    <content>Glaucoma is the leading cause of blindness in many countries. An estimated 7.6 billion people are living with glaucoma worldwide. In Japan, it is the leading cause of visual impairment including blindness. 1 in 20 people over the age of 40 is reported to have glaucoma, but it's hard to detect. It is thought that 90% of people living with glaucoma are unaware of it. Why is the disease hard to notice? Find out how to detect glaucoma early in order to protect your vision.</content>
    <description>Glaucoma affects 7.6 billion people worldwide. In Japan, glaucoma is the leading cause of visual impairment, but it is hard to spot. Find out how to detect glaucoma early to protect your vision.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-01T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vh0SXaqZ#8c3forVwzAaP7JyKqixWjg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-01T04:55:30.590Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-01T04:44:20.017Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>94d9c56cb3c306ea3c5cacdd1a67c1a9631fde3a2770212a75e04822a3bf2bf2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-01T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #6: Glaucoma</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T10:55:26.091Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/9REglZjL#P2eM2mzdXx1sw0c23D5Cig</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>