<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-30T18:10:03.271Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>328f69455964a591</seriesId>
  <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>007</airingId>
    <content>COVID-19 poses a higher risk of serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Recent studies show that heart patients particularly have a high mortality rate. People with heart failure, a form of heart disease, have symptoms similar to COVID-19 and this can lead to late detection of the infection. What are the signs to look out for? How can heart patients prevent serious illness? Find out tips on what people with heart conditions can do in their daily lives.</content>
    <description>COVID-19 poses a higher risk of serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Heart patients particularly have a high mortality rate. Find out what they can do to protect themselves.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-08T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HwNW2J5b#VRxmokvwBE_EWDo7QqllKg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-08T04:55:23.530Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-08T04:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>d928261e44a7f7cf4ee0ac68a44beb04d1e3757669ffafa5be02145723811cce</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-08T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #1: Heart Disease</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T19:16:48.908Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/rx9GABrC#p3ZMoRPW9mXM_LFxD4BoNA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>008</airingId>
    <content>COVID-19 can cause serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Kidney disease patients, increasing globally, need to be extra careful. Recent studies found that immunosuppressive drugs used for treating kidney conditions increase the risk of infection. Furthermore, kidney patients that do get infected have a higher risk of developing pneumonia and even acute kidney injury. What can they do to avoid becoming severely ill from COVID-19? Find out coronavirus tips that kidney patients can apply in their everyday lives from an expert in treating kidney disease.</content>
    <description>COVID-19 can cause serious illness for people with underlying conditions. Kidney disease patients, increasing globally, need to be extra careful. We'll ask a doctor on what they can do to stay safe.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-15T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0wNA0JTJ#F6gVGT8aJYj-vv0lih5YCQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-15T04:55:27.795Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-15T04:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>56aa5b4e6aa88cec64a0ba82311b4082c324955d461e11705ac3c8b531e47d96</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-15T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #2: Kidney Disease</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T19:08:02.054Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/I09UkDRA#QZl7NND_xkSvy6jZj8_-ZQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>009</airingId>
    <content>Underlying health conditions are said to increase the risk for severe COVID-19. People with COPD (chronic obstructive pulmonary disease) mainly caused by smoking need to be especially careful. They are more susceptible to the novel coronavirus and to infection in general. This is due to the impaired function of the "cilia" in the airway that protects us from viruses. It's crucial to quit smoking and avoid becoming infected. Find out the precautions COPD patients should take to protect themselves.</content>
    <description>Underlying health conditions are said to increase the risk for severe COVID-19. Smokers and COPD patients need to be especially careful. Find out what COPD patients need to know about COVID-19.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/K1Nz1QqI#YZ7_h-ufGcNg6qf9IZN6nQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T04:55:27.822Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T04:44:20.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>f27b4db4e4f7ed87795abd948c3da5ffa7e9b688289f12d6cf6ad8eab3645884</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #3: COPD</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T06:51:17.777Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TYlCkB5B#MhPOw9QqLRZa3uqwN5ht4Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>010</airingId>
    <content>Underlying health conditions are said to increase the risk for severe COVID-19. Diabetes patients have more than twice the mortality rate and risk of severe illness from COVID-19 compared to non-diabetics. Studies also found that severe symptoms can be seen not only in the lungs but other organs such as the heart and kidneys. Keeping the blood sugar level normal is key to protecting yourself from the virus. Find out specific ways to control your blood sugar level and tips to reduce the risk.</content>
    <description>People with underlying conditions are said to have a higher risk for severe COVID-19. Diabetics have twice the risk of mortality and serious illness from COVID-19. Find out tips to reduce the risk.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-29T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qs9DUISJ#VnRUF-CaH8U-EzT3yWcGYg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-29T04:55:29.202Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-29T04:44:20.031Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>69e8e114d0f37245b42e0a1ca407c639560aedb326f231a2bd367919288fba93</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-29T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Reducing Your Risk of Serious Illness #4: Diabetes</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T05:23:02.857Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SgtlXKgI#NLRzzfsGOnlNLSjfc9mTfw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>012</airingId>
    <content>Vision is one of the most important of our senses and plays a critical role in our daily lives. Nonetheless, the WHO has estimated that more than 2 billion people around the world have a vision impairment or blindness. Some types of eye diseases can greatly impact our lives and early detection is key. Find out the warning signs and symptoms of common eye problems.</content>
    <description>The WHO estimates that there are over 2 billion people worldwide with vision impairment or blindness. Find out the warning signs to watch out for and prevent eye problems with early detection.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-26T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8AQTEAYb#BM4HP0-37lI_uK3Sa8J6LQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-26T04:55:26.017Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-26T04:44:22.575Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>71d3efbe93f073bd80caa8a2456a124519f0151aaadd29bfbe978f526ffbbe1d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-26T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #1: Check Your Symptoms</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-26T05:24:47.548Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/azZFyKLa#acqUiI-ylKsBraawfhI0wQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>013</airingId>
    <content>The prevalence of myopia, or nearsightedness, is rapidly increasing worldwide and particularly in East Asia. The WHO estimates 1.3 billion people with myopia in 2000, 2.5 billion in 2020, and 5 billion people by the year 2050. Do you consider nearsightedness as a simple problem that can be corrected with prescription glasses or contact lenses? Recent studies have shown that myopia increases the risk of blindness. Find out the hidden risks of myopia and what we can do about it.</content>
    <description>Myopia, or nearsightedness is a growing global problem. The WHO estimated 1.3 billion people with myopia in 2000 and 5 billion by 2050. Find out the risks of myopia and what we can do about it.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-02T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xJ9ykaTC#mEfOvA3O-CEqTbKZjnGzwA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-02T04:55:29.294Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-02T04:44:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>3a1075734b1a68a609e1aae7f560a00a54edb34fe0b325c9ef8a08d085de32d5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-02T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #2: Myopia</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-02T05:24:37.382Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tNk0VIqC#YvLuJWkESkSBtz23pkZQ7g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>What are cataracts? People with cataracts experience blurry or cloudy vision, glare and even double vision. In Japan, 60-80% of those in their 60's, 90% of those in their 70's and 100% of those over 80 years old are reported to have developed some degree of cataracts. This tendency is the same anywhere in the world regardless of race. The cause is found in the natural lens of the eye. Find out the mechanisms of cataracts and its latest treatment options.</content>
    <description>Cataracts develop as we get older, causing blurry or cloudy vision, glare and even double vision. What happens in the lens? Find out the mechanisms of cataracts and its latest treatment options.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-09T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xApQkLrb#wnYHPdrD_i-vfgg7qRavDA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-09T04:55:30.957Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-09T04:44:20.013Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>880506b9ccb234dc086a14ccc2c3e1352081f12c24a1f22c9b65dc25bf8b1bb6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-09T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #3: Cataracts</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-09T05:18:07.321Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MaYUzLSZ#uSRb3d8xQ4wcXSQI6uVEGw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>Have you experienced problems with your eyesight? Do objects appear distorted? Is there a blind spot in the center of your field of view? They may be signs of a retinal disease called "age-related macular degeneration" or AMD. AMD is the leading cause of blindness in the US and in Europe. In Japan, it is the 4th leading cause, but the number of cases is rising. What is AMD? Find out about the different types of AMD and how to perform a self-test for this eye disease.</content>
    <description>Have you ever heard of "age-related macular degeneration" or AMD? It's the leading cause of blindness in the US and in Europe. Learn about the different types of AMD and how to perform a self-test.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-16T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LxZUADLD#2MwikehLTc8PFsLWPPhFbw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-16T04:55:23.960Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-16T04:44:22.431Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>fe9d81bc3aaddea15606f3466858a1b8aa647a5127985891457dd3c711f40b95</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-16T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #4: Age-related Macular Degeneration</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-16T05:41:49.019Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/59VE3T6R#gvixixrAxwW6agJhBH69Yg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>016</airingId>
    <content>The retina is a layer of tissue in the back of our eyes. It acts as a screen where images are projected. We need a healthy retina to see things clearly. However, diabetes can slowly damage the retina. According to the WHO, among the 420 million people with diabetes worldwide, 1 in 3 people have diabetic retinopathy, a retinal disease caused by diabetes. People with good vision can experience sudden vision loss. Find out how to protect yourself from this silent killer of eyesight.</content>
    <description>The retina plays an essential part of our vision. However, "diabetic retinopathy" can slowly damage the retina and even cause sudden vision loss. Find out what you can do to protect your eyes.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-24T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/X58GnKTL#AzK3XGI7nz8wAovdN_V_6A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-24T04:55:26.301Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-24T04:44:20.029Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>84ac7397bb4b1f54ceb499ce0367a36962184fcec9fa97a45dc3f95c94147b1f</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-24T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #5: Diabetic Retinopathy</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T19:25:12.681Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FB5glbaR#rmMFQWBdUS3rIOR8DQ0Ihg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>017</airingId>
    <content>Glaucoma is the leading cause of blindness in many countries. An estimated 7.6 billion people are living with glaucoma worldwide. In Japan, it is the leading cause of visual impairment including blindness. 1 in 20 people over the age of 40 is reported to have glaucoma, but it's hard to detect. It is thought that 90% of people living with glaucoma are unaware of it. Why is the disease hard to notice? Find out how to detect glaucoma early in order to protect your vision.</content>
    <description>Glaucoma affects 7.6 billion people worldwide. In Japan, glaucoma is the leading cause of visual impairment, but it is hard to spot. Find out how to detect glaucoma early to protect your vision.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-01T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vh0SXaqZ#8c3forVwzAaP7JyKqixWjg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-01T04:55:30.590Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-01T04:44:20.017Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>94d9c56cb3c306ea3c5cacdd1a67c1a9631fde3a2770212a75e04822a3bf2bf2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-01T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eye Diseases #6: Glaucoma</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T10:55:26.091Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/9REglZjL#P2eM2mzdXx1sw0c23D5Cig</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>The COVID-19 pandemic has taken a heavy toll on our minds. According to a survey by the CDC in the US, 40% of adults show symptoms of conditions such as anxiety disorder and depression. In Japan, experts are concerned about the growing number of people suffering from various mental disorders. We'll introduce a method of visualizing internal mental status that involves writing out your worries. Also, find out how to relieve stress effectively using stretching techniques and evidence-based mindfulness exercise. Learn helpful mental health tips from an expert to prepare for the stressful long-term fight against the COVID-19 pandemic.</content>
    <description>The COVID-19 pandemic drastically changed our lifestyle. Studies show that anxiety is taking a heavy toll on our mind and body. Find out self-management and relaxation tips to keep your mind healthy.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-05T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5ZQFDYqT#-1xT43SjlaLsKV6R6nEeLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-05T04:55:31.518Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-05T04:44:20.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2086</seriesId>
    <sha256>2994d74a54f932a86c4ef9ca1169ea559938efa972f433736cdfea24d70a5c4d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-05T04:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: Mental Health Tips</subtitle>
    <title>Doctor's Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T12:58:21.674Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/w0lnhSiB#tzmqRue8kM26Nu_-wINlDQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>