<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T16:15:03.361Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>3ff887cb76b1a490</seriesId>
  <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>075</airingId>
    <content>Chizu Express is a third sector local railway, which runs 56.1km through the Chugoku Mountains between Tottori and Hyogo Prefectures. From the beginning, the railway was constructed for high-speed operation. While many third sector railway companies are struggling to make a profit, Chizu Express has been in the black for 21 consecutive years. See how the company is able to run through the mountains at 130km/h with their pendulum type express trains, as well as the company's strategies to increase ridership on their local trains. In "Trains in Focus," hop on JR West's "Ametsuchi" tourist train that runs between Tottori and Izumoshi Stations.</content>
    <description>Chizu Express, which runs through the Chugoku Mountains, has recorded a profit for 21 consecutive years. See how the company has managed to stay on top and what they are doing to ensure their future.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8gUCARZI#pioTjoy0DIVGKbEUdVD49w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T16:00:31.578Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T15:29:20.070Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>6b525fa50fde336e34a9412fafb1d170f0445c38d6af933e1a2b9e384392fd9e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Chizu Express: A Top Tier Third Sector Railway</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:43:07.088Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0Z011ITK#br4UeB4YzPusfVHWkcRaOw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>076</airingId>
    <content>Hitachinaka Seaside Railway in Ibaraki Prefecture opened in 2008. When it began operation, the 14.3km railway had a ridership of less than 700,000. Now, ridership exceeds 1 million annually. Making a profit in 2017, the company now plans to extend the line by 3.1km. See how the company is working with locals to increase ridership even further, and how the company's president is putting passengers first.</content>
    <description>Since it opened, Hitachinaka Seaside Railway in Ibaraki Prefecture has seen an increase in ridership. See how this passenger focused railway is working with locals to increase ridership even further.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ShMggTBa#9QrTUuMADosXY0_AsmUYzw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T22:00:29.764Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T21:29:20.079Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>24f15d97e2e3558bfef9a380ad6778e0e663395d15f7923ae7ca35e1f98bf702</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T21:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hitachinaka Seaside Railway: Pulling Together with the Local Community</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T18:46:05.431Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MlMRhKyA#w_53egBDrGCF04ubglNWsg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>JR West is developing new services in response to lifestyle changes brought about by the coronavirus pandemic. One service involves the idea of a "workcation." JR West is now experimenting with packages that enable people to travel, stay and work in rural areas away from their homes in the city. To improve tourism, JR West has introduced a new tourist train called "etSETOra." The high-speed cruiser "SEA SPICA" and the "TWILIGHT EXPRESS MIZUKAZE" will also resume operation. Join us as we discuss the future of the railway post-pandemic with JR West's president, Mr. Hasegawa Kazuaki.</content>
    <description>JR West is developing new services in response to lifestyle changes brought about by the coronavirus. We talk to the president of JR West about the future of the railway post-pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/J08xQIjA#XtXj7OjLaNeVRt_LhmW28w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T16:00:22.589Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T15:29:23.045Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>d8ba107c8e561d5af8ffbf54ea3b95cca808649004289cf311d97807332d70f4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>JR West: Redefining the Role of the Railway Post Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:25:33.297Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>095</airingId>
    <content>Many new express, commuter and tourist trains, as well as a sleeper train, began service in 2020. See the latest express trains, including the Tokaido Shinkansen "N700S," Kintetsu Railway's "HINOTORI" and JR East's luxurious "SAPHIR ODORIKO." Also, see the tourist train "etSETOra," which operates in the Setouchi region, and JR Kyushu's richly designed "36 Plus 3." In addition, see the "WEST EXPRESS GINGA," the first new sleeper train to be introduced in 21 years. Join us as we take a look back at Japan's latest trains and trends.</content>
    <description>In 2020, many new express, commuter, and tourist trains, as well as a sleeper train, made their debut in 2020. Join us as we review Japan's latest trains and trends.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/a9clza7A#y0cXQdxLXVdsnla-g5Tscg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T16:00:30.470Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T15:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>3707e297f3e93acda410a30478617031c6ffc6220ecc8bf7b38bfef6b39b0ae2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Reviewing the New Trains of 2020</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:12:05.234Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>