<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-12T05:05:03.506Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>3ff887cb76b1a490</seriesId>
  <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>074</airingId>
    <content>South Hokkaido Railway is home to a popular tourist train. A third sector company, South Hokkaido Railway began operation in 2016 with the opening of the Hokkaido Shinkansen. With limited resources, the railway asked a major tour company to help develop and operate a tourist train. See how the company worked with the community, and used their know-how to turn a "regular" train into a fun tourist train that has been gaining attention across Japan.</content>
    <description>South Hokkaido Railway is home to a tourist train that has been gaining attention across Japan. See how a tour company used their know-how to develop this popular and entertaining tourist train.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QRZiXbLJ#I1zSmWXXTtp0mD_YujH8wg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T16:00:20.544Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-19T15:29:23.037Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>a0046fd40291fe8a0e3e74888c1cc6197c5a51ddbbaec60ec36f955f6288e261</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-19T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>South Hokkaido Railway: A Tourist Train Developed by a Tour Company</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:39:59.058Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FEoQBCxY#y-epQMo1_jGf11ltnqwYpA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>075</airingId>
    <content>Chizu Express is a third sector local railway, which runs 56.1km through the Chugoku Mountains between Tottori and Hyogo Prefectures. From the beginning, the railway was constructed for high-speed operation. While many third sector railway companies are struggling to make a profit, Chizu Express has been in the black for 21 consecutive years. See how the company is able to run through the mountains at 130km/h with their pendulum type express trains, as well as the company's strategies to increase ridership on their local trains. In "Trains in Focus," hop on JR West's "Ametsuchi" tourist train that runs between Tottori and Izumoshi Stations.</content>
    <description>Chizu Express, which runs through the Chugoku Mountains, has recorded a profit for 21 consecutive years. See how the company has managed to stay on top and what they are doing to ensure their future.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8gUCARZI#pioTjoy0DIVGKbEUdVD49w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T16:00:31.578Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T15:29:20.070Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>6b525fa50fde336e34a9412fafb1d170f0445c38d6af933e1a2b9e384392fd9e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Chizu Express: A Top Tier Third Sector Railway</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:43:07.088Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0Z011ITK#br4UeB4YzPusfVHWkcRaOw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>076</airingId>
    <content>Hitachinaka Seaside Railway in Ibaraki Prefecture opened in 2008. When it began operation, the 14.3km railway had a ridership of less than 700,000. Now, ridership exceeds 1 million annually. Making a profit in 2017, the company now plans to extend the line by 3.1km. See how the company is working with locals to increase ridership even further, and how the company's president is putting passengers first.</content>
    <description>Since it opened, Hitachinaka Seaside Railway in Ibaraki Prefecture has seen an increase in ridership. See how this passenger focused railway is working with locals to increase ridership even further.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ShMggTBa#9QrTUuMADosXY0_AsmUYzw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T22:00:29.764Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T21:29:20.079Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>24f15d97e2e3558bfef9a380ad6778e0e663395d15f7923ae7ca35e1f98bf702</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T21:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hitachinaka Seaside Railway: Pulling Together with the Local Community</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T18:46:05.431Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MlMRhKyA#w_53egBDrGCF04ubglNWsg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>077</airingId>
    <content>"Ekinaka" refers to the shops and facilities that are usually found inside the station. Now JR East is expanding on that concept, developing the viaducts beneath the Chuo Line in a project they are calling the "Chuo Line Mall." Utilizing the 70,000 square meters of open space beneath the railway, 5 stations are working to develop new shops and facilities that will greatly benefit the community. See how JR East's "Ekinaka" development strategy is bringing the towns and stations closer together.</content>
    <description>5 Chuo Line stations are currently developing the viaducts beneath the railway, bringing the towns and stations together with new shops and facilities. See JR East's "Ekinaka" development strategy.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1oU3hCrb#w5kyF-aFN5_26EZVcIJyqw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T16:00:34.061Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T15:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>145c3b0325310c039fb50b2b269a37f42d280652850ac66188b3d74fcb10449d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>JR's Ekinaka Development Project: A New Lifestyle Below the Chuo Line</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T17:22:33.244Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4kcHwarZ#LhqoCmT9Jjq0xpORultp6Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>078</airingId>
    <content>JR Central's long-awaited next-generation Shinkansen; the N700S is scheduled to begin operation in summer 2020. The new N700S makes use of state-of-the-art technology to enhance safety, convenience, and comfort. Changes include the addition of lithium-ion batteries, used to power an emergency self-propulsion system, and a fully active vibration control system, installed to improve the comfort of the ride. Join us as we look at how the Shinkansen has evolved over the years and get a sneak peek of this supreme new train.</content>
    <description>JR Central's next-generation Shinkansen; the N700S is scheduled to start operation in summer 2020. Get a sneak peek of the new technologies employed to enhance safety, convenience, and comfort.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-07T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/94lnkQ5J#E47BzKT01farSOq4OWzwgQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-07T22:00:28.844Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-07T21:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>3abdecdfda6f6f6a3b7f015c7821d5baf0cc607d250f831d98c7bb03117db063</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-07T21:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Introducing the N700S: JR Central's Next-Generation Shinkansen</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-08T05:56:17.307Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/M40njS7S#X4U60XmUIadSroOfhJu7aQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>JR West is developing new services in response to lifestyle changes brought about by the coronavirus pandemic. One service involves the idea of a "workcation." JR West is now experimenting with packages that enable people to travel, stay and work in rural areas away from their homes in the city. To improve tourism, JR West has introduced a new tourist train called "etSETOra." The high-speed cruiser "SEA SPICA" and the "TWILIGHT EXPRESS MIZUKAZE" will also resume operation. Join us as we discuss the future of the railway post-pandemic with JR West's president, Mr. Hasegawa Kazuaki.</content>
    <description>JR West is developing new services in response to lifestyle changes brought about by the coronavirus. We talk to the president of JR West about the future of the railway post-pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/J08xQIjA#XtXj7OjLaNeVRt_LhmW28w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T16:00:22.589Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T15:29:23.045Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>d8ba107c8e561d5af8ffbf54ea3b95cca808649004289cf311d97807332d70f4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>JR West: Redefining the Role of the Railway Post Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:25:33.297Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Pk0RBKAD#wJHo2q6kMNKrxHLv2kIjuA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>094</airingId>
    <content>The 67.7km Tenryu Hamanako Railroad in Shizuoka Prefecture is a third sector railway that connects 5 cities and 1 town. The railway is famous for its railway heritage, remnants of which can be found along the line, such as a turntable and roundhouse, old station buildings and bridges, 36 of which are registered tangible cultural property of Japan. This year marks the railway's 80th anniversary, but the coronavirus pandemic has seen ridership decline. See how Tenryu Hamanako Railroad is working with the local community to revitalize the area and make a comeback.</content>
    <description>Tenryu Hamanako Railroad is famous for its turntable and old station buildings, but the pandemic has seen ridership decline. See how the railway is making a comeback with the local community.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tcp32CST#ZSU6SIOyE21kMHL1MuY_bw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T16:00:20.832Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T15:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>b68193205c2955534dd81636d005080e6dbe97366c1cd5e1344a9a0b92117f56</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tenryu Hamanako Railroad: Working with the Community to Revitalize the Railway</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T18:01:16.085Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/dY8nzCaD#001ODnbgmFTdp4NHtyV56Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>095</airingId>
    <content>Many new express, commuter and tourist trains, as well as a sleeper train, began service in 2020. See the latest express trains, including the Tokaido Shinkansen "N700S," Kintetsu Railway's "HINOTORI" and JR East's luxurious "SAPHIR ODORIKO." Also, see the tourist train "etSETOra," which operates in the Setouchi region, and JR Kyushu's richly designed "36 Plus 3." In addition, see the "WEST EXPRESS GINGA," the first new sleeper train to be introduced in 21 years. Join us as we take a look back at Japan's latest trains and trends.</content>
    <description>In 2020, many new express, commuter, and tourist trains, as well as a sleeper train, made their debut in 2020. Join us as we review Japan's latest trains and trends.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/w4cTyajC#AR0OcZzrJ5Rdn4mtZW2QSg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T16:00:30.470Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T15:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2049</seriesId>
    <sha256>19bf433957a53b5fa4e786f446459f8a41931babf164baf84489c7788f14073a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Reviewing the New Trains of 2020</subtitle>
    <title>Japan Railway Journal</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T02:53:18.845Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/hQclBCxQ#uZPrgfR0564_1xrNu35iBg</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>