<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-04T09:10:03.494Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>4365cf84c14911e8</seriesId>
  <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>085</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
An online bus tour started by a small bus tour company in western Japan is growing in popularity. Participants are sent food and drinks from the tour destination in advance and are able to enjoy them while listening to the tour conductor from the comfort of their homes. Another advantage these online tours offer clients is the lack of travel time between destinations. Realizing that these virtual tours can allow clients to participate from anywhere in the world, the tour company has also created tours for clients in the United States in an effort to expand on what was once a completely domestic client base. This episode focuses on how the pandemic has forced a local tour company to shift its business model in order to survive.
[In Depth: China Gives Agriculture Tech Boost]
China is gearing up to digitalize its agricultural industry to make farming more profitable. It is hoping that the shift will help close the income gap between urban and rural households. We see how these efforts are helping farmers.
[Global Trends: Pandemic Turns Chinese Thrifty]
In China, being seen as a cheapskate can bring shame. But that has been changing during the economic uncertainty of the coronavirus era. A website showing people how to save money is a hit with younger people. Some of them did not have savings when the virus appeared. We take a look at changes in consumer awareness among young Chinese, and how their new thrifty habits will affect the future of consumption in China, and the global economy.</content>
    <description>This episode examines how a small bus company that saw its core business threatened by the pandemic was able to adapt and survive by taking its popular guided tours online.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-17T20:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1Is2kTCa#J-_Emtn2t6ywAMq6xdJvAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-17T20:30:24.987Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-17T19:59:20.366Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>09ba00a38dc4b41e0fc74c773fd92a3f626633dbf3b85af2dde872832118318f</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-17T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Pandemic Pushes Bus Tours Online</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T08:17:28.000Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/DItBkaIZ#NsKIZUAHDk8nqimVHeZ93Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>086</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
Strong, portable and weather resistant, shipping containers are becoming a popular choice in modern architecture. Recently, a company that operates 20 shipping container hotels in Japan's Kanto region has made many of its units available for use as portable "rescue hotels" that can be deployed almost anywhere in the country for use by rescue workers, medical staff, or for other relief services. An industrial equipment dealer also was similar potential in shipping containers and is now equipping them with solar-powered generators and high capacity batteries to create emergency response stations that can instantly provide local areas with a much needed boost to infrastructure during times of trouble. In this episode, we focus on how shipping containers can be used to bolster the Japan's emergency response capabilities.
[In Depth: Japan Economy on Uncertain Path After GDP Bounce]
Japan's economy had a record surge in the July to September quarter after taking a deep dive in the previous 3 months. Much of the bounce came from reopening parts of the economy that had been shut to stem the spread of the coronavirus. Now, a resurgence of cases is threatening a sustained recovery.
[Global Trends: Indian Hotel on Wheels Offer Safe Journey]
Tourism in India has been decimated by COVID-19, as foreign visitor numbers have plummeted and sites like the Taj Mahal have seen temporary closures to stem the spread of the virus. A hotel outside New Delhi is trying to make up for some of its lost business by offering guests something different -- a luxury suite on a bus that can take them anywhere without exposing them to anyone outside their social bubble. We catch a ride on the bus to see what the five-star hotel service looks like on wheels.</content>
    <description>From earthquakes to typhoons, Japan is prone to a variety of natural disasters. This episode shows how shipping containers are being used to bolster the country's emergency response capabilities.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/V49wgbqb#ZNlWyeQBSpWbAij5A5sSlA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T14:40:27.876Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T14:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>fd77ac8d50fd3093133d46aaa85e5d3c2c617cedb0cb795ea2d9628d6dc4b9b1</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shipping Containers to the Rescue</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T08:11:06.092Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YAxUGahQ#Q6Og1v9CY-Tu7Zb32piIkA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>087</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
This week's episode gives you an inside look at 2 companies that are combining modern technology with personal experience in order to create custom-made products for their disabled clients. One company, with a large number of disabled staff, is creating custom-built vehicles for people with disabilities. From design to fabrication, the company's staff incorporate their own experiences into the creation process as they seek to provide their clients with the best solutions possible. A small start-up is also using a similar approach to create "powered prosthetics." These new prosthetics use sensors and motors to assist users with movement. The CEO and lead developer, an amputee himself, has spent the last 5 years developing a powered prosthetic leg and is aiming to have it ready for market in 2021.
[In Depth: China's Export Law Has Trade Partners Guessing]
The trade standoff between the U.S. and China just got worse after Beijing rolled out new restrictions on exports. That puts global businesses at the risk of once again being caught between the world's 2 biggest economies.
[Global Trends: Tourists in Asia Still Get Their Japan Fix]
The popularity of Japan as a tourist destination had been growing steadily in the past decade. But travel restrictions earlier this year reduced the flood of foreign visitors to a trickle. With people unable to make the journey by plane, some businesses in Southeast Asia are offering them a chance to experience Japan closer to home. We visit an inn in Bangkok that has all the touches of an authentic Japanese ryokan, and see plans for a hotel in Vietnam that is modeled after large-scale resorts in Japan.</content>
    <description>This episode features Japanese companies that are combining modern technology with first-hand experience in order to create products that can meet the specific needs of their disabled clients.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FB5CjbZR#FxzSv8rek0qRi4LzMtso1A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T14:40:29.086Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T14:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>4cfa0b721bd7b52ce8d564b278efe7604dac46d433d79a29ea526bd80366144b</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Designing for Disabilities</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T08:17:25.549Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/y48F0ABI#2fsfVovlaP1N8aWmnk4AXQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>088</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
As e-commerce sweeps the globe, retail stores and other businesses are looking to technology to help them compete in the digital age. A supermarket in Tokyo's neighboring Chiba Prefecture has introduced smart shopping carts that allow shoppers to ring up items as they shop. This system not only increases efficiency by letting shoppers avoid checkout lines, a built-in AI system analyzes their shopping behavior and makes suggestions to improve their shopping experience. Retail isn't the only field where technology is changing how business is done. A Tokyo-based IT venture has come up with a fun and unique way to carry out meetings for sales, marketing and customer service-based businesses -- by using a digital avatar. The system also uses AI to analyze client responses in order to improve overall customer service.
[In Depth: Long Road to Green and Self-Driving Cars]
The landscape of the auto industry is rapidly changing with the advance of technologies and tougher regulations on gas emission. Japan's conventional automakers are facing major challenges as they change gears.
[Global Trends: Food Delivery Services See Evolution in Bangkok]
Restaurants are ramping up delivery services as they see their on-site business plummet due to COVID-19 restrictions. We see how companies in Bangkok are coming up with ways to help restaurants reduce delivery costs and get meals to customers efficiently.</content>
    <description>From smart shopping carts to digital avatars, this episode looks at how retail stores and other businesses are implementing new technologies to help them remain competitive in the age of e-commerce.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-12T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LhkQDI5b#-PXAaDN-NOPl5DfHWaO5_g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-12T14:40:23.378Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-12T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>83b6eafa650f1c6d585472ff4dcdcbcc87b0954126f99deb8d057e54ebc007fd</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-12T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tech Transforms In-Store Shopping</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:33:45.165Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1x9GDCqL#I9YHsDFOmwTioMQ1vgzD7A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>089</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
This episode examines how technology could fill the gap as Japan's food industry struggles to deal with the country's labor shortage. A Tokyo-based robot maker has developed a "humanoid" helper robot that is capable of working alongside humans. It implements advanced image analysis and AI as it helps pack elaborate boxed lunches. A Japanese confectionery is using a special oven equipped with AI to bake Baumkuchen. The system automatically adjusts oven temperature and is able to decide when to apply a new layer of batter to the rotating cake - both tasks that normally must be done under the watchful eye of an experienced baker.
[In Depth: IPO Market Sizzles as Pandemic Deepens]
The pandemic has been devastating for the global economy, but you wouldn't know it by checking the stock market. Share prices are soaring, leading to an IPO gold rush.
[Global Trends: Sustainable Success in Sweden]
A growing number of companies in Sweden are finding success in sustainability. We take a look at how some are using upcycling and new technology to make the country a leader in the transition to green economic development.</content>
    <description>Featuring a bento-packing robot and an AI-equipped oven, this episode examines how technology could fill the gap as Japan's food industry struggles to deal with the country's labor shortage.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zJ1QyYZT#P7ftXe2DkmUv75urfuZbAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T14:41:12.463Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T14:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>275dcd3483d15d8c249970c5cff1626239c3f0b62f3695be638bffafd606654a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Robots Support Cooks and Bakers</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:31:26.489Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/718AyaSb#ymDDQ35jr4NzQEqhPm-f5w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>090</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
The Japanese government has recently pledged to become carbon neutral by 2050. Experts say that hydrogen will be one of the keys to achieving this goal. This episode features a company in northern Japan that is using cow manure to produce hydrogen, and a local government project that is providing local businesses with electricity that was generated using hydrogen produced from plastic waste.
[In Depth: Companies Pitch for Future at Virtual CES]
CES, the world's largest tech trade show, moved completely online due to the coronavirus. The breathtaking innovations unveiled at the event indicate that companies are thinking about how we live and work during the pandemic.
[Global Trends: A Walk in the Digital Forest]
Japan is leading in the new field of health care known as "forest therapy." Specially-trained guides show stressed-out people how to best absorb nature. For those who cannot make it to the forest, a digital version is available in the form of an immersive theater experience.</content>
    <description>This episode features a company that is turning livestock waste into hydrogen and a local government's plan to produce electricity using hydrogen made from plastic waste.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-16T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HtkUUTZT#hxDXcfLgrgdvKMyU7zfxwg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-16T14:40:28.707Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-16T14:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>3806a302956dc534afa2afa81b212ddbe96098926e43cba6fd1196f1b929519a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-16T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Japan Looks to Hydrogen Energy</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-16T22:18:42.663Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jk81UaTB#W41Ujy0IvSKTwNv9Q7nXPQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>091</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
The implementation of education technology, or "EdTech," is advancing rapidly around the world. In Japan, many EdTech companies are focusing on using technology to not only stimulate the minds of students, but to meet the changing needs of teachers. This episode features an Osaka-based company that has created easy-to-follow lesson plans for teaching robotics and a Tokyo startup that has drawn global attention for its intelligence-increasing smartphone apps.
[In Depth: Biden Takes the Reins of US Economy]
It's a new dawn for America as Joe Biden becomes the 46th President of the United States. He takes office pledging to restore the country's battered economy. We look at his plans and their global impact.
[Global Trends: Eco-Friendly Sugar Harvest Brings Sweet Success]
A growing environmental awareness in Thailand is bringing change to the country's sugar industry. Producers are turning away from the polluting ways of the past and finding new business opportunities.</content>
    <description>This episode focuses on education technology in Japan and features a company offering easy-to-follow robotics lessons and an IT startup that is creating intelligence-increasing smartphone apps.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-23T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ryY02ByR#IZ3JeYCXfoFRaeSHg5SrLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-23T14:40:43.617Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-23T14:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>9da74ce2817cd19ad475ecdf0ec9faebdd7d766829069e08f3c8c3b46eeb5e53</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-23T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>EdTech in Japan</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-23T15:36:53.809Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Oy5wgTbT#wNbwmvve-9Z8Le4HdGLzEg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>092</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
Jackets, sweaters and other products made from synthetic fibers inspired by spider silk are attracting attention for their comfort, durability and environmental friendliness. The fibers are made of synthesized proteins created by genetically modified microorganisms. This episode takes a look at the exciting potential these synthetic fibers are bringing to the fashion world and beyond.</content>
    <description>This episode features durable and environmentally friendly synthetic fibers inspired by spider silk that could revolutionize the fashion and apparel industry.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-06T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/x9dUwLxC#AIY60NefR5gYUMlcLmH26A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-06T14:40:32.609Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-06T14:09:20.122Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>3c70fd097f164592b7ebeaa896e4422866c2bd0abbc93eec89cdce19598d2ed3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-06T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Chemistry on the Catwalk</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T22:50:34.338Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/f1VU3JRS#_ETowZt8KA37Sftf9DzGuA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
Wearable devices are now expanding into safety and healthcare applications. A Kyoto-based company has created undershirts that can measure and display core body temperature, pulse and other biometric data. Construction businesses are using them to help prevent heat exhaustion and other health risks by monitoring their workers' biometric data and as Japan's elderly population increases, some local governments are using the technology to keep an eye on the health of senior citizens.
[In Depth: Tesla's Bet Boost for Bitcoin]
The world's richest person Elon Musk has taken a step to endorse bitcoin. Cryptocurrencies have faced years of skepticism, but we look into how they are gaining acceptance as a mainstream method of payment.
[Global Trends: Hydrogen Race Car Set to Take Lead]
The organizers of 24 Hours of Le Mans will open the race to fuel-cell cars in 2024, and are even developing a hydrogen-powered racing car. We look at how the project is pushing forward fuel-cell technology.</content>
    <description>A unique type of wearable device that can monitor various types of biometric data is now being used to protect workers from heat stroke and to keep watch over the elderly.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-13T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xEYB2YhB#L0jrES4MrxAClBeTrJb49Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-13T14:40:33.722Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-13T14:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>1d36d408b484b40d023f4a8ef30bd064d13cc8544859c126381ba3ea98f01d2a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-13T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Wearables Tackle Health and Safety</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T09:15:49.209Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/810k2ADJ#l_VnFpsb5i6TVDvo1kUaDg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>094</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
According to a government survey, nearly 1.27 million small and medium-sized enterprises in Japan will be in danger of going out of business by 2025. Although the number of companies being forced to close during the pandemic is increasing, the number of prospective buyers is also on the rise. This episode looks at how Tranbi, an online matching service that helps facilitate mergers and acquisitions, is saving many small and medium-sized Japanese companies from going out of business.
[In Depth: China Celebrates New Year in New Way]
China celebrated the Lunar New Year this year but without the usual swarms of travelers. Concerns about a coronavirus resurgence have put a new spin on age-old traditions. We take a look at how people and businesses adapted.
[Global Trends: Entrepreneurs Rise from Bali Tourism Struggles]
The tourism industry on the Indonesian resort island of Bali has been hit hard by coronavirus restrictions. With foreign visitors out of the picture, many locals are charting a new course by starting their own businesses.</content>
    <description>This episode looks at how an online matching service that helps facilitate mergers and acquisitions is saving many small and medium sized Japanese companies from going out of business.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-20T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5eQESb5C#am64HWOe6Wu0oj2AEuLikQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-20T14:40:32.151Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-20T14:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>d971f16126a162885c55c21ef4190a36a6c449327b3b66f782d4f52884979743</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-20T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>E-Commerce Meets M&amp;A</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-20T15:44:41.505Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IeACVTwb#PfpBB5tfYMEVXbpPdnaRDw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>704</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. As the pandemic approaches the one-year mark, the way many people live and work has changed drastically. In Japan, a new type of share house system has been introduced that allows customers to rotate between several locations all over the country. The company's business model is also attracting attention as one way to make use of the increasing amount of vacant housing in Japan's rural areas.</content>
    <description>This special edition features a business that converts vacant properties in scenic rural areas across Japan into share houses that tenants can rotate between.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vZNm0LpT#1uxyCIuUIpn_J-V6daLIGw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T02:24:00.902Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-21T02:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>951e8af278ba329d3a4f23bcde8de5a023bbe6b1611f79ec7c32eb975dddbc5e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-21T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Getting a New Lease on Life During the Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T06:28:32.933Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/981ARKiL#IM4kPRqQiabwvUVO1j4nSQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>705</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. Businesses that help customers to stay socially distanced are catching on as people seek ways to venture out while still following safety guidelines. This episode features a shopping complex with AI-driven digital floor maps that show customers how crowded shops and restaurants are in real-time and a restaurant management company that is using outdoor spaces to provide customers with safer ways to dine out.</content>
    <description>From AI-driven digital floor maps to open-air restaurants, this special edition of Biz Stream features businesses that are helping customers to remain socially-distanced while eating out.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xgtyWZ4b#DqtNxQr0xqlogMxrv8hMvA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T02:23:31.296Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T02:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>6dfebde5ca414e9fcc73e1fe6251769b113668a216d5ecdca4708dffa7e66420</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Distancing-Based Businesses Providing Peace of Mind</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T04:31:35.400Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/69s0EDwR#3QY81TP8kuB414c051I7iA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>706</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. Off the coast of Tohoku, hungry sea urchins are wiping out kelp forests. A young entrepreneur has come up with a way to stop them that could provide additional economic benefits to the region by collecting, feeding, and selling the prickly pests. In other parts of Japan, a major steel producer is using one of its byproducts, steel slag, to assist in the regrowth of marine plant life. This episode highlights the efforts of companies that are working to counter the effects of seafloor desertification along Japan's coastlines.</content>
    <description>This special edition of Biz Stream highlights the efforts of companies that are working to counter the effects of seafloor desertification and bring back marine plant life to Japan's coastal waters.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/x5MDRKZL#dwpYCybjMz-U6zfUNn33Kg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T02:23:28.542Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T02:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>d33b5415f16dda391760acf1ab6df9da0a4c142a224aaffd5b7a4f99a82299c4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Saving the Seas with Sustainability</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:41:23.873Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Xtt2yDRS#61YXqA8l9D7miXuaCSiKJw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>707</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. As the battle continues against COVID-19, advances in antimicrobial and disinfectant treatments are receiving more attention than ever. This episode highlights efforts to fight against microscopic threats by featuring a special antimicrobial coating that was inspired by ancient treatment techniques for protecting and preserving Japanese artifacts and artwork as well as the first safe-for-human UV light that effectively inactivates COVID-19.</content>
    <description>This special edition of Biz Stream features an antimicrobial coating inspired by ancient Japanese techniques for protecting artwork as well as a COVID-19 inactivating UV light that is safe for humans.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tBgCHQpb#ct9-TkrAZFUfFyc-AhikOA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T02:23:30.467Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T02:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>332601c68a1360d2b79457c975ddf6e1fb22ff2e11cc92165c3ff7983af7cf14</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Japan's Germ-Fighting Tech</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T03:55:41.282Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/8VtgiKzD#H1mmJfz-NmQoLrbZh5YFew</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>708</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. This episode examines how advances in the recycling of bio-waste are playing a key role in creating a more circular society. We feature a Japanese company that has found a way to extract hydroxyapatite (a key ingredient in making toothpaste and cosmetics) from eggshells, and another company that is turning sugar cane and other waste products into biofuel.</content>
    <description>From minerals found in eggshells to cotton extracted from second-hand clothing, this special edition shows how advances in recycling technology will help lead to a more circular society.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-25T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5M5UwCZY#3bOcjaM8oa_inNbcs49TEQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-25T02:23:30.196Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-25T02:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>cc9f8b54f5e384b3615c3cc42ccb920dd047d399f6b5eaa416104a98637acd37</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-25T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Getting More from Biowaste</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM </title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T15:57:46.156Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6l802CDS#2asu-7sNLEODKnlrmlWs6A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>709</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. This episode examines how technology could play a key role in saving Japan's struggling agriculture industry. One company is drawing attention for its AI-driven robots, which are assisting farmers with harvesting produce. Another business is hoping that its online matching service will bring much needed short-term workers from across the country to assist farmers in need of support.</content>
    <description>Japan is facing a major lack of farmers. This special edition explores how an online matching service and specially designed harvesting robots may be the key to saving the agriculture industry.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/NVZSWTYB#ML4lOJC4-Lg21gPjuwpO3w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T02:23:32.396Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-28T02:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>512c11b48d860453314c3ab4c55a6e1b0e0b90c16e249698809aca397e6bf963</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-28T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Solving Farmer Shortage with Technology</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T22:24:43.411Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1lFQRRKT#GzxNBWPpb704NsiK6X5wEA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>710</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. "Clean Water and Sanitation" is one of the 17 sustainable development goals set forth by the United Nations. This episode features 2 Japanese companies that have made it their mission to find ways to conserve on water usage. One company has created a recycling system that makes up to 98% of household water reusable, and the other has developed an automated cultivation system that uses solar heat to grow crops with small amounts of water.</content>
    <description>This special edition of Biz Stream features Japanese companies that are developing new water conserving technologies for both domestic and agricultural use.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-29T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/UkkTXCrB#O-2ZFKs1EGT0_Le3LiyhZw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-29T02:23:33.144Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-29T02:09:20.048Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>56b4dd241a0744a7b14dfa6f01e44f13012987e841508897d70a929431199a2e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-29T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Making Every Drop Count</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T05:45:43.404Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/G0lFiIbK#kVp-j9IlN7gR6brT8DzF-w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>711</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. This episode looks at how unintended results and accidental discoveries during the research and development process can sometimes lead to new applications. We feature cold storage technology that was developed during research on liquid crystal displays and a porous odor adsorbent carbon material which was created while trying to improve lithium-ion battery performance.</content>
    <description>From cold storage technology to odor absorbent material, this special edition of Biz Stream looks at how unintended results during the research and development process can lead to new applications.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-30T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sg9XRC4R#sV7UWN3qT-9rrMAJ5Agf_A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-30T02:23:31.326Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-30T02:09:20.119Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>1539608d47c4f875e9870f38cc8c0a6915ee61eb2fffb5a9907aa1fb89acea4e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-30T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Adventitious Advances in R&amp;D</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-30T04:11:49.387Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/q01zRIQA#ht65uBWWnOD0Kd0DVhv42w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>712</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. This episode focuses on how the pandemic has forced a local bus tour company to take its business online in order to survive. Participants are sent food and drinks from the tour destination in advance and are able to enjoy them while watching and listening to the tour conductor from the comfort of their homes. Realizing that these virtual tours can allow customers to join from anywhere in the world, the tour company has also created tours for foreign clients.</content>
    <description>This special edition of Biz Stream examines how a small bus tour company that saw its core business threatened by the pandemic was able to adapt and survive by taking its popular guided tours online.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RFVWSDwR#wvw2714nMYr4_oXIwrK5-g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T02:23:30.400Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T02:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>9b1455ad21d7a6de3a3e5518744992720df4e62a9e21b99b019374cc2ed536bc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Pandemic Pushes Bus Tours Online</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T11:37:10.101Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WgkQCBaA#un2lnFdxT9XMc760kv7g-w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>713</airingId>
    <content>[BIZ STREAM SPECIAL EDITION]
This series of special editions feature selected stories from BIZ STREAM's signature "On-Site" reports. A hospitality company that operates a chain of shipping container hotels across Japan has made its rooms available to local governments for use as portable "rescue hotels." Elsewhere, a truck repair business is now equipping containers with solar-powered generators to create emergency response units that can instantly provide local areas with a much-needed boost to infrastructure during times of trouble. This episode focuses on how shipping containers can be used as a tool to bolster Japan's emergency response capabilities.</content>
    <description>From earthquakes to typhoons, Japan is prone to a variety of natural disasters. This special edition shows how shipping containers may help bolster the country's emergency response capabilities.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-01T02:23:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/y8903LQR#8lEH3noXVEgNFPNBKAiemw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-01T02:23:33.511Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-01T02:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3004</seriesId>
    <sha256>ffb6714917f621b259ddb1b1b8bcce63487e084ffbd07761f503211954a898b2</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-01T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shipping Containers to the Rescue</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-01T04:24:08.303Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FIsXgAzB#fYrTV4Ozu5AmrWNm3t1i8A</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>