<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-26T08:10:03.255Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>4365cf84c14911e8</seriesId>
  <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>088</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
As e-commerce sweeps the globe, retail stores and other businesses are looking to technology to help them compete in the digital age. A supermarket in Tokyo's neighboring Chiba Prefecture has introduced smart shopping carts that allow shoppers to ring up items as they shop. This system not only increases efficiency by letting shoppers avoid checkout lines, a built-in AI system analyzes their shopping behavior and makes suggestions to improve their shopping experience. Retail isn't the only field where technology is changing how business is done. A Tokyo-based IT venture has come up with a fun and unique way to carry out meetings for sales, marketing and customer service-based businesses -- by using a digital avatar. The system also uses AI to analyze client responses in order to improve overall customer service.
[In Depth: Long Road to Green and Self-Driving Cars]
The landscape of the auto industry is rapidly changing with the advance of technologies and tougher regulations on gas emission. Japan's conventional automakers are facing major challenges as they change gears.
[Global Trends: Food Delivery Services See Evolution in Bangkok]
Restaurants are ramping up delivery services as they see their on-site business plummet due to COVID-19 restrictions. We see how companies in Bangkok are coming up with ways to help restaurants reduce delivery costs and get meals to customers efficiently.</content>
    <description>From smart shopping carts to digital avatars, this episode looks at how retail stores and other businesses are implementing new technologies to help them remain competitive in the age of e-commerce.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-12T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LhkQDI5b#-PXAaDN-NOPl5DfHWaO5_g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-12T14:40:23.378Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-12T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>83b6eafa650f1c6d585472ff4dcdcbcc87b0954126f99deb8d057e54ebc007fd</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-12T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tech Transforms In-Store Shopping</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:33:45.165Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>089</airingId>
    <content>[On-Site Report]
This episode examines how technology could fill the gap as Japan's food industry struggles to deal with the country's labor shortage. A Tokyo-based robot maker has developed a "humanoid" helper robot that is capable of working alongside humans. It implements advanced image analysis and AI as it helps pack elaborate boxed lunches. A Japanese confectionery is using a special oven equipped with AI to bake Baumkuchen. The system automatically adjusts oven temperature and is able to decide when to apply a new layer of batter to the rotating cake - both tasks that normally must be done under the watchful eye of an experienced baker.
[In Depth: IPO Market Sizzles as Pandemic Deepens]
The pandemic has been devastating for the global economy, but you wouldn't know it by checking the stock market. Share prices are soaring, leading to an IPO gold rush.
[Global Trends: Sustainable Success in Sweden]
A growing number of companies in Sweden are finding success in sustainability. We take a look at how some are using upcycling and new technology to make the country a leader in the transition to green economic development.</content>
    <description>Featuring a bento-packing robot and an AI-equipped oven, this episode examines how technology could fill the gap as Japan's food industry struggles to deal with the country's labor shortage.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zJ1QyYZT#P7ftXe2DkmUv75urfuZbAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T14:41:12.463Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T14:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2074</seriesId>
    <sha256>275dcd3483d15d8c249970c5cff1626239c3f0b62f3695be638bffafd606654a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Robots Support Cooks and Bakers</subtitle>
    <title>BIZ STREAM</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:31:26.489Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>