<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-17T00:30:03.160Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>4562406e38a4085a</seriesId>
  <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>176</airingId>
    <content>Our theme for this episode is topped rice bowls. A bowl of rice with delicious toppings is a quick and easy single-dish meal popular in Japan. We'll be introducing one of the many common rice bowls: Oyako-don. We'll show you the techniques needed to prepare the chicken and onion, with the great flavor of dashi and beaten egg, cooked until the egg is perfectly rich and fluffy, and then we'll top it with deliciously crisp Naganegi long onion to provide a great accent. We'll also be making another variant on Oyako-don, using flaked salmon -- a popular ingredient in bento lunches -- and salmon roe, for great taste and a fun texture. The green, yellow, red and pink of these dishes are sure to make them a colorful delight!</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Oyako-don: Chicken and Egg Rice Bowl (2) Salmon and Roe Rice Bowl. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-12T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0GpFTYzB#0ShQ8aeMYTeL3wCavCZ-2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-12T01:00:31.730Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-12T00:29:20.124Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>7b96c6ffb42b75a96b1f22daed7aac7d86d9aa8505ba08ea1f8de1e85fdf56e9</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-12T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Oyako-don - Chicken and Egg Rice Bowl</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-12T04:38:37.482Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0DoUBRTR#t2hmbI_eLHIvlBUNjxdj2w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>184</airingId>
    <content>Our theme for this time is hot pots. Chef Saito will be making Hari-hari hot pot, a delicious favorite perfect for cold winter days. Thinly sliced daikon radish, mizuna potherb mustard greens and pork are briefly dipped in a rich dashi soup to cook them. With Chef Saito's techniques, it's a delicious hot pot that you can make even without a lot of ingredients. After those ingredients have all been eaten, we'll be adding thin Inaniwa udon noodles to help pick up the soup for a delicious finish to the meal -- these noodles go great with hot pots! And for dessert, we'll be having persimmon topped with a homemade sesame sauce.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Hari-hari Hot Pot. (2) Poached Persimmons with Sesame Cream Sauce. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-29T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Xh0knSKS#ITLrIm2wrmBlgBIXgs2JVw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-29T01:00:26.672Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-29T00:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>b8d926e65d040b8af30f89b1f682655a8eb1946e95e046b96d1dae3fc3c2dc0d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-29T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Hari-Hari Hot Pot</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T03:47:21.740Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/K9lh3AwA#iO6Ri6krNlY46uTASQRCfw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>185</airingId>
    <content>Our theme for this episode is steaming. We'll be making Kabura-mushi, or steamed turnip, steaming pure white grated turnip together with shrimp and vegetables for a beautiful traditional Japanese dish. The fluffy white of the grated turnip is evocative of snow, and the thick and shiny yet clear sauce shimmers like ice, giving it a look wonderfully reminiscent of winter scenery in Japan. We'll also be making delicious and nutritious Kayaku Gohan, or rice with chicken and various vegetables mixed in.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Kabura-mushi "Steamed Turnips" (2) Kayaku-gohan "Mixed Rice." Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-08T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/L1MEUJSZ#cQrEtXCQiOIe0-2UA3Raog</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-08T01:00:35.633Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-08T00:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>f85264429de2a2a60fd6226a85e608162ba80ee097a1fe198711b8e5b68405a9</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-08T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Kabura-mushi "Steamed Turnips"</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T12:40:26.220Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5cwAXKDC#Y9kis1tGUpauocFcZwoXkA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>192</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we'll be making onigiri rice balls, a favorite in Japan among young and old alike. This simple dish is made by lightly salting freshly cooked rice, and shaping it into triangles or rough cylinders, then wrapping it in nori seaweed. Chef Rika will be showing us some tricks to make rice balls even tastier. For our side dishes, we'll be making Kimpira and Tamagoyaki rolled omelet -- perfect for bento meals! Our crisp Kimpira is made with potato and carrot, while the Tamagoyaki omelet has a deliciously tender, fluffy texture.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Onigiri "Rice Balls" (2) Kimpira Stir-fry (3) Tamagoyaki "Rolled Omelet." You can cook modern Japanese home meals by yourself with her fun lesson!</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-05T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/gZwyGYAY#G5driuMyN0zOkJHyylP03Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-05T01:00:55.451Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-05T00:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>5290f9e7d8d8c7546435d58c55750c58503c69e73997beee1c4ec3d65c52f5a5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-05T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Onigiri "Rice Balls"</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T07:30:20.229Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7tl1FSSR#QlUdm3Q3YpgB2gkw5n4sfQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>219</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we'll be making 3 uniquely Japanese sandwiches, made with Japanese ingredients, to be served like a multi-course meal. Our main sandwich features a Menchi-katsu ground meat cutlet: the crunchy fried panko bread crumbs and the juicy pork go perfectly with bread. We'll also be making a side sandwich with burdock root -- a popular vegetable in Japan -- and chicken, tossed with mayonnaise. For dessert, we have one more sandwich, filled with a combination of cream and a sweet bean paste made with Azuki beans, an indispensable ingredient for Japanese sweets. We hope you'll join us for these 3 convenient and delicious tastes of Japanese cuisine!</content>
    <description>Today's Japanese Sandwich Trio recipe: Fillings are Menchi-katsu, Burdock Root Salad and Creamy Anko. You can cook modern Japanese home meals by yourself with Rika's fun lesson!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-04T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Ck1g3BQI#W-ESD3qORjygIcMbUZ-zcA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-04T15:00:33.622Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-04T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>6fa3640a14541d4925bafbddf0b1f24fedc72ec7f53bc03de4a3a58612814f4e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-04T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Japanese Sandwich Trio</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:32:27.618Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Z99BwCQQ#q9hLwoGw47xaX4hZtt9VWA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>222</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we'll be making Ten Don, or tempura rice bowls, a popular dish in Japan. We'll be using shrimp, corn and other colorful ingredients, and Chef Rika will share her secret technique to easily make crunchy, delicious tempura. For our side dish, we'll be making chrysanthemum greens seasoned with vinegar -- the perfect match for Ten Don! The mild bitterness of the chrysanthemum greens goes wonderfully with the flavor of the vinegar, for a deliciously refreshing side dish.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Ten Don [Tempura Rice Bowl] (2) Sunomono [Shungiku and Abura-age]. You can cook modern Japanese home meals by yourself with Rika's fun lesson!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-17T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xYwgkLTY#J85jsZdW-M8IOb2USfRAHA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-17T07:00:26.422Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-17T06:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>515d4388155e0817d576feec7f2615941b0488de67900553a8e4470d8a832885</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-17T06:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Ten Don "Tempura Rice Bowl"</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:58:18.052Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0p02wYpb#NpMUMrePUTgJdBPqe8omSA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>223</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we'll be cooking with sake -- it's more than just a drink! Steaming salmon and Asari clams with sake gives those foods the savory umami flavor of the sake, for a dish with a delicious depth. We'll also be making a dessert with sake: Chef Rika's own original recipe for Castella sponge cake, featuring the light, fragrant aroma of sake, and coarse sugar to provide a crunchy accent.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Sake-steamed Salmon, Potatoes, and Clams (2) Sake Kasutera. You can cook modern Japanese home meals by yourself with Rika's fun lesson!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-01T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/bsMACLbJ#I0wHUNiDsy8AaFwS8t4ugA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-01T01:00:28.850Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-01T00:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>5999a7cdf2d987188183d9c9c862bdb959241d726dfa0fd90b08d5058cb06503</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-01T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Sake-steamed Salmon, Potatoes, and Clams</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T12:46:18.354Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tAo0EKya#7CIe4wwtKOXuU4A9_UpTKQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>246</airingId>
    <content>Our theme for this episode is decorating. We'll be making Temari sushi, a charming bite-sized style of sushi with beautiful toppings, said to have originated in Kyoto Prefecture. The colors red and white are considered auspicious in Japan, so this sushi is topped with salmon and scallops, to make a dish perfect for serving at a house party! Our side dish is oyster Mizore-jiru soup, a warm dish that's especially good for the colder months. This soup is made with grated daikon radish for a look evocative of snow, and topped with yuzu citrus to give this elegant dish a bright yellow accent and a refreshing aroma. Chef Saito will also share some of the delicate presentation techniques used in Japanese cuisine.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Temari Sushi (2) Mizore-jiru. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-24T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZBoGmR6C#aAJgnC71N6FF2cw1AJJyvw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-24T01:00:26.918Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-24T00:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>e2006dbe16d3956825b025cb3ecfb8502ce9c8ff189ee8a234721a1ad048bf0c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-24T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Temari Sushi</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:33:03.935Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MAlmhSpR#5l0ULXVyqjlK9AC7KGmpvA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>247</airingId>
    <content>Our theme for this episode is seasoning. We'll be making a stir-fry, a home-cooked dish popular for its casual simplicity, and add a seasoning made with miso to give it a deliciously sophisticated flavor. Chef Saito will share his own unique seasoning blend, too: by mixing miso with other distinctively Japanese seasonings, you too can bring out the best of ingredients' flavors and give dishes a satisfying depth! For our side dish, we'll be cooking rice with sweet potato, an ingredient commonly eaten throughout Japan in autumn and winter. We'll also learn about how to use a versatile Japanese seasoning that has long been beloved as a drink, to help enhance the sweetness of other ingredients.</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Miso Stir Fry with Lotus Root and Chicken (2) Sweet Potato Rice. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-27T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OgNTGA6L#FxGbmS5nlHATeHZYLpjXOA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-27T15:00:31.192Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-27T14:29:20.092Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>5d4f2b7f24caa5825640527f757704709904962064ea7925514b6d19c5f4c242</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-27T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Miso Stir Fry with Lotus Root and Chicken</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:18:04.305Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3ltGUaBB#uiol8MzWjFqKxtyVpZS3sg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>248</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we'll be making beautiful Chirashi sushi. This dish is perfect for winter, which is a great season for parties: not only is Chirashi sushi healthy and delicious, it's also incredibly picturesque and great for sharing on social media! This sushi features toppings in 5 different colors, arranged in straight lines, for a striking appearance that will make you want to show this dish off! For our side dish, we're preparing Chawan-mushi savory custard, a popular side for sushi, served topped with a gorgeous thickened Ankake sauce made with crab and Naganegi long onion. This meal is a great way to learn about the careful techniques used in Japanese cuisine, including how the rice is cooked, how the ingredients are prepared and advice for cooking eggs. And the result makes for a spectacular dish to serve at your next party!</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Shrimp Chirashi Sushi (2) Chawan-mushi with Crabmeat Sauce. A gorgeous Chirashi-sushi set that's perfect for parties. Give it a try at home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/XxslHSCA#CxYwib9ZPXLmiJR9J_W3cQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T01:01:07.976Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T00:29:20.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>abd00edb4eea2419528365dcbe031997e2ab5cb0dd1f3993aee64dbfa05e29a6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Shrimp Chirashi Sushi</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T01:56:36.158Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5080kKaQ#rL0a0DdUFNZci7Y-n2DOig</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>251</airingId>
    <content>In this episode of Authentic Japanese Cooking, professional chef and Japanese cuisine expert Tatsuo Saito will be teaching us about the fascinating essence of Japanese cooking. Recipes: (1) Chikuzen-ni (simmered chicken and root vegetables), (2) octopus rice. We hope that this look at Japan's food culture will inspire you to try these authentic dishes at home!</content>
    <description>Today's recipes: (1) Chikuzen-ni (Simmered Chicken and Root Vegetables) (2) Octopus Rice. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-15T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Xw9xjaKR#i86fWP1wOeSgiPfcjAL2aw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-15T01:00:29.485Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-15T00:29:23.062Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>d432cfaef86804c9b891688fe787fb26eebe0f20541c858cd3197ff8f491b8cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-15T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Chikuzen-ni (Simmered Chicken and Root Vegetables)</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:05:00.008Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/8tUwzJrC#a7GroPo1-oKeP6bBCUUXrQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>253</airingId>
    <content>Learn about easy, delicious and healthy cooking with Chef Rika! Featured recipes: (1) Korokke (Camembert cheese, canned sardine, kabocha squash), (2) Bean sprout and bell pepper salad. These 3 kinds of Korokke are quick and easy to prepare!</content>
    <description>Today's recipe: (1) Korokke (Camembert cheese, Canned Sardines, Kabocha Squash) (2) Bean sprout and Bell pepper Salad.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-15T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4qhC0AzY#Zz5meAnUfdmZV0XnX0hCEA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-15T15:00:34.700Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-15T14:29:20.178Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>d32964ef3cf8544de5344870ceb62c959abd59ab89b212042a04f80af329c181</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-15T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Korokke Trio</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-17T00:28:56.838Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>254</airingId>
    <content>Learn about Japanese home cooking with master chef Saito, based on traditional Japanese cooking techniques! Featured recipes: (1) Mushi sushi (2) clear dashi with clams.</content>
    <description>Chef Saito's new recipes: (1) Mushi Sushi (2) Clear Dashi with Clams. Why not learn Japanese food culture and try real Japanese dishes at your home!</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-08T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qp9yxBgI#GqXqctg601J5HG3tTmOeFQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-08T15:00:28.776Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-08T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>3203c2689bdf9be4e7e4d5ff4fc60d28643a8a171a58f2f683b6f906bc6c0da2</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-08T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Mushi Sushi</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-08T15:44:59.501Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WF1AAL6Q#Gh3EOGVQFfXwcIm3iGiC3g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>278</airingId>
    <content>Learn about easy, delicious and healthy cooking with Chef Rika! Featured recipes: (1) Homemade Udon Noodles (2) Homemade Udon Noodles with Poached Eggs (3) Homemade Udon Noodles with Black Sesame Sauce (4) Homemade Udon Noodles with Sudachi Citrus.</content>
    <description>Featured recipes: (1) Homemade Udon Noodles (2) With Poached Eggs (3) With Black Sesame Sauce (4) With Sudachi Citrus. Learn about easy, delicious, and healthy cooking with Chef Rika!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-20T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Ow13CKKb#y1pln1MkrlZCot1aT6llHQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-20T15:00:30.380Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-20T14:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>8abd1bd559fa7aafe7d1b5297bf912e1a0907b11e3698492189e650cc993bfaf</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-20T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rika's TOKYO CUISINE: Three Ways to Enjoy Homemade Udon Noodles</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:00:19.771Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/R0d3gIgS#eBLFiHnnRLdIfl2ZFS3e0A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>279</airingId>
    <content>Learn about Japanese home cooking with Master Chef Saito, based on traditional Japanese cooking techniques! Featured recipes: (1) Squid and Nori Rolls (Isobe-age) (2) Ankake Noodles with Mushrooms.</content>
    <description>Featured recipes: (1) Squid and Nori Rolls/Isobe-age (2) Ankake Noodles with Mushrooms. Learn about Japanese home cooking with Master Chef Saito, based on traditional Japanese cooking techniques!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-11T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/jUEj3QYT#p8fhvc8-JCRWeLe9TwljqA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-11T15:00:31.619Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-11T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>d9740c6ec18d12119c054e50f80e372d95740ec9de43fca43257de9e6157892a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-11T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Squid and Nori Rolls (Isobe-age)</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T01:33:58.046Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ipEg0LYL#_ZODAUxq8cGYMcDCCeI7Nw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>280</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we focus on Nagano Prefecture. It depicts the world of simple Japanese food created by the pure water that flows from the mountainous area.</content>
    <description>In this episode, we focus on Nagano Prefecture. It depicts the world of simple Japanese food created by the pure water that flows from the mountainous area.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-18T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5gkGwLaA#-9pZ_OXUopQk9qPKjW7k2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-18T15:00:27.366Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-18T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>4b45fbaf05dfce9e5b36d5407fe1fe8bda1e3996ec361b5d53e7fea8ecee64c0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-18T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Cook Around Japan "Nagano": Water Complementing Rice, the Japanese Way</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T01:32:25.051Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cpETQSiY#va0VEr2AA0MQ3EuSjzp-2A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>281</airingId>
    <content>In this second episode, we learn about Nagano's local specialties, as discovered by a chef who moved from Tokyo.</content>
    <description>In this second episode, we learn about Nagano's local specialties, as discovered by a chef who moved from Tokyo.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-25T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KU0SyaaS#4NyURlBGO5tgUin-vqC3PA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-25T15:00:26.960Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-25T14:29:22.773Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>09faca4e6c87a0d9c0364a7496c4427ff8ba5bdb49ff7d95867515a3c47210a1</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-25T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Cook Around Japan "Nagano": Discovering Nagano's Local Specialties</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T10:28:39.936Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/s89yjJSJ#DeHhw8g8oSkNCFeRATozbQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>282</airingId>
    <content>Learn about Japanese home cooking with Master Chef Saito, based on traditional Japanese cooking techniques! Featured recipes: (1) Beef with Kombu Dashi Sauce (2) Chrysanthemum-shaped Turnips.</content>
    <description>Featured recipes: (1) Beef with Kombu Dashi Sauce (2) Chrysanthemum-shaped Turnips. Learn about Japanese home cooking with Master Chef Saito, based on traditional Japanese cooking techniques!</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-01T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hE8GDS4I#PIBb9OCoDHK-739nw9R6qg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-01T15:00:51.184Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-01T14:29:22.606Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2019</seriesId>
    <sha256>525f1c1696fa8c003ff9edb35a1c1a7d75eeee0a13eff7b8b7120e1a1d4d6b43</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-01T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Authentic Japanese Cooking: Beef with Kombu Dashi Sauce</subtitle>
    <title>Dining with the Chef</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-01T15:47:45.401Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tNdRWA6B#I3CkYc4eh8IxfaO2LTVcIg</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>