<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-24T00:30:04.080Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>4b75bcecb7568a5f</seriesId>
  <title>J-Arena</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>072</airingId>
    <content>We explore speed climbing, a unique competitive discipline that sees 2 climbers race to the top of a standardized 15m wall. Japan's climbers have traditionally been strong in bouldering and lead climbing, however, the advent of combined events that include speed climbing has prompted a concentrated effort to slash times. We check in to see what progress is being made and also meet speed climbing specialist Ikeda Yudai, who helps us analyze the innovative technique of world champion sport climber Narasaki Tomoa.</content>
    <description>We explore speed climbing, a unique competitive discipline that sees two climbers race to the top of a 15m wall, and analyze the innovative technique of world champion sport climber Narasaki Tomoa.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-04T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wU8DyIDY#4e1_h_a4JuaVtK_85CCLqg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-04T05:00:27.925Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-04T04:29:20.007Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>c204e02dc7c17a8e3867b9f4705b891979aac3d44ae4a3743bdc8a4242a4a7cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-04T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sport Climbing - Speed</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T01:19:07.052Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/XlU2hbhI#9QeT9nYLkk9nmCHb4vPaWw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>073</airingId>
    <content>Breaststroke is a popular and easy to learn recreational swimming style, but when it comes to top-level competition it's actually considered one of the most technically challenging of all. The effects of water resistance are particularly pronounced for breaststroke, meaning small adjustments can make a big difference. Down the decades Japanese swimmers have time and again set new standards for technique in the stroke. We meet Watanabe Ippei, the first man ever to record a sub-2m07s time in the 200m event, and assess his prospects for beating his formidable rivals on the world stage.</content>
    <description>Down the decades Japanese swimmers have time and again set new standards for technique in the breaststroke. We meet Watanabe Ippei, the first man ever to record a sub-2m07s time in the 200m event.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-01T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xxs0wJYQ#1f_yI62fo_HnazveOrNFTQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-01T05:00:23.852Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-01T04:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>964c2e3355e61980cfaa0036085d0981a66761b6c172bbbef832fbf5f534981b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-01T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Swimming - Breaststroke</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-01T06:34:20.177Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/n0dABRqT#kgFXsmSDRqacuzapNZYssw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>075</airingId>
    <content>Since its earliest iterations in the 1960's, wakeboarding has evolved into one of the fastest-growing water sports in the world. Using the wake created by a boat as a ramp, riders perform mind-boggling aerial tricks, twisting and turning with extreme creativity and style. 16-year-old Takamura Taiga is the current Japan Men's Champion, but is yet to make a serious breakthrough onto the world stage. Coached by his father on a lake at the foot of Mt. Fuji, we follow Taiga as he tries to land a highly advanced trick and see if he has what it takes to compete against the world's best.</content>
    <description>In wakeboarding, one the world's fastest growing water sports, riders display all kinds of mind-boggling tricks. We follow a young Japanese champion in his quest to reach a par with the world's best.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-27T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/EdoSQTDR#thxuRCVV8KlSklsS0Fq5VQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-27T05:00:28.263Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-27T04:29:22.254Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>8fc02e4f7d1a5b92716575bd1c256e17b71b218f2fd5ce4364e8b6c33f070a78</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-27T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Wakeboarding</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:54:42.499Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IcoAEI6K#qb5allW8QlqYmu9xpYC4Ag</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>076</airingId>
    <content>At the 1972 Munich Games, Japanese gymnast Tsukahara Mitsuo stunned the world with his revolutionary horizontal bar dismount. The "Tsukahara" would have a lasting impact on gymnastics, influencing countless techniques including the "Kolman" and the "Cassina." In the 21st century, Japanese gymnasts such as Tomita Hiroyuki, Uchimura Kohei and most recently Miyachi Hidetaka, have taken the Tsukahara's key elements into fresh territory, pushing the boundaries of human potential in gymnastics on the way. We explore the rich legacy of this iconic move.</content>
    <description>At the 1972 Munich Games, gymnast Tsukahara Mitsuo stunned the world with his revolutionary horizontal bar dismount. The "Tsukahara" had a lasting impact on gymnastics, inspiring countless variations.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-11T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rtcA1bYC#2gMVRgvPGgsWVO9ZS2zUFQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-11T05:00:28.580Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-11T04:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>6cfaa06283d3e02222289cf89c44ba9ab418e8208219c7f402de1bde9c83b52b</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-11T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Gymnastics - Horizontal Bar</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:32:29.949Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SclQlSAL#ISNaiIQbEcLRejc6n5hhfw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>077</airingId>
    <content>Core training has become a buzzword in the fitness industry in recent years, with well-known sports personalities like Japanese footballer Nagatomo Yuto extolling its benefits. We find out how balanced conditioning of the low back and abdomen not only boosts performance for elite athletes, but also provides the stability to avoid many common sports injuries and health issues. We meet a core training expert who has helped many of Japan's top athletes, and explore some of the similarities between core training methods and traditional Japanese martial arts principles.</content>
    <description>Core training has become a buzzword in the fitness industry. We find out how balanced conditioning of the low back and abdomen can boost performance and provide the stability to avoid common injuries.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-18T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IlVDxaKA#AmUkuXk18x8YI8pltStQ6A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-18T05:00:29.702Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-18T04:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>e6d58db38e0c430001ebbbdced790f659494b40c86a2cb225fde417644789eaa</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-18T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Core Training</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T17:46:58.519Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ix9igSLJ#2chXxFpRbVqSrc10pWk9eg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>078</airingId>
    <content>Over the past 2 decades, the world of competitive video-gaming has transformed from niche amateur hobby to a multi-billion dollar spectator sport with global reach. We take the pulse on Japan's rapidly evolving esports scene and meet the legendary Umehara Daigo, known as "The Beast" for his unrivaled mastery of 2D arcade fighting games. As he turns 40 this year, we look back over Daigo's record-breaking career so far, and explore the secrets of his enduring success after decades in the sport.</content>
    <description>As esports hit the mainstream, we take the pulse on Japan's rapidly evolving scene. We meet fighting game legend Umehara Daigo and reveal the secrets to his enduring success after decades in the game.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-29T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/a3Zj3AjB#xP66EbC1NGSOsXSqhZUJHg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-29T05:00:27.547Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-29T04:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>fb8f059207bc9ffd4989043a158d97873017155ce06e4c9f494e4152be918f7e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-29T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>eSports</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-29T05:49:04.494Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/pSY1CSSR#zOLklHoVefSTSKzb6_mYnA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>079</airingId>
    <content>Ekiden is a hugely popular form of long-distance relay race in Japan, dating back to 1917. Key races are typically held in winter, with televised races over New Year's drawing audiences in the tens of millions. The team relay format makes for a distinct atmosphere and appeal that sets Ekiden apart from individual long-distance events. In this episode we feature the inter-high school Ekiden held in Kyoto at the end of 2020. We also explore the relationship between Ekiden events and local communities, and learn about the key role played by overseas students from East Africa.</content>
    <description>"Ekiden" is a hugely popular form of long-distance relay race in Japan, dating back to 1917. With key races typically held in winter, we report on the recent inter-high school ekiden event in Kyoto.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-05T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sE1h2CDY#znToPX0PENuuZuUXQcHRdg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-05T05:00:28.145Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-05T04:29:20.136Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>f3c1cbbe6994d0061793f4441cfcb264953f5575ad0af94fc2cfa487b9269792</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-05T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ekiden</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-05T21:51:15.452Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JoplEI5D#gBakNuHWiqDnnka6rB2r2w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>080</airingId>
    <content>With no divisions by weight class, the All Japan Judo Championships is a unique event said to determine Japan's overall top judoka. Held yearly since 1948, the tournament stands out for its memorable scenes of smaller wrestlers attempting to topple larger opponents, including a valiant effort by 75kg judoka Koga Toshihiko, who made it all the way to the final in 1990 only to lose to a rival weighing over 50kg more. Through the lens of the tournament's 2020 edition as well as past historic bouts, we examine the spirit of judo and the core principle of "softness overcomes hardness."</content>
    <description>The All Japan Judo Championships determine Japan's overall top judoka. With only an open weight division, the event is noted for its scenes of smaller wrestlers attempting to topple larger opponents.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-19T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0V5CyDZT#QgzaCQll0Y2gEhjGEmw8Ow</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-19T05:00:28.761Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-19T04:29:20.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>319bb842f3104e85934a91abe92b10da021527cd994a255dae66ba3406f20175</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-19T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Judo</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-19T05:55:40.163Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/G5QyELoK#0D19v9eRNcf9LLBq_XDdvg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>081</airingId>
    <content>In Japan, some college-level sports have as dedicated a following as the professional leagues. A baseball league contested by 6 Tokyo universities has a proud history stretching right back to a match between the universities of Keio and Waseda in 1903. The 2 teams' century-spanning rivalry includes a particularly dramatic series from 1960 that remains etched in the national memory. We also learn about the student sumo wrestlers who later turn pro, as well as the student football teams giving top J.League sides a run for their money in a unique open tournament.</content>
    <description>In Japan, some college-level sports have as dedicated a following as the pro leagues. We cover college baseball and sumo, as well as the student football teams giving the pros a run for their money.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-26T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fwsFxSiD#HsgJIotP9X2C_k7oCruQ2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-26T05:00:28.466Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-26T04:29:23.904Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>f56bda6ff04dd3086fc7801b8d0191f96ec04d0798cc070fb740ec93f4730fdb</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-26T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>College Sports</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-26T06:10:24.717Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WkBWwLpB#SByPNCEYKHMVOk4DDXg6pg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>082</airingId>
    <content>Shorinji Kempo is a dynamic martial art that combines both hard and soft techniques while developing mind and body as one. Previously, we followed British practitioner Paul King as he trained intensively for his 4th dan exam at the head dojo in Shikoku, Japan. In this episode we catch up with Paul, who returned home to the Netherlands to fulfill his long-held dream of opening his own dojo. Not long after he started, the pandemic hit, yet Paul is applying Shorinji Kempo's philosophy to help him be there for his students and ensure their continued progress amid the challenges of lockdown.</content>
    <description>We catch up with a 4th dan Shorinji Kempo teacher in Holland as he strives to keep the members of his new dojo on track with their training in the martial art amid the ongoing pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-05T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rw5kwTDS#AQkxOYa709poPKq54sIYbw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-05T05:00:28.186Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-05T04:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2073</seriesId>
    <sha256>295ddb5bafb2623c301b4282664720ce680c5183beef8dcd576ca85e726ed94a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-05T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shorinji Kempo</subtitle>
    <title>J-Arena</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-05T05:51:56.851Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1aoHgIAL#DuB8kh5rFO7wOw3skoQh9A</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>