<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-16T22:40:03.544Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>50872d98dbace20c</seriesId>
  <title>TOKYO EYE</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>185</airingId>
    <content>Asakusa is one of Tokyo's most popular tourist destinations. But due to the coronavirus pandemic, visits to Asakusa are down, and the neighborhood is feeling the pinch. At the same time, it's using the situation as a chance to get inventive. This time, we take a virtual tour of Asakusa from our studio to see how things are going.</content>
    <description>Due to the coronavirus pandemic, visits to Asakusa are down. Now it's using the situation as a chance to get inventive. We take a virtual tour of Asakusa from our studio to see how things are going.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8gNinTxL#NPK_AgjmujLDa4MpRBB-XQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T00:00:28.552Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-24T23:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>49dbdfd149e1fb4d10347f208dad528f52f43008a916892e67de7031603d6d3e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-24T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: A Virtual Tour of Asakusa</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:31:11.414Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1skAVAiY#nXENBQFPsDji42GLU2WEww</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>189</airingId>
    <content>Masks: an essential tool in the fight against the coronavirus. Now Tokyoites are putting their own spin on masks, expressing their individuality with unique patterns and designs. Let's learn how masks are serving as both pandemic protectors and fashion items!</content>
    <description>Tokyoites are putting their own spin on masks, expressing their individuality with unique patterns and designs. Let's learn how masks are serving as both pandemic protectors and fashion items!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VAQ2ALra#kS73bCjzok-1R1EiIdx2Tw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T00:00:28.304Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-01T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>39b32b74ce86fc009d20051373d13034c4ec677bf2c1403841a04053cdaf3607</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-01T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Masks on the Move</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:25:16.988Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/bwsnUCSC#UNFAO-W0XbK7NzQJJtajKg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>191</airingId>
    <content>In Japan, the coronavirus pandemic has brought new attention to a Japanese creature or Yokai, called Amabie, who's said to protect against plagues. Thanks to social media, drawing images of Amabie has become a new trend. Let's find out more about this mysterious creature.</content>
    <description>In Japan, the pandemic has brought new attention to a monster called Amabie. It's said to protect against plagues. Thanks to social media, drawing images of Amabie has become a new trend.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/bIkVSAgS#pcy6tBrirmQdM7lX7F9D4g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T00:00:32.789Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-17T23:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>cd55b71cb1cdede4778db4196fd89f1f0d66f39d734fee8b28c39773f79bad37</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-17T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Amabie vs. the Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:12:11.183Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/nwlyWLzL#kywu4aYqGdo20UO-EDY7Ew</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>192</airingId>
    <content>The coronavirus pandemic has changed how we eat. With fewer visits to restaurants and more meals at home, people in Tokyo have started to think about food in a whole new way. Today we discover some new ways that food is nourishing both our bodies and minds.</content>
    <description>The coronavirus pandemic has changed how we eat. With fewer visits to restaurants and more meals at home, people in Tokyo have started to think about food and nourishment in a whole new way.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-09T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/oNh1yQoI#Uwk1ddicl9RgMCOpHq-ojQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-09T00:00:33.046Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-08T23:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>576fe91c6c5b3ccaa560020efd2ee77d94efa6d227b34057fd4e2cd8c068c131</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-08T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: The Power of Nourishment</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:58:36.469Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/C4Fi2b7C#iL20PanF3ukCb-cGApTNUQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>193</airingId>
    <content>The pandemic has revived interest in an old pastime: fishing! Many Tokyoites are discovering the fun of this relaxing, refreshing activity and enjoying the way it helps them get in touch with nature. Let's cast a line and learn more.</content>
    <description>The pandemic has revived interest in an old pastime: fishing! Tokyoites are discovering the fun of this relaxing, refreshing activity and enjoying the way it helps them get in touch with nature.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/TVVAQbiL#V-vhX6v_SF8mh0FqLpn3QQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T00:00:28.269Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-15T23:29:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>ebe50179f8c4366834d7322dade0dbf6a1e8cb79446910a33e058d4985a35bd4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-15T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Fishing for Relaxation</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:24:02.816Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/BttEnR7D#Dmz-jvSox-4gpvZVCZBkAA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>194</airingId>
    <content>The hotel business has taken a huge hit during the pandemic. That includes reasonably priced hotels popular with tourists from abroad, which are virtually on hiatus. Today, we find out how Tokyo hotels are fighting for survival by embracing new ideas.</content>
    <description>The hotel business has taken a huge hit during the coronavirus pandemic. Today, we find out how hotels in Tokyo are fighting for survival by embracing new ideas.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fh9zEKBS#yfrIiOzlHsoIiNBAJM5Y6g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T00:00:26.829Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T23:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>0935e16484e1f29fa31e9914ad726f168f3ec883607f5d2030551bf816d1ee8c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Hotels Fight for Survival</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T18:22:26.088Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ERtz3aYK#2guUtBCWuj8xEtSlF-BVPw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>195</airingId>
    <content>During the pandemic, parks around Tokyo have been putting their impressive power on display. They're gaining fresh attention for their ability to connect people with nature -- and with each other. Let's take a refreshing stroll through Tokyo's great parks.</content>
    <description>Parks around Tokyo are gaining fresh attention during the pandemic for their ability to connect people with nature. Let's take a refreshing stroll through Tokyo's parks.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Cl8SxYhI#gKfOJiHhPzXAf-1gvjtZkg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T00:00:28.400Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-05T23:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>0668d8f2736f520b6700e73f2ad6c4d87794c181bebc0c408a19d4e874b7366b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-05T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Parks Offer Pandemic Peace</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T07:45:30.877Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TRkAmLLZ#VAbROcbIwaClmMkR5t152Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>196</airingId>
    <content>Here on TOKYO EYE 2020, we've featured many people and organizations trying to make the most of the coronavirus pandemic and give back to society. Today, we'll revisit some of our stories from the past few months and see how the people behind them are doing.</content>
    <description>We've featured many people trying to make the most of the coronavirus pandemic. We will revisit some of our stories from the past few months and see how the people behind them are doing.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-30T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/H4tlSayD#qb_ze9LS2k7fnR9jJdRvzQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-30T00:00:32.853Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-29T23:29:20.067Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2053</seriesId>
    <sha256>3eda4d86408a914adfe6f023fc43fdcdd018ecfca7304f430b3a86df15858dd6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-29T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo and the Coronavirus: Tokyo Fights On</subtitle>
    <title>TOKYO EYE 2020</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-30T01:00:16.934Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ahkhFCgT#7qeAK9CpaF7ehQO_Yjv0Gw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>