<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-13T04:00:04.481Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>509fab78036b7f12</seriesId>
  <title>RISING</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>041</airingId>
    <content>LED grow lights for use in agriculture are currently in the spotlight. Not only do they enable vegetables to be reliably grown all year round, for crops produced in a sterile environment they allow the elimination of agricultural chemicals. And fine adjustment of this lighting even enables regulation of a crop's nutritional content. We follow developer Seiichi Okazaki, a man hoping to harness the cutting edge of veg for a future food revolution.</content>
    <description>Seiichi Okazaki develops LED grow lights that are currently in the spotlight. Year-round growth, reduced chemical use, and control of nutritional value combine to signal a future food revolution.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-02T20:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OEMUlDjY#VSSCrv-X8KUYcKERXH_WMA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-02T20:30:28.289Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-02T19:59:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>ee391093d870e2fb904410b6a5aa56f19ec8d8f55e6cd9d23a6d19be5b448fab</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-02T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Spotlight on a Future Food Revolution: LED Grow Light Developer - Seiichi Okazaki </subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-03T00:36:24.869Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yEECALaA#FNCZIZHMlH6UMAzdDH5WOg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>065</airingId>
    <content>Across Japan, a decline in public transport and small retailers is said to have left as many as 7 million seniors unable to access basic daily necessities. 6 years ago, to address the needs of these "shopping deprived," former magazine editor Tatsuya Sumitomo set up a mobile supermarket service. Now with over 300 trucks, each offering up to 1,200 items, along with clothing and monitor services, his business regularly serves around 40,000 people nationwide, with an average age of 80.</content>
    <description>Follow Tatsuya Sumitomo, founder of a mobile supermarket service with some 300 trucks bringing food, clothing and other daily necessities to some 40,000 elderly "shopping deprived" across Japan.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/N0UEGJbY#5P6pt4uGWf3RBxjosRKjqA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T14:40:30.565Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>97736a1f305bb1fac06fc320fdb8f10df555c356adc80b34baa20af491e66412</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Deals on Wheels: Mobile Supermarket Innovator - Tatsuya Sumitomo</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T23:42:49.732Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UUx3SSbL#jbUzaB0zHGW2TYMxdtdZ-Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>069</airingId>
    <content>With 80% of Japan's regional bus routes operating at a loss, Masaru Yajima runs a firm working to revive these vital transport lifelines. GPS and sensors are used to track progress and passenger flow, and this big data is analyzed to optimize routes and departure times. Further innovations like waiting rooms and wholesale local produce at bus stops have helped to attract passengers beyond the typical user base. And this pioneering transport firm is now taking its successful template overseas.</content>
    <description>Masaru Yajima runs a firm using big data and improved service to revive Japan's declining regional bus routes. We follow a Japanese transport pioneer now taking its successful template overseas.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-09T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/29UHVaAB#jjURHbzN8QztpIgilSpcPg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-09T14:40:44.509Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-09T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>5eac79132a1ccf499fe06d8be8186f33e0da989f773f998b65761be599bd68a7</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-09T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Big Data Driving a Bus Revolution: Public Transport Innovator - Masaru Yajima</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T16:38:57.752Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/So8GhIga#nsvNACQD-R-MyH48GLOUlg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>088</airingId>
    <content>Agricultural science PhD Yukihiro Maru is head of a unique business striving to raise the floor for science and technology in Japan, through both educational workshops and support for science-based startups. Staffed by science graduates and postgrads, the firm conducts around 300 workshops each year aimed at boosting interest in STEM subjects among kids and teens, and has also helped kickstart over 200 tech ventures. Follow their efforts to save the world through the power of science.</content>
    <description>We follow a unique business striving to raise the floor for science and technology in Japan, both through traveling educational workshops and support for science-based startups.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-02T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/UEMEwRAT#41mcTONRmY7M3pPZYxMA5w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-02T14:40:32.536Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-02T14:09:20.131Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>7adf403e837be22a45fc4ec54abb32ff644d6b17535bf7287aa25ceca9ca3cef</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-02T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Saving the World through the Power of Science: STEM Support Innovator - Yukihiro Maru</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T11:11:11.951Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6Q9A2JzD#35_N1CtFFwscKfOARlG2eA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>Year round, Japan plays host to an estimated 300 thousand matsuri. But dwindling rural populations and weakened community bonds now place around a quarter of these colorful traditional festivals in jeopardy. Manabu Ohara heads a unique organization that recruits young people from across the country and overseas to help keep these festivals alive, forging ties with locals and giving a much-needed lift to every aspect -- from preparation, to float-bearing, to cleanup.</content>
    <description>Japan is a country rich in traditional festivals. But as depopulation and community breakup threaten many of these colorful matsuri, one unique group is recruiting young people to help stem the tide.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/aFVTxQwL#4RVjXXO_iFRTLeBTp5z_lA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T02:00:32.279Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T01:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>8df3a1eed98137f8e8ee75f5ff1c1a881117c84b795baa893d8e9b206bf257b4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Giving a Lift to Traditional Festivals: Matsuri Revivalist - Manabu Ohara</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T22:51:24.010Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/o5kQyaBK#1KjaVIVSHaYtxnCVvaCBjA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>095</airingId>
    <content>In Japan, over 6 million tons of food, much of it perfectly edible, go to waste every year. To combat this, Kazuma Kawagoe developed a web application that aims to rescue food otherwise headed for the dumpster. Users can browse and reserve items for collection at reduced prices at registered restaurants and bakeries. Follow a unique venture using technology to raise awareness of this issue and change the attitudes of both, consumers and producers, while reducing the waste of precious food.</content>
    <description>Each year in Japan, over 6 million tons of food go to waste. To combat this issue, Kazuma Kawagoe developed a web application that aims to rescue edible food otherwise destined for the dumpster.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZIBS3TxJ#vq0HdghpSddB698gTKmHLg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T02:00:34.301Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T01:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>42c5510fad14c1d7a6eb8005295f359e2bdc8968260cd649f64aa4a1d11f1d00</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rescuing Doomed Dishes: Anti-Food Waste Pioneer - Kazuma Kawagoe</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T09:03:22.640Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/VQsTFQYD#kWmlyFHE_vmCJkkgxn2wkg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>097</airingId>
    <content>In Osaka, Japan's second-largest city, one NPO is working with the homeless to help them get back on their feet. Founder Kawaguchi Kana has launched various initiatives providing temporary work and accommodation as a bridge back into mainstream society. These include a city-wide bike share scheme and a social business selling photos that leverage the unique perspectives of those who live on the streets. Follow a unique enterprise striving towards a society that offers everyone a second chance.</content>
    <description>Kawaguchi Kana is the founder of an Osaka-based NPO working with the city's homeless to help them get back on their feet. Follow a unique enterprise striving towards a second-chance society.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/G8VkzTRQ#WFJPX_RCbhanxn9A6JLdxA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T02:00:26.138Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>e1b3489229bce1137093f9d6798390c17f9af079f287f528da591dfc7c57a270</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Second-Chance Society: Social Entrepreneur - Kawaguchi Kana</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T18:03:10.756Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/vBsU3Iqb#SWHCaVk1W03TO34wVsXLzA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>098</airingId>
    <content>Widespread school closures due to COVID-19 have thrust online learning resources into the spotlight. In Japan, one such service offering a fun introduction to the world of smartphone and computer programming received 10 thousand signups in just one month, with over 600 schools considering integrating it into their curriculum. We follow founder and former supply teacher Mizuno Yusuke's efforts to bring new opportunities to teenagers at a crucial stage in their educational journey.</content>
    <description>School closures due to COVID-19 have put online learning resources in the spotlight. We follow one such initiative offering Japanese teenagers a fun introduction to the world of digital programming.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-14T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vdMShDDB#F90E9CtiEvEIEzKik8bj9w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-14T02:00:32.583Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-14T01:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>1f91c7268bdf4a69c2061fe7638c2b128d419246bdf4ef378b17573f29ca0a8a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-14T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Progress through Programming: E-Learning Innovator - Mizuno Yusuke</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-14T03:09:57.176Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/xP5gnDJI#LWBtXSxOfqZVaIrHPefQFA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>099</airingId>
    <content>In March 2020, to curb the spread of COVID-19, schools across Japan were urged to close, prompting widespread fears that children may fall behind on their studies. Enter Yunokawa Takahiko, developer of a unique e-learning platform that uses AI to assess students' shortcomings and provide an adaptive learning experience to match. Having rolled out to almost 370 schools during the pandemic, Yunokawa aims to provide affordable, egalitarian learning opportunities to students in Japan and overseas.</content>
    <description>In March 2020, COVID-19 forced schools across Japan to close. Yunokawa Takahiko helped to fill the gap with e-learning materials that use AI to provide an adaptive, accessible educational experience.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fwdR1ArK#pzSjZRyJ1Pq7kTobfx3HdA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T02:00:33.047Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T01:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>91a5a7c228a7ad5c603a56c9c4bdf17d15ae20097a1edffdad2d567a85b0e4f4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>AI - Leveling the Educational Playing Field: E-Learning Innovator - Yunokawa Takahiko</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-27T07:36:12.024Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WAlyTa7A#ofSl7U1Y-LIYR8NhrGegbg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>100</airingId>
    <content>Small scale, specialist technical workshops, or "machikoba," have long been a lynchpin of Japanese manufacturing. But without the ability to effectively communicate their supreme skills, overseas competition and a lack of successors have seen the sector shrink in recent decades. Entrepreneur Furukawa Taku is aiming to change all that, working with a network of over 100 workshops in downtown Tokyo to refresh their old-fashioned business models and promote creative cross-sector collaborations.</content>
    <description>Furukawa Taku is an entrepreneur working to preserve the skills of Tokyo's "machikoba" technical workshops, by refreshing their old-fashioned business models and promoting creative collaborations.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-07T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9dcjnICK#CNHLqLT0AFloimVJMhZhFw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-07T02:00:35.612Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-07T01:29:20.073Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>1d1a71d9a46eabd6a7139c1dfaf746084840a75284f827238fc4bbd75aea1c91</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-07T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Showcasing Tokyo's Technical Treasures: Business Matching Innovator - Furukawa Taku</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-07T02:46:51.856Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SU1GCSpB#Gb3QKiJQTQpojYgzQpWwCw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>103</airingId>
    <content>In spring 2020, with Japan facing a shortage of protective gowns for medical staff battling COVID-19, one 18-employee apparel firm in Nara Prefecture produced 100 thousand gowns in just 3 months thanks to a nationwide network of tailors working from home. Using a unique online platform, founder Tani Hideki recruited some 250 craftspeople left without work by a declining sewing industry. Moving forward, he aims to develop a new generation of craftspeople suited to the demands of the new normal.</content>
    <description>We follow a unique apparel firm using digital technology to build a network of textile craftspeople working from home to create protective medical garments and respond to the needs of the new normal.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-04T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/UWwARapI#0Zq7_QeaowhqmBu_CBp3qg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-04T02:00:32.132Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-04T01:29:20.137Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>022a995e5d99ee8790da457c4799ec2e5758752b2da5686b290df070aa4c0eb0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-04T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Weaving a Textile Network for the New Normal: Textile Industry Innovator - Tani Hideki</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-05T23:51:28.479Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wcQAmDAb#AoxOtD2e3OuWMzj5hvuTKA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>104</airingId>
    <content>In recent years, tough working conditions for often-modest pay have brought serious staff shortages for Japan's food service sector, which faces annual staff turnover of almost 30%. Sawanobori Tetsuya runs a groundbreaking business working to address this issue with cutting-edge yet affordable robots designed to lighten workers' load by taking care of food preparation, hygiene and even customer service. Follow a unique enterprise using robotics to revolutionize Japan's catering sector.</content>
    <description>Sawanobori Tetsuya runs a groundbreaking firm solving staff shortages in Japan's food service sector with cutting-edge robots capable of food preparation, customer service, and more.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-25T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Q9pggaoA#V3dqHosa1h1FhrBtURYWIg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-25T02:00:31.743Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-25T01:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>6738b190e5db5fa85bce6a5353764db7aac4ec29d4a2d150122dbc39fc2a9f52</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-25T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rise of the Kitchen Robots: Catering Robot Pioneer - Sawanobori Tetsuya</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-25T03:38:19.482Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/lJtiQSKS#JWgmoSN4dUyym9nK6XjZUw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>105</airingId>
    <content>Throughout the COVID-19 pandemic, Japan has placed great emphasis on avoiding the Three Cs: closed spaces, crowding and close contact. Kawano Takanobu runs a business that aims to bring peace of mind through digital systems that allow users to avoid such conditions and curb the risk of infection. Rolled out in restaurants, restrooms, hotels and more, his solutions leverage AI, IoT and sensor technology to help people cope with the new normal.</content>
    <description>Against the backdrop of COVID-19, Kawano Takanobu runs a venture that offers peace of mind through digital solutions leveraging AI, IoT, and sensor technology to help users curb the risk of infection.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fJEnFIoQ#gAu7jqOMmUOgsBnEtcWFFw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T02:00:29.421Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-19T01:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b4a6caba9747071f7f689985dbcc451075f8e9fd6ac198e6499ad6a6eb8794a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-19T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fighting Infection by Controlling the Three Cs: Systems Innovator - Kawano Takanobu</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T17:44:47.288Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MwcznKrB#LPZnbzZ_3VHZBNWx0fUq0Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>106</airingId>
    <content>Follow a pioneering Kyoto-based firm that boosts producers across Japan by canning local specialty foods. Under the motto "bringing a brighter future through canned goods," the business, led by former IT engineer Inoue Kazuma, eschews additives to deliver the natural flavor of primary ingredients. From game and seafood, to premium vegetables and other rare and unique delicacies, this unique business fields 20-30 inquiries a month from producers eager to reach a wider audience.</content>
    <description>Follow a unique Kyoto-based firm that boosts Japan's food producers by canning local specialty goods, from game, to seafood, to premium vegetables and other rare and unique delicacies.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/JdR3AKgQ#RDJCsxbRy_jb31ctOxQ6CA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T02:00:30.052Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T01:29:20.064Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>df664c6a1a3345e112622db3867da30d1f0fde8bcf8bf012f1f2fa609e05598d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bringing a "Can-Do" Spirit to Specialty Produce: Preserved Food Pioneer - Inoue Kazuma</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T17:46:08.202Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YQ9Q3Jab#S3xX9aRTYOd04JBkuFyJDg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>107</airingId>
    <content>COVID-19 has hit restaurants hard. Faced with steady running costs despite low sales, some are turning to kitchen cars as a solution. Ishizawa Masayoshi runs a service uniting some 900 independent food truck operators. For a small commission, he matches them with unused patches at office buildings, switching up the selection to give local workers a constantly changing choice of exotic lunch options. As the pandemic runs on, coverage has also expanded to residential areas and medical facilities.</content>
    <description>COVID-19 has put mobile dining options in the spotlight. Follow a service helping food truck operators by matching them with patches at office buildings, residential areas, and medical facilities.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hxdxXCZS#GbsWqD-EAGMceWHmKUlh-Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T02:00:30.217Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T01:29:24.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>8766d694f3660358b03309d5a9d9e6bbb5089d6f9bb56b606e20baa7600ecf21</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Food Trucking the Blues Away: Mobile Dining Innovator - Ishizawa Masayoshi</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T08:03:44.155Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0sNlXA6b#dQ8komILwws0SvQhZnIOgQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>108</airingId>
    <content>Around the world, the chaos caused by the COVID-19 pandemic has brought calls for a green recovery focused on eco-friendly businesses and renewable energy. Yoshida Hiroko runs an NPO promoting green energy and sustainable food production in rural Japan. By creating virtuous cycles, and organizing events that attract participants from further afield, she leverages local natural resources to revitalize mountain areas hit by depopulation.</content>
    <description>The COVID-19 pandemic has brought global calls for a green recovery. We follow an NPO using green energy and sustainable food production to revitalize rural communities.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-21T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ui5wwbaL#GxdcypufeOJUdBY_VAiapg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-21T02:00:32.977Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-21T01:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>d8ecc9d312960387f853cb15f486546f4af71399a533a8d60da58ad13619aaf5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-21T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Green Recovery in Rural Japan: NPO Founder - Yoshida Hiroko</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-21T03:43:00.142Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UJhCUKAQ#eBBNFrphuyBrkrTLw8oCCQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>109</airingId>
    <content>With human interaction restricted by the pandemic, robotic communication aids are in the spotlight. Aoki Shunsuke heads a firm that develops such devices, with user-friendly messenger robots aimed at children and seniors uncomfortable with smartphones; home sensors that pair with the robots to let you monitor the wellbeing of isolated relatives; and robotics kits that help kids learn while expressing their creativity. Follow a unique business developing innovative solutions for the new normal.</content>
    <description>With human interaction limited by the pandemic, robotic communication aids for kids and seniors are in the spotlight. Follow a unique robot business developing innovative solutions for the new normal.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-18T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/P41mjBgL#RebRV124eFP11gIx9w9Y5w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-18T02:00:28.750Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-18T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>7a337fd71104b0943c2e7cefe616d63040531d90bbe1c558d73661db34973a23</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-18T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tackling the New Normal - Robots with a Human Touch: Personal Robotics Innovator - Aoki Shunsuke</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-18T03:01:47.180Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/c8sWBTYI#Xjo53_OiARmjCse7T1Vz8Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>110</airingId>
    <content>Food waste is a global issue. And fresh fruit -- easily bruised; rejected for minor deviations in size, shape and color; and prone to price dips due to bumper crops -- is among the most widely discarded items. Kinoshita Masayuki set out to solve this with tailored flash freezing technology that maintains the taste and texture of cut fruit without the need for conventional preservatives. And now his approach is even helping pandemic-hit restaurants deliver their dishes with no loss in quality.</content>
    <description>Follow a firm using unique freezing technology to reduce food waste by preserving discarded fruit with no loss of taste or texture, and helping pandemic-hit restaurants deliver fresh dishes to diners.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-18T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Tkoy0KIJ#EPcRkJj2MdNJnTmqwgaIkA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-18T02:00:27.881Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-18T01:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>7e5a9bca1fdb469b10cf146115c63fa3a45bf5bdeeedc4115e475a252f675a6b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-18T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Quick Freezing Breathes New Life into Waste Food: Freezing Consultant - Kinoshita Masayuki</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T01:25:22.087Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/DglBxAjI#Q3t4LhYWonTrKU_kx7V3Zg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>111</airingId>
    <content>Kuji Kosuke heads an Iwate Prefecture's sake brewery with 119 years of history. Through an approach that melds tradition with the French "terroir" philosophy, using mountain spring water and rice varieties suited to the local environment, his beverages have won prizes in Japan and overseas. But with demand for sake falling due to the pandemic, he responded with "Japanese spirit," turning his surplus rice crop to more storable gin made with local botanicals, and vodka filtered with Iwate charcoal.</content>
    <description>Follow an historic sake brewery tackling the pandemic with "Japanese spirit," turning surplus rice crop to gin made with local botanicals, and vodka filtered with Iwate charcoal.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-25T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7xg0iaqD#qtdrKm0QW_n9mhwztSJUBA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-25T02:00:27.140Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-25T01:29:23.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>564561f22ef315564cf851dd12bda6575ff3e8ab5a267192d3d6bc507174e13f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-25T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tackling the Pandemic with "Japanese Spirit": Sake Modernizer - Kuji Kosuke</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-29T11:48:29.807Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/GhAQwD7K#OcOZC57CI6HnQ5r4KHJCEw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>