<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-06T16:05:02.922Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>509fab78036b7f12</seriesId>
  <title>RISING</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>065</airingId>
    <content>Across Japan, a decline in public transport and small retailers is said to have left as many as 7 million seniors unable to access basic daily necessities. 6 years ago, to address the needs of these "shopping deprived," former magazine editor Tatsuya Sumitomo set up a mobile supermarket service. Now with over 300 trucks, each offering up to 1,200 items, along with clothing and monitor services, his business regularly serves around 40,000 people nationwide, with an average age of 80.</content>
    <description>Follow Tatsuya Sumitomo, founder of a mobile supermarket service with some 300 trucks bringing food, clothing and other daily necessities to some 40,000 elderly "shopping deprived" across Japan.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/N0UEGJbY#5P6pt4uGWf3RBxjosRKjqA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T14:40:30.565Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>97736a1f305bb1fac06fc320fdb8f10df555c356adc80b34baa20af491e66412</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Deals on Wheels: Mobile Supermarket Innovator - Tatsuya Sumitomo</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T23:42:49.732Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UUx3SSbL#jbUzaB0zHGW2TYMxdtdZ-Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>088</airingId>
    <content>Agricultural science PhD Yukihiro Maru is head of a unique business striving to raise the floor for science and technology in Japan, through both educational workshops and support for science-based startups. Staffed by science graduates and postgrads, the firm conducts around 300 workshops each year aimed at boosting interest in STEM subjects among kids and teens, and has also helped kickstart over 200 tech ventures. Follow their efforts to save the world through the power of science.</content>
    <description>We follow a unique business striving to raise the floor for science and technology in Japan, both through traveling educational workshops and support for science-based startups.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-02T14:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/UEMEwRAT#41mcTONRmY7M3pPZYxMA5w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-02T14:40:32.536Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-02T14:09:20.131Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>7adf403e837be22a45fc4ec54abb32ff644d6b17535bf7287aa25ceca9ca3cef</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-02T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Saving the World through the Power of Science: STEM Support Innovator - Yukihiro Maru</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T11:11:11.951Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6Q9A2JzD#35_N1CtFFwscKfOARlG2eA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>Year round, Japan plays host to an estimated 300 thousand matsuri. But dwindling rural populations and weakened community bonds now place around a quarter of these colorful traditional festivals in jeopardy. Manabu Ohara heads a unique organization that recruits young people from across the country and overseas to help keep these festivals alive, forging ties with locals and giving a much-needed lift to every aspect -- from preparation, to float-bearing, to cleanup.</content>
    <description>Japan is a country rich in traditional festivals. But as depopulation and community breakup threaten many of these colorful matsuri, one unique group is recruiting young people to help stem the tide.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/aFVTxQwL#4RVjXXO_iFRTLeBTp5z_lA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T02:00:32.279Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T01:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>8df3a1eed98137f8e8ee75f5ff1c1a881117c84b795baa893d8e9b206bf257b4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Giving a Lift to Traditional Festivals: Matsuri Revivalist - Manabu Ohara</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T22:51:24.010Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/o5kQyaBK#1KjaVIVSHaYtxnCVvaCBjA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>095</airingId>
    <content>In Japan, over 6 million tons of food, much of it perfectly edible, go to waste every year. To combat this, Kazuma Kawagoe developed a web application that aims to rescue food otherwise headed for the dumpster. Users can browse and reserve items for collection at reduced prices at registered restaurants and bakeries. Follow a unique venture using technology to raise awareness of this issue and change the attitudes of both, consumers and producers, while reducing the waste of precious food.</content>
    <description>Each year in Japan, over 6 million tons of food go to waste. To combat this issue, Kazuma Kawagoe developed a web application that aims to rescue edible food otherwise destined for the dumpster.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZIBS3TxJ#vq0HdghpSddB698gTKmHLg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T02:00:34.301Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-31T01:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>42c5510fad14c1d7a6eb8005295f359e2bdc8968260cd649f64aa4a1d11f1d00</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-31T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Rescuing Doomed Dishes: Anti-Food Waste Pioneer - Kazuma Kawagoe</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T09:03:22.640Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/VQsTFQYD#kWmlyFHE_vmCJkkgxn2wkg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>097</airingId>
    <content>In Osaka, Japan's second-largest city, one NPO is working with the homeless to help them get back on their feet. Founder Kawaguchi Kana has launched various initiatives providing temporary work and accommodation as a bridge back into mainstream society. These include a city-wide bike share scheme and a social business selling photos that leverage the unique perspectives of those who live on the streets. Follow a unique enterprise striving towards a society that offers everyone a second chance.</content>
    <description>Kawaguchi Kana is the founder of an Osaka-based NPO working with the city's homeless to help them get back on their feet. Follow a unique enterprise striving towards a second-chance society.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/G8VkzTRQ#WFJPX_RCbhanxn9A6JLdxA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T02:00:26.138Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>e1b3489229bce1137093f9d6798390c17f9af079f287f528da591dfc7c57a270</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Second-Chance Society: Social Entrepreneur - Kawaguchi Kana</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T18:03:10.756Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/vBsU3Iqb#SWHCaVk1W03TO34wVsXLzA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>099</airingId>
    <content>In March 2020, to curb the spread of COVID-19, schools across Japan were urged to close, prompting widespread fears that children may fall behind on their studies. Enter Yunokawa Takahiko, developer of a unique e-learning platform that uses AI to assess students' shortcomings and provide an adaptive learning experience to match. Having rolled out to almost 370 schools during the pandemic, Yunokawa aims to provide affordable, egalitarian learning opportunities to students in Japan and overseas.</content>
    <description>In March 2020, COVID-19 forced schools across Japan to close. Yunokawa Takahiko helped to fill the gap with e-learning materials that use AI to provide an adaptive, accessible educational experience.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fwdR1ArK#pzSjZRyJ1Pq7kTobfx3HdA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T02:00:33.047Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T01:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>91a5a7c228a7ad5c603a56c9c4bdf17d15ae20097a1edffdad2d567a85b0e4f4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>AI - Leveling the Educational Playing Field: E-Learning Innovator - Yunokawa Takahiko</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-27T07:36:12.024Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WAlyTa7A#ofSl7U1Y-LIYR8NhrGegbg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>105</airingId>
    <content>Throughout the COVID-19 pandemic, Japan has placed great emphasis on avoiding the Three Cs: closed spaces, crowding and close contact. Kawano Takanobu runs a business that aims to bring peace of mind through digital systems that allow users to avoid such conditions and curb the risk of infection. Rolled out in restaurants, restrooms, hotels and more, his solutions leverage AI, IoT and sensor technology to help people cope with the new normal.</content>
    <description>Against the backdrop of COVID-19, Kawano Takanobu runs a venture that offers peace of mind through digital solutions leveraging AI, IoT, and sensor technology to help users curb the risk of infection.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fJEnFIoQ#gAu7jqOMmUOgsBnEtcWFFw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T02:00:29.421Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-19T01:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b4a6caba9747071f7f689985dbcc451075f8e9fd6ac198e6499ad6a6eb8794a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-19T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fighting Infection by Controlling the Three Cs: Systems Innovator - Kawano Takanobu</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T17:44:47.288Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MwcznKrB#LPZnbzZ_3VHZBNWx0fUq0Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>106</airingId>
    <content>Follow a pioneering Kyoto-based firm that boosts producers across Japan by canning local specialty foods. Under the motto "bringing a brighter future through canned goods," the business, led by former IT engineer Inoue Kazuma, eschews additives to deliver the natural flavor of primary ingredients. From game and seafood, to premium vegetables and other rare and unique delicacies, this unique business fields 20-30 inquiries a month from producers eager to reach a wider audience.</content>
    <description>Follow a unique Kyoto-based firm that boosts Japan's food producers by canning local specialty goods, from game, to seafood, to premium vegetables and other rare and unique delicacies.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-10T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/JdR3AKgQ#RDJCsxbRy_jb31ctOxQ6CA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-10T02:00:30.052Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-10T01:29:20.064Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>df664c6a1a3345e112622db3867da30d1f0fde8bcf8bf012f1f2fa609e05598d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-10T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bringing a "Can-Do" Spirit to Specialty Produce: Preserved Food Pioneer - Inoue Kazuma</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T17:46:08.202Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YQ9Q3Jab#S3xX9aRTYOd04JBkuFyJDg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>107</airingId>
    <content>COVID-19 has hit restaurants hard. Faced with steady running costs despite low sales, some are turning to kitchen cars as a solution. Ishizawa Masayoshi runs a service uniting some 900 independent food truck operators. For a small commission, he matches them with unused patches at office buildings, switching up the selection to give local workers a constantly changing choice of exotic lunch options. As the pandemic runs on, coverage has also expanded to residential areas and medical facilities.</content>
    <description>COVID-19 has put mobile dining options in the spotlight. Follow a service helping food truck operators by matching them with patches at office buildings, residential areas, and medical facilities.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hxdxXCZS#GbsWqD-EAGMceWHmKUlh-Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T02:00:30.217Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T01:29:24.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2042</seriesId>
    <sha256>8766d694f3660358b03309d5a9d9e6bbb5089d6f9bb56b606e20baa7600ecf21</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Food Trucking the Blues Away: Mobile Dining Innovator - Ishizawa Masayoshi</subtitle>
    <title>RISING</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T08:03:44.155Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0sNlXA6b#dQ8komILwws0SvQhZnIOgQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>