<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-11T17:25:03.637Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>56ef83def0753222</seriesId>
  <title>NHK Documentary</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>074</airingId>
    <content>The assassination of US President John F. Kennedy is still shrouded in mystery. With the help of top experts, NHK takes a new look at the incident through reenactments and fresh theories on the case.
Lee Harvey Oswald, the man who killed JFK, was once a US Marine stationed in Atsugi, Japan who later defected to the Soviet Union. While his own upbringing played a role in his decisions, there is also a possibility that a certain organization was manipulating him behind the scenes. The testimony of Oswald's wife, Marina, also reveals a failed assassination attempt by Oswald in the months leading up to Kennedy's death. We follow the little-known footprints left by this infamous assassin.</content>
    <description>The assassination of US President John F. Kennedy is still shrouded in mystery. With the help of top experts, NHK takes a new look at the incident through reenactments and fresh theories on the case.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T20:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/K0UjRCaQ#XB0ilzWbndZu__PXMWYlUw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T20:50:27.508Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-14T19:59:20.093Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>7294b5998c5ba8f6de51b063aeb734e53f72cd5e35ecd14295ea8ed3e00501d2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-14T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Oswald and JFK UNSOLVED CASES Part 1: The Pawn</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:42:24.341Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cRUkCDza#PUPmr40TPXZGY8XDd9uf7Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>075</airingId>
    <content>6 months before JFK was killed, Lee Harvey Oswald attempted a separate assassination. Our coverage reveals the possibility that this attempt served as a focal point that linked Oswald to the JFK killing. The day of that killing, Oswald brought a rifle into a Dallas building. The US government report says 3 shots from that building killed JFK, but we take a new look at witness testimony and speak to 66 prominent campaigners to ask: was the assassination really the work of a "lone wolf"?</content>
    <description>The assassination of US President John F. Kennedy is still shrouded in mystery. With the help of top experts, NHK takes a new look at the incident through reenactments and fresh theories on the case.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rBMWDZ5b#5t_vNSN41Oe8YYZs1jI5-Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T16:01:12.558Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T15:09:22.752Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3016</seriesId>
    <sha256>1531f9c5881dd160093a8b7bf5b8c888d6413f49585ff9f87025f0c26b9fc950</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Oswald and JFK UNSOLVED CASES Part 2: The Chessmaster</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T23:55:38.067Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tFYE1BbZ#rfxKNrVZ4RL-PlTK0gvXGA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>119</airingId>
    <content>Successive meltdowns of reactors at the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Plant resulted in significant nuclear contamination. How did the disaster unfold? NHK interviewed more than 400 people and conducted simulations based on volumes of data. Our independent investigation sheds new light on the accident 2 years after it occurred.</content>
    <description>Hard-hitting documentary that takes an in-depth look at some of the political, economic, and social challenges that Japan is facing. Today: Meltdown: Oversights in the reactor cooling system.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tVoEzBiA#J58abiMxeYbHpBTAFdSJxQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-13T00:00:23.160Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-12T23:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>f2fdb99219a4062a8ae7add41a74f434429570f4e3a8a4e0eeb1ccdb10a03958</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-12T23:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Meltdown: Oversights in the Reactor Cooling System</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-13T12:22:56.319Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/CxIyDZAC#lqF2z_RBH_Z5VMRxXsBMsA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>232</airingId>
    <content>"Hello. If you're out there, please listen to me." On a hill overlooking the ocean in Otsuchi Town in northeastern Japan is a phone booth known as the "Telephone of the Wind." It is connected to nowhere, but people come to "call" family members lost during the tsunami of the 2011 Great East Japan Earthquake. Many visit the phone booth including a mother and 3 children who have lost their father. This documentary looks at the unique role that this phone is playing in helping the grieving process of many.</content>
    <description>On a hill near the ocean is a telephone booth known as the "Telephone of the Wind". It is connected to nowhere, but people come to whisper messages to family members lost in the 2011 tsunami.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-06T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/T850HDhS#j97C3JwJJNcaazlwL87oEg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-06T16:00:29.723Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-06T15:09:22.408Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>e024f687cad249854256b34baca1d7f4c91c04b2cbe84d1e6d966890f71e626e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-06T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Phone of the Wind: Whispers to Lost Families</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-06T17:31:34.612Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/RagwQDKb#ED54qj0PoNCQ0MbK0S6cSw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>329</airingId>
    <content>Scientists are discovering what's behind the strong bonds that can form between dogs and humans. And few bonds are stronger than those between therapy dogs and the patients they care for. Bailey was the first resident therapy dog to work in a large Japanese hospital. Over his 9-year career, he's cared for thousands of children, comforting them as they face intractable diseases. The dedicated therapy dog is now ready to retire. But first he must help a young girl named Yui deal with a life-threatening illness.</content>
    <description>Therapy dog Bailey has been comforting sick children for 9 years. Now on the verge of retirement, he's dedicating himself to caring for Yui, a young girl with a life-threatening illness.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-20T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IbwkmC6Y#NuNtzpuoEc_KCwcTDCgzlA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-20T16:00:29.293Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-20T15:09:22.665Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>d89497f278e98f01105e32ece90dc16e11843ffaf6fa86710190fb5a3fd8c2ef</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-20T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yui and Bailey the Therapy Dog</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-20T18:16:28.784Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4D4VQK4B#6fl6tJBWBJoEU3LuxSok8A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>342</airingId>
    <content>In September 2018, an unprecedented large-scale blackout wreaked havoc on Japan's northern island of Hokkaido Prefecture following an earthquake. Over the 45 hours it took to resolve, its impact was felt right across society in ways previously assumed unimaginable. A similar prolonged blackout in the Greater Tokyo metropolitan area could have even more devastating effects. We investigate what might happen if Japan's capital were ever struck by such a crisis and reveal the preparations now being made.</content>
    <description>In 2018 an extended blackout wreaked havoc on Japan's northern island of Hokkaido. We investigate what might happen if Tokyo were ever hit by such a crisis and look at the preparations now being made.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-03T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7pxEVYhY#hXjlW13ByWnPPKyrF2vPEw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-03T16:00:27.585Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-03T15:09:20.080Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>39ca7f2d274ac63a3f7bf2a7001158c847c8a55bf762e5ed06361c8a3b48c082</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-03T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Great Metropolitan Blackout: Preparing for Crisis</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-03T19:18:01.942Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/eNp0yBDL#ndBDcvgWHkg8W-BFAOPDxw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>343</airingId>
    <content>Many Japanese businesses are experiencing "lonely deaths," closing their doors with little fanfare or preparation. Over 300,000 businesses could shut down this coming year, leaving behind mountains of debt and further weakening regional economies already affected by dwindling populations. Now a new breed of management consultants is using big data to analyze what's behind this rash of business closures, and to reduce their impact.</content>
    <description>Many companies in Japan experience "lonely deaths," closing down and weakening regions already affected by shrinking populations. Now such companies are getting help from a new breed of consultants.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-27T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1pZzxaoK#PGAjp78_lFm5rP4aKTQXyw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-27T16:00:22.507Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-27T15:09:20.122Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>855adfd39b1d6a17feea8f05bc1fc0fbbe2c5e7e457c1ba83915e923e565d319</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-27T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>"Death Doulas" for Businesses: End-of-Life Care for Dying Companies</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-28T04:30:44.839Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/u4BXWawR#_XMUi2YrslSNhvkWQMIH6w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>352</airingId>
    <content>The tsunami that struck northeast Japan in March 2011 was among the largest in Japanese history. But it didn't correlate with the intensity of the preceding earthquake. How did the wave get to be so astonishingly big? We investigate a little-known seabed phenomenon that may have contributed. It seems that if a landslide and slow-motion plate shifting occur at the same time, they can cause a tsunami of an enormous size. 9 years after the disaster, a true picture of what happened is beginning to emerge.</content>
    <description>The 2011 tsunami was among the largest in Japanese history, but it didn't correlate with the intensity of the preceding earthquake. To find out why, we investigate a little-known phenomenon.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-13T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/yBJETDzT#50DxsMLJOCulaO9B9hjQ8g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-13T16:00:28.236Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-13T15:09:22.754Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>604918489f48b1fb609af35d5eb1f6f31983b05994a932de00b6d2afbf131f69</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-13T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Mystery of the 40-Meter Tsunami: The Great East Japan Disaster</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T11:59:14.453Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/etcgmZhI#3o57nJbm74uP-jmT0PyalQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>361</airingId>
    <content>Hokkaido Prefecture's Shiretoko Peninsula is a UNESCO World Natural Heritage site. The area includes one of the world's densest concentrations of wild brown bears. 84-year-old fisherman Ose Hatsusaburo has forged a remarkable relationship with these creatures over a lifetime of working among them. Bears obey his commands without a fuss, and no fisherman has suffered a bear attack in 50 years. A rapidly shifting climate and recent UNESCO directives mean this unique way of life now faces an uncertain future.</content>
    <description>Hokkaido's Shiretoko Peninsula is home to some 500 brown bears. 84-year-old fisherman Ose Hatsusaburo has built a remarkable relationship with the creatures, one that now faces an uncertain future.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-09T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rYdDTI7K#SZJzV0Zk1HBhcez8PT3_jQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-09T16:01:02.355Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-09T15:09:22.824Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>6c1d4fdd1ab4e5fca06b9a2ee53d0b435c033b95a84b061ebe9aaa6971f7a7e0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-09T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bearman of Hokkaido</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T16:29:44.817Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/L8s2gKYS#KAsS1iml_XAEDY_6_Op5nA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>375</airingId>
    <content>Watanabe Shinji is a teacher known among students for his passionate teaching style. For the past year, he's been pursuing one particular challenging topic: bullying. Always in the back of his mind, is the memory of a boy who eventually took his own life, after being repeatedly tormented by his peers. This is a record of the year-long struggle by a teacher and his students to create a class completely free from bullying.</content>
    <description>Watanabe Shinji is a teacher passionately dedicated to tackling the sensitive issue of bullying. We follow a year-long struggle by him and his students to create a class completely free from bullying.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-23T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vi4jhSYL#D0QAJhkKH3LqXV0Dv82ueg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-23T16:00:28.835Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-23T15:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>4fce5d6cc883360d32f562465df1abf092f01530b6942626e625615ba94e7ce4</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-23T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Leaving No One Behind</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-23T17:54:40.840Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/r2xFGKaC#zgNliGklkdH4JEXaEnJa_Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>377</airingId>
    <content>The COVID-19 pandemic is changing our lives in many ways, including how we work. Many white-collar jobs can now be done remotely, from anywhere with an internet connection. Meanwhile, "essential" workers, including nurses, risk their lives on the frontlines, often under miserable conditions and for low pay. Many hospitals are struggling to pay the bills. The pandemic has forced us to ask: "What jobs are truly important and how should they be compensated?" We look at 2 very different kinds of work in a search for answers.</content>
    <description>Which jobs are important and how should they be compensated? That's a question the COVD-19 pandemic has raised. In this program, we look at two very different kinds of work in a search for answers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VRZlFIhD#1UlnsW7CLg4DrJkrIR_7GQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T10:00:26.482Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T09:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>773696a2f1e50f1ad0628381650a77bb5cd697050dd9c7a158f51e888fbf653d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T09:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19 Pandemic: Transforming the Way We Work</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:08:30.544Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MoMwgJjT#HH0fO7et4-_VLrpyaAL7uA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>378</airingId>
    <content>In the series Tokyo Miracle City, we unravel the secrets behind some of the capital's most intriguing wonders. In this fourth episode, we focus on Tokyo's "shinise" or long-established businesses. Tokyo is home to more than 3,000 shops and businesses with over a century of history. In the 20th century, Tokyo was razed to the ground twice, first by natural disaster, then by war, yet countless businesses found the resilience to rebuild and survive amid destruction and hardship. Actor Sato Takeru takes us on a tour of artisanal businesses keeping alive unique, age-old traditions, as he explores the roots of their longevity.</content>
    <description>In the series Tokyo Miracle City, we unravel the secrets behind some of the capital's most intriguing wonders. In this fourth episode, we focus on Tokyo's "shinise" or long-established businesses.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3oN1UCya#q0vVHzNH3jnvo7NoKz3aiQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-22T10:00:24.006Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T09:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>2ab2eabbc68a7050a1b1e70359cc9962df31b55accf1a66772588be981cd4707</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T09:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo Miracle City: Shinise - Tokyo's Time-Honored Businesses</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:55:44.625Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yAtQnSQS#HsazXub8lB_d5DWtppj18A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>379</airingId>
    <content>On June 30, 2020, China's top legislature passed a new national security law for Hong Kong with far-reaching implications for residents of the territory. The new law came after more than a year of protests that at times saw the city rocked by scenes of violence and destruction. While some believe the law has helped bring Hong Kong back from the brink, many others are now afraid to even voice their views for fear of prosecution. In a city increasingly divided along political lines, we hear both the hopes and fears of Hongkongers caught up in these unprecedented times.</content>
    <description>At the end of June, China's top legislature passed a new national security law for Hong Kong with far-reaching implications. We hear both the hopes and fears of residents in these unprecedented times.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8ZljwIrJ#29r7MKPa25t-k4nY3fC0GQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T22:00:20.192Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T21:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>dc8d58bffe3c88984618adcd41b789dfcd0f91d067a0fd3e5931068c9ace1a6a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T21:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hong Kong in Turmoil: A Crisis of Identity</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:59:27.728Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/2h8xgI4I#y8x9XKZyjDVLyAzocB8vcA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>380</airingId>
    <content>Mysterious notes were unearthed near the ruins of the crematoriums at the Auschwitz concentration camp, the site of the mass extermination of Jews during World War II. Deciphered using cutting-edge digital technology, it was discovered the notes were written by Jews who were part of a special unit called the Sonderkommando, which assisted the Nazis in guiding fellow Jews to the gas chambers and cremating their corpses. These prisoners were deemed "traitors" amidst the shadows of the largest mass extermination program in human history. What took place within the inferno? More than 7 decades later, this disturbing, tragic reality is brought to light.</content>
    <description>Mysterious notes were unearthed at the Auschwitz concentration camp, site of the mass extermination of Jews. They were written by Jews who cremated fellow believers. What did they see in the inferno?</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Dc8TBYwQ#daJGCC8tFJhrdoWfn6afAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T16:00:28.001Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T15:09:22.533Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>36c25257238c45fc91496b6b0a5fc320c065c77e7ca6e0d5ef833f98b918afff</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Inferno: Letters from Auschwitz</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:39:05.543Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6JtxSa7b#ckBUwX3lmpd3HfhpsR2M7g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>381</airingId>
    <content>How do you know if what you're reading is true or just a carefully crafted lie? Increasingly, social media exposes us to a flood of information, much of which aims to persuade us to believe things that are false. It can even encourage acts of violence. Fake images are being used in applications ranging from politics to pornography. And they're threatening our ability to tell fact from fiction. How can we stem the tide of bogus information? Or is it already too late?</content>
    <description>Social media exposes us to a flood of disinformation in areas ranging from politics to pornography. How can we tell fact from fiction? Can we stem the tide of fake news? Or is it already too late?</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T15:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5p8gCQaZ#hOcqubfl6sb3-WpONyTFkQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T15:55:28.395Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T15:09:22.860Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>258857ab3ef5cf1682ed49f0720661d3a5cf4cfa099e7e42c68ccc7c7b772d39</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Digital vs. Real: Infodemic - The Onslaught of Fake News</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T00:14:56.447Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/r1dVlS6A#pF0B71BOkm8kIPJuaNGJsQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>382</airingId>
    <content>Every day, people willingly surrender their personal data in pursuit of entertainment or convenience. This information is stored in giant repositories, then used to track our movements, sell us products and determine our future. Technology now allows the creation of "digital twins," virtual copies of our real selves based on our search histories and online habits. But what are the human and social costs of these innovations? Will they bring us more freedom and opportunity? Or will they lead to increased loss of individual liberty? We explore the ongoing conflict between digital convenience and personal privacy.</content>
    <description>Every day, people willingly surrender their personal data. It can be used to create "digital twins," virtual copies of our real selves. What happens when our private lives are no longer private?</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-02T15:57:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LhFwmbiL#VQIeErhgjZGt9Tw3oJo3lg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-02T15:57:27.499Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-02T15:09:22.846Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>767755517b6c5fe6b93578980865edabc034384c226315e68e07d5c3c607000f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-02T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Digital vs. Real: Digital Twin - The End of Privacy?</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T11:53:08.881Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IJxHxSAa#4am-3968piUHf3fu4jWx4Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>383</airingId>
    <content>It's estimated over a million Japanese live as "hikikomori," recluses totally withdrawn from society. Some hikikomori may even go for decades without leaving their house. While in the past the phenomenon was most commonly associated with young men, recent data has revealed a much wider demographic of people whose confidence in themselves, and in society, has been shattered. As the parents or relatives hikikomori so often depend on entirely become too old to care for them, many now face a dire situation, left alone and unable to cope.</content>
    <description>It's estimated over a million Japanese live as "hikikomori," recluses totally withdrawn from society. As the parents they depend on age, many now face a dire situation, left alone and unable to cope.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-16T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IYBVnA4Y#KGiyL-lngsyENP1gtpmo6A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-16T16:00:27.790Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-16T15:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>f659755e2c186b1cd376f0de7b24bef97dea4bb8ee6ac63e1b787e15c75132d7</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-16T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dying Out of Sight: Hikikomori in an Aging Japan</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T08:57:06.891Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/nAlR3CQY#Uc_tkFhupu0HrqBKfIQ1Gw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>384</airingId>
    <content>Ever since the COVID-19 pandemic first hit Japan, the far-reaching economic fallout has disproportionately impacted women's livelihoods. More than twice as many women have lost work, or seen their incomes slashed, compared to men. In an era where women are now often key breadwinners for their families, the repercussions have created a dire situation for households across the country. We explore what lies behind stark demographic discrepancies between men's and women's employment, and report first-hand on the bitter struggles of those whose voices all too often go unheard.</content>
    <description>The pandemic's far-reaching economic fallout has disproportionately hit women's livelihoods, with more than twice as many losing work as men. We hear from families struggling with the repercussions.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-30T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/u2xggYhS#vFNKd34gjgGBjk_X_ywkkQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-30T16:00:29.264Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-30T15:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>3216b9a1cbaa5140daf0413b47b2c80b594c9a8300bce96d7ec592d39a5855da</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-30T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Women's Livelihoods in Crisis: Bearing the Brunt of the Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-31T09:14:50.401Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W6oSGLIY#uFm6_cGOCpLgpw_GozCvuw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>385</airingId>
    <content>How far will COVID-19 spread before it subsides? An artificial intelligence system developed by NHK analyzed more than 200,000 scholarly articles to answer some pressing questions: how many more people will get infected this winter, why does the number of deaths differ from country to country, when will the pandemic begin to slow down, and what is the key to stopping this deadly disease? Learn some of the most effective ways to fend off the virus and hasten our return to normal life.</content>
    <description>Recent COVID-19 research debunks the myth that it's not much worse than a cold and underscores the power of masks. Learn some effective ways to fend off the virus and hasten a return to normal life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-06T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/v0syyICJ#EvcrWfEK49yioPUuRIOUyA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-06T16:00:26.704Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-06T15:09:23.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>642a0212304a5ae900f2ef0f00370e6fa6fdacbb62b47195a7b1fbd9bb589f78</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-06T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19: AI Decodes the Research</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T23:44:01.921Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/RMhC0IBS#QmeUM0gHk9fJZ43CbURoFw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>386</airingId>
    <content>How far can a human go to adapt? Tatyana McFadden of the United States is a wheelchair athlete who was born paralyzed from the waist down. She is already a legendary figure in para track and field who has won major events at all distances. In order to understand the secrets of her almost superhuman dominance, we did a scientific analysis of her body. What gives her speed in her wheelchair is not just raw strength, but also her exceptional command of her arms. She has this power because of remarkable adaptations within her body. To explore this further, we went to Russia, where McFadden spent her early childhood, and discovered that the first years of her life were unimaginably harsh. Born without certain physical abilities, she adapted ... and a "miracle body" was born. At the difficult time with the coronavirus, we offer this story about the wondrous potential of the human body to overcome seemingly impossible odds.</content>
    <description>Tatyana McFadden is a Paralympian who has won multiple gold medals competing in marathons and more. We see how her brain rewired itself to achieve such feats in a phenomenon called hyper-adaptability.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-15T20:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/n0glEK4K#t-qumTbGSC3q1Jg06KuJ9w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-15T20:50:26.378Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-15T19:59:22.400Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>5a2eb614c0df8f29748d8852e5216a00c5dd6abdfe9b9330765db8252b44d23f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-15T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miracle Body: Breaking Limits with Hyper-Adaptability</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-16T00:02:11.484Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/w1UTEATI#VnTWS9iQBXlJG_JL0DmL_Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>387</airingId>
    <content>Musical polymath Tsuneta Daiki is the mastermind behind chart-topping Japanese rock group King Gnu, and now also heads a boundary-pushing artist collective called "millennium parade." In an exclusive first, we were given full access to witness his intense creative process up close for a whole 3 months, tracking the progress and development of a special track entitled "2992" that boldly juxtaposes sonic genres. As Tsuneta over and again applies his ruthless process of destruction and creation in pursuit of his musical vision, our cameras are there to capture every step of the way.</content>
    <description>Musical polymath Tsuneta Daiki is mastermind behind chart-topping Japanese rock group King Gnu, and also heads a boundary-pushing artist collective. We witness his intense creative process up close.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-27T15:54:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/v950RRKb#Czx6iUy3rhaKdaXV-mwf1w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-27T15:54:28.792Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-27T15:09:22.773Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>8da62a5f0172032f3f254b2664380a68f73fb07b038571145721f31432cd3873</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-27T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tsuneta Daiki: Creation through Destruction</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-27T18:17:38.237Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3whxTCxB#NdTrQ75bv69Jt_AhKgixwg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>388</airingId>
    <content>In the series "2030" we tackle the challenges facing humanity over the next decade. We start with the pivotal issue of climate change, exploring what it will take to rein in our current trajectory as we hurtle toward a point of no return. Today we're seeing historic storms, floods and wildfires of increasing frequency and intensity. Climate change has entered a new phase, calling into question the very long-term survival of the human race. Drawing on the latest in climate modeling, we confront the bleak future that could be awaiting us and set out humankind's stark choice of paths to 2030.</content>
    <description>In the series "2030" we tackle the challenges facing humanity over the next decade. We start with the pivotal issue of climate change, exploring what it might take to avoid a disastrous tipping point.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-20T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0oozECyT#pJwx0puLclGyX5bin2KW5Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-20T16:00:27.062Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-20T15:09:20.108Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>eaacfd814daf0a725f71aa0be9236399c1308acf196b8446a0d9e0ad47d2da67</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-20T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>2030 At a Crossroads to the Future: Climate in Crisis - Realizing a Net Zero World</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-30T07:07:16.815Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3pNjxKJC#TGKF2FNLSwfCdBRCiqY7jg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>389</airingId>
    <content>In this two-part investigative report, NHK delves into scientific data and social media posts in search of clues to the origins of the new coronavirus. Part 1 looks at when and where the virus began spreading. Our team explores the possibility that human-to-human transmission started much earlier than believed.</content>
    <description>In this two-part investigative report, NHK delves into scientific data and social media posts in search of clues to the origins of the new coronavirus.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-10T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vJQgQDCR#QACMkEXPvfB4pDqvFOH3BA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-10T16:00:27.570Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-10T15:09:20.113Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>5681c77682fcdcf48d9a7b86322843be179084a7375b7ca2c15724ab4ff29d54</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-10T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Origins of the Pandemic: Part 1 The Beginning</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-11T01:23:46.697Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/8toRwSZQ#GpsODMtxX4IQGvinQwGc_Q</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>