<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-28T22:05:03.425Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>56ef83def0753222</seriesId>
  <title>NHK Documentary</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>377</airingId>
    <content>The COVID-19 pandemic is changing our lives in many ways, including how we work. Many white-collar jobs can now be done remotely, from anywhere with an internet connection. Meanwhile, "essential" workers, including nurses, risk their lives on the frontlines, often under miserable conditions and for low pay. Many hospitals are struggling to pay the bills. The pandemic has forced us to ask: "What jobs are truly important and how should they be compensated?" We look at 2 very different kinds of work in a search for answers.</content>
    <description>Which jobs are important and how should they be compensated? That's a question the COVD-19 pandemic has raised. In this program, we look at two very different kinds of work in a search for answers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T10:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VRZlFIhD#1UlnsW7CLg4DrJkrIR_7GQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T10:00:26.482Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T09:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>773696a2f1e50f1ad0628381650a77bb5cd697050dd9c7a158f51e888fbf653d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T09:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>COVID-19 Pandemic: Transforming the Way We Work</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T20:08:30.544Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MoMwgJjT#HH0fO7et4-_VLrpyaAL7uA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>378</airingId>
    <content>In the series Tokyo Miracle City, we unravel the secrets behind some of the capital's most intriguing wonders. In this fourth episode, we focus on Tokyo's "shinise" or long-established businesses. Tokyo is home to more than 3,000 shops and businesses with over a century of history. In the 20th century, Tokyo was razed to the ground twice, first by natural disaster, then by war, yet countless businesses found the resilience to rebuild and survive amid destruction and hardship. Actor Sato Takeru takes us on a tour of artisanal businesses keeping alive unique, age-old traditions, as he explores the roots of their longevity.</content>
    <description>In the series Tokyo Miracle City, we unravel the secrets behind some of the capital's most intriguing wonders. In this fourth episode, we focus on Tokyo's "shinise" or long-established businesses.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-22T10:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3oN1UCya#q0vVHzNH3jnvo7NoKz3aiQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-22T10:00:24.006Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T09:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>2ab2eabbc68a7050a1b1e70359cc9962df31b55accf1a66772588be981cd4707</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T09:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokyo Miracle City: Shinise - Tokyo's Time-Honored Businesses</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:55:44.625Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yAtQnSQS#HsazXub8lB_d5DWtppj18A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>379</airingId>
    <content>On June 30, 2020, China's top legislature passed a new national security law for Hong Kong with far-reaching implications for residents of the territory. The new law came after more than a year of protests that at times saw the city rocked by scenes of violence and destruction. While some believe the law has helped bring Hong Kong back from the brink, many others are now afraid to even voice their views for fear of prosecution. In a city increasingly divided along political lines, we hear both the hopes and fears of Hongkongers caught up in these unprecedented times.</content>
    <description>At the end of June, China's top legislature passed a new national security law for Hong Kong with far-reaching implications. We hear both the hopes and fears of residents in these unprecedented times.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8ZljwIrJ#29r7MKPa25t-k4nY3fC0GQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T22:00:20.192Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T21:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>dc8d58bffe3c88984618adcd41b789dfcd0f91d067a0fd3e5931068c9ace1a6a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T21:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hong Kong in Turmoil: A Crisis of Identity</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:59:27.728Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/2h8xgI4I#y8x9XKZyjDVLyAzocB8vcA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>380</airingId>
    <content>Mysterious notes were unearthed near the ruins of the crematoriums at the Auschwitz concentration camp, the site of the mass extermination of Jews during World War II. Deciphered using cutting-edge digital technology, it was discovered the notes were written by Jews who were part of a special unit called the Sonderkommando, which assisted the Nazis in guiding fellow Jews to the gas chambers and cremating their corpses. These prisoners were deemed "traitors" amidst the shadows of the largest mass extermination program in human history. What took place within the inferno? More than 7 decades later, this disturbing, tragic reality is brought to light.</content>
    <description>Mysterious notes were unearthed at the Auschwitz concentration camp, site of the mass extermination of Jews. They were written by Jews who cremated fellow believers. What did they see in the inferno?</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Dc8TBYwQ#daJGCC8tFJhrdoWfn6afAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T16:00:28.001Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T15:09:22.533Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4001</seriesId>
    <sha256>36c25257238c45fc91496b6b0a5fc320c065c77e7ca6e0d5ef833f98b918afff</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T15:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Inferno: Letters from Auschwitz</subtitle>
    <title>NHK Documentary</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T19:39:05.543Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>