<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-26T05:05:03.460Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>67d2ae7ac69fb919</seriesId>
  <title>Core Kyoto</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>080</airingId>
    <content>Sento, or bathhouses, were built in Kyoto to cater to the large student and artisan population who lived in lodgings without baths. Many are worthy of historic note. One has been operating for 1,300 years; another is part of a temple complex. Some have splendid decors or interesting baths. Today they remain lively social hubs of their communities. A young manager strives to create a Sento young people frequent. Discover the allure of Sento where people gather to relieve the stress of the day.</content>
    <description>Today: Public Baths where people gather to wash their troubles away. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IE1A0JRT#X9SZpP475tFooPs_SRUMiA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T15:00:30.801Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-23T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>724b4af06a5bdfbc12688647eee5a134a2d698b561e79ac627a1b6aa2fc70870</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-23T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Public Baths: People Gather to Wash Their Troubles Away</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T05:01:47.459Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>137</airingId>
    <content>Kyoto is dotted with Buddhist temples and Shinto shrines offering amulets for health, longevity, safety, easy childbirth and other blessings. An amulet warding off an epidemic centuries ago now eases Kyotoites' anxiety in the age of COVID-19. But amulets change with the times. A card that slips into a wallet and a microSD containing a Buddhist image for uploading to a mobile device keep the deities' spirits close by. Discover the charm of amulets through their history and their creation process.</content>
    <description>Today: Kyoto Amulets, the embodiment of prayers for happiness. The ancient capital continues to be innovative 1,200 years after its foundation. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ENlwjb4a#xFn1HDKfRqSrrNH6ZGIzkw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T00:00:32.448Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T23:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>a7a24898560c384f349f11b7a2ce9156389872436b1cf4a08450001b9cc21eed</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Amulets: The Embodiment of Prayers for Happiness</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:46:14.720Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jZdECT7I#VHWIFwxTedb8tR4iD_HO-w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>144</airingId>
    <content>Through novels and movies, the name Miyamoto Musashi has become synonymous with the word "samurai." The undefeated, 17th-century swordsman was also a master of calligraphy, the way of tea, and other arts. In his later years, he wrote "The Book of Five Rings" to relate the wisdom he gained through his duels. His teachings act a guide to living a significant life and remain seminal today during the pandemic. Discover Musashi's Kyoto through people who feel a deep affiliation with his way of life.</content>
    <description>Miyamoto Musashi, master of the sword and the arts, wrote his teachings 400 years ago. They act as a guide to living a significant life and remain seminal today, especially during the pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Ogt2xBAa#NXHQEB_iWp3gLO18jeqnqw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T00:00:23.702Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T23:29:21.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>22863a50f43b0544fe1b9132e639e9703b2c8be92de5a6ce1846039122a36fdc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miyamoto Musashi: Sword Mastery in the Ancient Capital</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T04:58:51.334Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>146</airingId>
    <content>Solid, durable and decorative, lacquer is a lustrous, natural polymer used in art, architecture, Buddhist statues, and everyday items. Kyoto was the seat of the emperor and aristocratic culture, so lacquerers always strove to out-dazzle each other and, in the process, refined their workmanship. Undeterred by difficulties they face from the pandemic, lacquerers today continue the art while searching for fresh ideas. Discover how they create the unconventional and innovative within the traditional.</content>
    <description>Solid, durable and decorative, lacquer is used in art, buildings, and everyday articles. Kyoto lacquerers strive to out-dazzle each other to create unconventional and innovative within the tradition.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3BdjiapC#L2yW58sPutoIiVh6LwrSkw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T00:00:25.846Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T23:29:23.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>b9845a688f7705fd79b5961c0618b044be8c976c450a2d0848eeb4eaa7a7f9de</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nouveau Lacquerware: Vibrant, Dazzling Beauty</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T04:53:28.963Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>