<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-24T04:10:03.609Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>67d2ae7ac69fb919</seriesId>
  <title>Core Kyoto</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>011</airingId>
    <content>In the 1200's, the monk Dogen brought Shojin-ryori, a vegetarian cuisine, from China along with Zen Buddhism, which forbids the killing of animals and the eating of meat. He once said, "Meals and their preparation are part of aesthetic training." Kaiseki-ryori and other Japanese cuisine have their base in and developed from Shojin-ryori, which wastes nothing of the seasonal vegetables and cereals used. Chefs, including a chef at a Michelin-rated restaurant, work to spread Shojin-ryori worldwide.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Shojin-ryori, Zen cuisine as training within the teachings.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-04T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/CZNnGQQZ#pMs7caG7v3WGa3EuXR8jew</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-04T15:00:35.811Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-04T14:29:20.126Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>65f32089e742b4946dd86af55c8cffa0ec5c800db659238cd6a7361203b18cec</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-04T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shojin-ryori: Zen Cuisine as Training within the Teachings</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T07:39:13.316Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/l9lBVabS#k3VrvcphA7jo0AsSv6zXvg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>A pointed boulder with a large stone at its foot reaches for the heavens. The white gravel between them represents a swift flowing river, without the use of water. Karesansui is a unique dry-gardening style that developed in the 14th century from ascetic practices at Kyoto's Zen temples. Monks aim for enlightenment within a world of rippling patterns that run between curious rock arrangements. Enter the infinite Zen cosmos through the Karesansui gardens at Tenryu-ji, Daisen-in and Ryoan-ji.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Karesansui, the Zen cosmos in a garden for spiritual training.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-16T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VZUWnZLA#Kn65KatxsBkzH6NMTf02EQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-16T15:00:28.791Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-16T14:29:20.117Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>903d2c929b464f3335ef71748c6fa112c98c3c3f5d2935f512ee7e1b1c2d8415</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-16T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Karesansui: The Zen Cosmos in a Garden for Spiritual Training</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T05:57:50.983Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/xc9V3KhZ#CHfqPedSZfuHX7QFKMVnig</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>Kyoto confections are Wagashi, or traditional confections, infused with Kyoto's charm and influenced by the tea ceremony. With beautiful designs and names that subtly reflect the seasons, tea confections are an art form to be appreciated with the 5 senses. When making these confections, importance is placed on the semblance and name they are given. Inspiration is drawn from local nature, art, music and literature. Feel Japan's culture, nature and climate through flavorsome Kyoto confections.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core. Today: Kyoto confections as experiencing Kyoto culture through the five senses.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-07T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QFRFXCaQ#TT42_ePVZzn5rl_E8QJnlQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-07T15:00:32.167Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-07T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>cfc54d74b8c88a3dd0c94b520560fc38e05fafd54493031bafc0a06d93d5a2f6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-07T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Confections: Experiencing Kyoto Culture through the Five Senses</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T14:51:12.246Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4xVH1QZJ#bjGovdIBDXeTK8TdeR6V8Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>027</airingId>
    <content>Filled with noble, graceful dignity, Kyoto dolls have long embodied people's prayers, relieved loneliness, and represented prayers for their children's growth. Connected to dynastic culture, these dolls evolved in the hands of talented Kyoto artisans. Edo-period craftsmen honed their doll-making skills, and these techniques are still practiced. Hina dolls reflect adoration for the nobility. Gosho dolls were adored at the palace. Find out how people's hearts are connected through Kyoto dolls.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Kyoto Dolls, adored by all, their grace brings peace.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-15T03:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2kU0lBqa#LKs2G6lwo5vzJUWMeP_-NA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-15T03:00:31.966Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-15T02:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>57d34411e2938e798db4d43bf810739fde77338708ee3a2fba5989f8e203f802</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-15T02:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Dolls: Adored by All, Their Grace Brings Peace</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T14:15:25.628Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oVcRTKAD#mGD9nAGOMkz9EnM_nftaWw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>028</airingId>
    <content>Kyoto is home to most Buddhist head temples, which shaped the ancient capital's historical landscape and fascinate visitors. Shichido-garan, the 7 most important buildings for Zen religious training, are positioned in the shape of a person. Maintaining temples for centuries, carpenters conduct major repairs at Chion-in and thatch Kiyomizu-dera's main-hall with cypress bark using traditional roofing methods. Look at the world of Buddhist architecture, sustained by craftsmanship and faith.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core. Today: Buddhist Architecture, craftsmanship unites places of worship.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3lk21BYZ#Gzfp7gfOfnkaw_jbSoUvqg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T15:01:06.494Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-21T14:29:22.611Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>593b21eccc4336886a7c327162540b8960fd620030f30f5499475c418995d8a2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-21T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Buddhist Architecture: Craftsmanship Unites Places of Worship</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T14:56:27.804Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/i5kVxKYK#IDgNV22fQQ9pugiBGx_lng</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>031</airingId>
    <content>Ogres, specters, demons, ghosts and hell. The ancient capital's many myths of the spirit world seem fantastic today. Kyoto's citizens lived in fear and awe of the other world and appealed to the deities for help. They honored milestones and kept the annual events in thanks to the deities for their protection. Consequences of the city's prosperity, the legends have origins in the deep in the recesses of the human mind, and the epidemics and wars that occurred throughout Kyoto's history.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core. Today: Legends of the spirit world that the mysterious inspires awe in the townsfolk.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/aVFBCQyL#oFaZ4yPZ0rWWonT4GC6q7Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T15:00:25.994Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-28T14:29:22.966Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>a044ead1cff902b6211e03da3883850ad98cb4accd60101728a9d1e102b17c2d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-28T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Legends of the Spirit World: The Mysterious Inspires Awe in the Townsfolk</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T07:18:54.395Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HttwUZqA#1ZqIONeVnOx49zlQwPXVAw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>040</airingId>
    <content>February 3 is New Year's Eve by the old, lunar calendar and is the boundary between winter and spring. On this day, called Setsubun, households scatter soybeans for good fortune in the coming year, expelling the demons that represent misfortune and calamity. The shrine Yoshida Jinja protects Kyoto at the "demon's gate" in the northeast with a ritual in which the "shaman" wears a four-eyed mask. Farmers in rural areas uphold the custom of driving out moles. Disguised Geiko pray for protection against evil. Discover how Kyotoites pray for order in life through these safeguarding traditions.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Setsubun, out with the demons and in with fortune in the spring.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-11T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/W04nQSrL#HeNDMl_4ScLirAOww_FZyQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-11T15:00:29.149Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-11T14:29:24.236Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>663b53c27cb0e2c40668d807bb44967ba11b33e8705a96f61ca5ffd00022b57f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-11T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Setsubun: Out with the Demons and in with Fortune in the Spring</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-12T04:33:56.619Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/q49lzKDD#NPHzpwPWeRRCNGa16Uj08w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>043</airingId>
    <content>After the first cafe opened in Kyoto in 1930, a coffee culture flourished as coffee salons enjoyed the patronage of local merchants, who prided themselves on staying abreast of the latest fashions. Kyotoites always placed the utmost importance on hospitality. Cafes may be relatively new to the cityscape, but they exude the local spirit of hospitality. Owners of distinct cafes find ingenious ways to infuse their service with this ethos. Discover the charm of Kyoto cafes while sipping on a brew.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Kyoto's Cafe Culture is a cup full of local hospitality.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-18T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OFcAhLSa#lAjh5nA9sywCbbo6Q-2t4w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-18T15:00:26.837Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-18T14:29:20.129Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>d3fd3007e57b313de231858f8867a15c46865df338f0cebbd99d249cf3fda54b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-18T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto's Cafe Culture: A Cup Full of Local Hospitality</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T01:49:20.468Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/QPZk2bCB#IQOfytCQmPPd-7lEMOqOkg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>044</airingId>
    <content>Kannon Bosatsu is warmly worshipped, a comfort for the heart. The subject of many paintings and statues, he saves people across Buddhist sects. The 11-faced Kannon faces each direction in search of people to save. The 1,000-armed Kannon holds objects used to relieve people's anguish. Kiyomizu-dera, where memorial services are held for him, attracts worshippers seeking salvation. Watch a sculptor carve a statue of Kannon. Discover the deep faith Kannon has drawn among Kyotoites over centuries.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Belief in Kannon, the God of Mercy redeems all.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-25T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9aYGhJgZ#tXqIVuH2tj9_W67OrKxrbg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-25T15:00:31.088Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-25T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>94e9512ed572c2bf8b886b8428bafea12e1808e7b1d2fe41b7c7ca3e82911db8</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-25T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Belief in Kannon: The God of Mercy Redeems All</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-25T16:05:38.386Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/mrh3gYgD#SJP74oY20GpH7WfNTsle_Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>050</airingId>
    <content>The ancient capital was devastated during a period of intense war lasting 2 centuries until the late 16th century, when Toyotomi Hideyoshi assumed supreme power. He envisioned rebuilding a city that would prosper through a free economy and a stable government. A rampart was built around Kyoto, and rezoning increased residential areas. Hideyoshi's palace of gold was a symbol of his glory, and he influenced the lavish Momoyama culture. Discover the traces of Hideyoshi's legacy in Kyoto, today.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core. Today: The Capital of Peace and Bliss, Kyoto streets still bear Hideyoshi's mark.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-01T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sqQXVKTJ#LbHWSS0EKDoOVIQlkCygmA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-01T15:00:30.715Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-01T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>f14ac3f1f12c7e65c281b7901d49da764443b745f2d4856ac80b493e3631f745</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-01T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Capital of Peace and Bliss: Kyoto Streets Still Bear Hideyoshi's Mark</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-01T16:06:27.247Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HJNX1S4a#Ttcl3WTPJ0QoJ5YkqpPCjA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>054</airingId>
    <content>Iwashimizu Hachiman-gu lies in the southwest of Kyoto Prefecture. On September 15, this shrine holds the Iwashimizu-sai. This some 1,000-year-old festival is held in prayer for the peace of all living things. In the darkness at 2 a.m., the mystical ritual begins with 3 mikoshi portable shrines, on which the deities ride, departing down the mountain. The scene is a living manifestation of ancient picture scrolls. Discover the Kyotoites' respect for life through this festival's rituals.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core. Today: Iwashimizu-sai, the ritual in the gloom in respect for all life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-08T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/F9xUkaaK#c4dlyt5yocUwgY2mWmoMFw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-08T15:00:29.118Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-08T14:29:20.124Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>d304ac991328553370e2b0492e4b57c8685dd13b22aaa193f547739624f5cced</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-08T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Iwashimizu-sai: The Ritual in the Gloom in Respect for All Life</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-09T06:20:17.495Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/09oQzRKL#qHFviVTNLT_qLr3HOZqFhw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>056</airingId>
    <content>Kyoto today is a bustling tourist destination, but there was a time when it had lost its sparkle. The emperor moved to Tokyo 120 years ago to forge a modern state, and many followed, depleting the population. This crisis shook the city's foundation, but it reinvented itself through modern public works and other initiatives. The Jidai Matsuri pays homage to the past with 2,000 people parading in period costumes. Discover the citizens' resilience as they redefined their city, creating a new Kyoto.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Kyoto's Rebirth, the ancient capital prospers anew.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-15T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/BQpnWI7I#kmntea_kTUo7ocLzi_-D2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-15T15:00:27.418Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-15T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>aae87fc81c3209a8b918684eef9b9103ce55cc922a7a4a75819138bac5d2acbe</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-15T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto's Rebirth: The Ancient Capital Prospers Anew</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T16:46:58.405Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JotjiSLY#Ij-AV4edcnOOErmLUO2KDw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>059</airingId>
    <content>Suiseki is the appreciation of natural stone shapes using poetic imagination to visualize magnificent mountain, island or waterfall landscapes. This pastime arrived from China in the late 1100s and spread among Kyoto aristocrats and Zen monks. Suiseki's beauty lies in the stones' understated simplicity and becalming quality. The Seven Stones of Kamo found in the Kamo River basin are prized in Suiseki circles. Discover the profound world of rock appreciation that evolved in the old capital.</content>
    <description>The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program. Today: Suiseki, a world of understated beauty within natural stone.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-22T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/5KxiWZyL#EZtRmCh5mEikEZkDl3OYOw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-22T15:00:30.415Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-22T14:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>dce791cc80be3a66a6df617548ab6165784c1a3fd9af9b945fe500f26560eb61</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-22T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Suiseki: A World of Understated Beauty within Natural Stone</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-22T15:48:23.535Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/X8x3wIZa#zrOxzzm5xC1qwI8kVyuvqw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>062</airingId>
    <content>The obi sash is an integral accessory for the kimono. One company has produced opulent Nishijin-ori obi for more than 120 years. A lady conveys the obi's allure through fitting classes. A dresser deftly ties the trailing obi of the Gion maiko. Fastened with a decorative cord, the obi is the final touch in a kimono ensemble. Its form manifests the obi's rich history and the sentiments of the people who produce or tie them. Discover the profound world hiding in a beautiful obi and its knot.</content>
    <description>Today: Obi, unbridled beauty in a knot. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-01T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/GwYmmJYS#wSafgGPv_8wwaBSDu5faqA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-01T15:00:29.840Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-01T14:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>ccc43f30f6688e9abc3901113a4bbff72832408e5c74952a4a6fe6ed61e91aa1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-01T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Obi: Unbridled Beauty in a Knot</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-01T16:05:03.058Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ZMd0zb4Q#eZb2Ybcx7eKdjBhQhhnPjA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>064</airingId>
    <content>Traditional woodblock prints in the ancient capital have a strong, distinct history. Their origins lie in the woodblock printing of Buddhist scriptures. Compared to the mass production of ukiyo-e prints that were popular with Edo (now Tokyo) residents, woodblock printers in Kyoto were more focused on quality over quantity, creating delicate, soft expressions of art with their honed skills. Discover the subtle, elaborate beauty through the expertise of the 3 artists involved in process.</content>
    <description>Today: Woodblock Prints, beauty in the hands of a trinity of artists. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-11T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/GFVyjRiB#cNfpY6ZvD1zMnBtrdmi2yA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-11T00:00:30.361Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-10T23:29:20.060Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>ade3a7b67844b154ed5580b7bc9c3ea6394987cdf10b6aa14272daee1040dfcd</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-10T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Woodblock Prints: Beauty in the Hands of a Trinity of Artists</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T15:28:14.695Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/rhpi1BQJ#sL32CwBxYeuo8xNK2yCY0w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>068</airingId>
    <content>The ancient capital's dignified air of yesteryear is in part generated by earthen walls: the walls of the imperial palace, shrines, temples and even private properties. Earthen walls imbue tea houses with a rustic air. Kyoto is blessed with soil of a color ideal for these walls. Plasterers over centuries developed and refined their technique to produce walls befitting a capital. Discover the aesthetic sensibilities and expertise of traditional plasterers as they pursue beauty in earthen walls.</content>
    <description>Today: Kyoto Walls, elegance molded from earth. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-15T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Tx9ASRSA#okdyCZ6YgLYAJtntnNBJxA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-15T15:00:27.028Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-15T14:29:20.121Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>36c257a62d153edbbe49d971b66c4f9466d96a228d8436b4ef8d947df97392a3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-15T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Walls: Elegance Molded from Earth</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T05:05:31.763Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/r8pXhKZQ#JkldIJDQWCqEWfrnc0AhIw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>077</airingId>
    <content>At 3 a.m. on October 22, 2 large pine torches over 10m long are lit to signal the start of the fire festival at Iwakura Jinja. Long ago, it was believed that demons were contained by a huge boulder in the area, after which both the shrine and the area are named. In the late 1100's the shrine was built and the deity was transferred there, but it returns to the boulder on the day of the festival. Discover this 500-year-old festival through the preparations of the residents of Iwakura.</content>
    <description>Today: Iwakura Fire Festival, the boulder's divine spirit returns. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-30T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/24kmhZIT#alWSljuHwpgupqnbEdvi5Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-30T15:00:30.794Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-30T14:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>df216dc7e3ef2f6dbb93e13fb338fd4150777ea7d57193f8505c18025040fc19</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-30T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Iwakura Fire Festival: The Divine Spirit Returns</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T05:16:44.681Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MFE1GKZA#yf73Cw3iybkpZlEYjb-7_g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>078</airingId>
    <content>Some 1,000 years ago, monks from warring Mt. Hiei and nobles from the capital retreated from the world in rustic Ohara, northeast of Kyoto. The monks perfected the practice of Shomyo, a melodic singing of Buddhist sutras, and in its heyday the village had as many as 50 practice halls. Ohara also was a sanctuary for nuns, and is known for the distinctively dressed local women called Oharame, who sold firewood in Kyoto. Discover the nature and history of Ohara through the deep faith at its heart.</content>
    <description>Today: Ohara, a mountain village echoing with Buddhist chants. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-22T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9kw2wJwZ#6sZGFNM7lza1RfzuqWBDgA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-22T15:00:28.906Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-22T14:29:20.133Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>d941d186928a79b49c619e2fef4b37af75dc1db4b9b1a9dd9b71ad23065469ca</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-22T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ohara: A Mountain Village Echoing with Buddhist Chants</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T06:09:00.540Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/z4sxDQzA#DqbIqldMAznWGO445P2DNg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>080</airingId>
    <content>Sento, or bathhouses, were built in Kyoto to cater to the large student and artisan population who lived in lodgings without baths. Many are worthy of historic note. One has been operating for 1,300 years; another is part of a temple complex. Some have splendid decors or interesting baths. Today they remain lively social hubs of their communities. A young manager strives to create a Sento young people frequent. Discover the allure of Sento where people gather to relieve the stress of the day.</content>
    <description>Today: Public Baths where people gather to wash their troubles away. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IE1A0JRT#X9SZpP475tFooPs_SRUMiA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T15:00:30.801Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-23T14:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>724b4af06a5bdfbc12688647eee5a134a2d698b561e79ac627a1b6aa2fc70870</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-23T14:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Public Baths: People Gather to Wash Their Troubles Away</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T05:01:47.459Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/E4URlABB#exg_flmwYQ3Jj6CB1XEVIg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>083</airingId>
    <content>Tofu arrived from China along with Buddhism over a millennium ago. It further evolved in Japan as an ingredient in Shojin-ryori vegetarian Zen cuisine and in time appeared on the tables of the common folk. The pursuit and refinement of tofu-making and its cooking in the ancient capital produced distinct varieties. The artisans curdle the mix of soybeans and water with bittern to give a taste that is profound in its simplicity and sophistication. Discover the food culture surrounding Kyoto Tofu.</content>
    <description>Today: Kyoto Tofu, a subtle taste nourished by skill and pride. The ancient capital, Kyoto Pref., continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-14T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/L9AACBqI#lZFs1T3LNmhbKdyDTCAKuw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-14T00:00:33.663Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-13T23:29:20.087Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>3cd1c55bf902f3db83f02e480559cc340252ec0b19242beca75ce39c0eee2e59</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-13T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Tofu: Subtle Taste Nourished by Skill and Pride</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-14T00:56:50.783Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/kLZQEb4J#Qw66nahpVQDx7_bxQMQ2ow</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>099</airingId>
    <content>Kyotoites in days of old valued high quality fabric and woven textiles from abroad like gold. Pieces of these fabrics have been handed down and continue to fascinate people today. Their eternal beauty is preserved through repurposing as tea utensil pouches, tobacco holders, obi sashes and even as works of art. Weavers strive to learn the techniques used in days gone by in order to reproduce them. Discover the culture of reverence for the great beauty and skill to be found in old fabric pieces.</content>
    <description>Today: Fabric pieces, honoring and caring for the past. The ancient capital, Kyoto, continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/96Q2CByB#MibazfzJwCalqgwnrZf7Hw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-28T00:00:32.332Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-27T23:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>e249efab5d0ce4c6d5320fa9595387011f1a0c4461f75b68cba4f0c17a7f67f3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-27T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fabric Pieces: Honoring the Past</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-28T00:47:36.646Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TzJ30aqD#0iaIJojs7frkcRD7YXjPuA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>108</airingId>
    <content>The "satoyama" style of living in harmony with nature, and the customs that influenced life in the ancient capital, survive in the mountains north of central Kyoto. An old inn in the town of Hanase continues to serve the local specialty, Tsumikusa (foraged wild foods) cuisine. Miyama is famous for its thatching tradition, and the local artisans use skills passed down for generations to re-thatch Kyoto's many temples and shrines. Discover the local customs that keep Kyoto's culture alive.</content>
    <description>Today: Satoyama Living, country customs that sustain the ancient capital. Kyoto continues to be innovative after 1,200 years. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T13:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/u5liRLCK#FGvxLHevBK3tYy0PDNzBPQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T13:00:34.278Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T12:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>e100135ace28b53713cbb11c39723e7ae156bf6c5e2763aa1bd23bbe5745ee85</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T12:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Satoyama Living: Country Customs Sustaining the Ancient Capital</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T05:17:56.812Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/AsN1zKRZ#QlVvuoNJmL9LWUIY0jz1_g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>137</airingId>
    <content>Kyoto is dotted with Buddhist temples and Shinto shrines offering amulets for health, longevity, safety, easy childbirth and other blessings. An amulet warding off an epidemic centuries ago now eases Kyotoites' anxiety in the age of COVID-19. But amulets change with the times. A card that slips into a wallet and a microSD containing a Buddhist image for uploading to a mobile device keep the deities' spirits close by. Discover the charm of amulets through their history and their creation process.</content>
    <description>Today: Kyoto Amulets, the embodiment of prayers for happiness. The ancient capital continues to be innovative 1,200 years after its foundation. We dive deep into its core in this definitive program.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ENlwjb4a#xFn1HDKfRqSrrNH6ZGIzkw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T00:00:32.448Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T23:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>a7a24898560c384f349f11b7a2ce9156389872436b1cf4a08450001b9cc21eed</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kyoto Amulets: The Embodiment of Prayers for Happiness</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T05:46:14.720Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jZdECT7I#VHWIFwxTedb8tR4iD_HO-w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>138</airingId>
    <content>Flames rising from behind, piercing eyes and an enraged expression, statues of Fudo Myo-o hold a sword and lasso, both ritual implements. Despite its formidable appearance, this deity has a wide following among devotees and common folk alike. The solid power it emits has attracted many people craving comfort during the coronavirus pandemic. Discover the faith and customs surrounding Fudo Myo-o, and the undertakings of a monk cum Buddhist sculptor who is captivated by this protective guardian.</content>
    <description>Fudo Myo-o has flames at his back and wears a wrathful expression. A monk cum Buddhist sculptor, who is enchanted by this protective guardian, finds ways to overcome in the time of the coronavirus.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-31T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8ps3zSCb#pSrw7KJ-k99dZRtbSe86Bg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-31T00:00:27.071Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-30T23:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>d47a81e1f45f5d1ffdf267d3feb1907a730031694eebc24f4736677b77189c87</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-30T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fudo Myo-o: The Enduring Power of a Wrathful Deity</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-31T10:04:33.943Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tt110AKC#wRel4dRFpYU2eH4oFzdgSA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>139</airingId>
    <content>As the traditional confectionery industry wanes due to a growing preference for Western-style sweets, the younger generation of confectioners are using modern sensibilities to attract consumers. Some use only organic ingredients. Others create dry confections with pop designs. A heritage confectioner delivers fresh sweets for people to enjoy the seasons at home. A cafe serves the unthinkable pairing of Kyoto confections with sake. Discover how these innovative approaches invigorate tradition.</content>
    <description>Confectioners are blowing new life into traditional Kyoto sweets: fusing Western and Japanese styles, pairing with cups of sake, and using ingredients that increase immunity in the time of corona.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-07T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/oRsRAY6a#QqtWROswOHVHvEOsUeoG-g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-07T00:00:32.730Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T23:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>ed60534768d97fcc3a4c3ccb54700fce81211c24b89c4ec317a1390eb280b574</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nouveau Confections: A Feast for the Eyes, Mouth, and Mind</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-07T00:48:49.612Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/G0swwCgR#l5YKPL_NH2Z49Gjun7c7Uw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>141</airingId>
    <content>From the late 1800s to the early 1900s, dominant political and business figures owned villas in neighborhoods at the foot of the Higashiyama mountains. Many of their gardens were built by the pioneer of the modern Japanese garden, Ogawa Jihei VII. While Kyoto's cityscape was transforming after the fall of feudalism, Jihei designed spaces of comfort in a desire to return Kyoto to its glory days of scenic beauty. Discover natural spaces of calculated beauty that offer solace during the pandemic.</content>
    <description>The pioneer of the modern garden, Ogawa Jihei VII revolutionized Kyoto gardens 100 years ago. He cleverly used water and rocks in his relaxing spaces, which continue to inspire landscapers today.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-04T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8sZRDIxA#FTMyUMRJBtGK_ogQY-7VlA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-04T00:00:33.583Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-03T23:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b060d062bf90fe81fd9035e530e6a6ffafca7c329682c5235c8bafe094a2f2f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-03T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ogawa Jihei Gardens: Beauty Soothes and Nourishes the Soul</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-04T01:20:48.455Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ggZ3xSDS#MZ6e93Z2uDNZoPx3SK946g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>142</airingId>
    <content>The five seasonal festivals to drive out evil originate in Yin and Yang philosophy. The most important is the Double Ninth festival on September 9, the largest, single-digit odd number. Chrysanthemums, a medicinal herb, are used for purification in the 1,000-year-old longevity rituals; hence, the festival's name. A chrysanthemum-boy doll, Noh plays, children's sumo, and floss-adorned chrysanthemums. Discover how the Chrysanthemum Festival has taken on new significance during the pandemic.</content>
    <description>Chrysanthemum flowers, which are used as a medicinal herb, are used to ward off evil on September 9th. Communities are now reevaluating the festival's significance in light of the current pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-11T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/NXxWHTLD#NO9Hw19sxrmJ027aW0rRhQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-11T00:00:29.747Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-10T23:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>51d797751c8200bbd5acb1d0b23fdb4f761f76158bef5577b1ec33dacca33358</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-10T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Double Ninth Festival: Beautiful Chrysanthemums Grant Longevity</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-11T01:03:53.900Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/G4hGEABa#dBcePr8f-bqOKqQs-H9p7A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>144</airingId>
    <content>Through novels and movies, the name Miyamoto Musashi has become synonymous with the word "samurai." The undefeated, 17th-century swordsman was also a master of calligraphy, the way of tea, and other arts. In his later years, he wrote "The Book of Five Rings" to relate the wisdom he gained through his duels. His teachings act a guide to living a significant life and remain seminal today during the pandemic. Discover Musashi's Kyoto through people who feel a deep affiliation with his way of life.</content>
    <description>Miyamoto Musashi, master of the sword and the arts, wrote his teachings 400 years ago. They act as a guide to living a significant life and remain seminal today, especially during the pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Ogt2xBAa#NXHQEB_iWp3gLO18jeqnqw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T00:00:23.702Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T23:29:21.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>22863a50f43b0544fe1b9132e639e9703b2c8be92de5a6ce1846039122a36fdc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miyamoto Musashi: Sword Mastery in the Ancient Capital</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T04:58:51.334Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UkNjwKpD#WDNfmTvY3TBYvt6PPBptVw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>145</airingId>
    <content>With the spread of Covid-19 in 2020, many annual festivals were condensed. But Kitano Goryoe was revived at Kitano Tenmangu after a 550-year hiatus in prayer for an end to the pandemic. The joint Shinto-Buddhist rite was originally held to appease the deity of plagues and honor dignitaries who were tragically killed. From this, Gion Matsuri and other festivals similarly evolved over the centuries. Discover the Kyoto customs to eradicate epidemics through rites, amulets, dolls, and confections.</content>
    <description>Due to the 2020 pandemic, many annual festivals that originated to curb disease were condensed. Even with medical advances today, people turn to age-old customs for comfort and strength.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/pQxQSJJZ#RpaVOy2Pv157TS6B2jRl_Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T00:00:30.810Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T23:29:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>4a90f266158e6fd358cb22c9a0a9bf660f5878daa6c09c17a0d1c95bcbe8a86b</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Warding off Epidemics: Heartfelt Prayers for Safety</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:22:29.831Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/dINDiCLB#lbZ8KoqQtQsdpXbFRAvS9g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>146</airingId>
    <content>Solid, durable and decorative, lacquer is a lustrous, natural polymer used in art, architecture, Buddhist statues, and everyday items. Kyoto was the seat of the emperor and aristocratic culture, so lacquerers always strove to out-dazzle each other and, in the process, refined their workmanship. Undeterred by difficulties they face from the pandemic, lacquerers today continue the art while searching for fresh ideas. Discover how they create the unconventional and innovative within the traditional.</content>
    <description>Solid, durable and decorative, lacquer is used in art, buildings, and everyday articles. Kyoto lacquerers strive to out-dazzle each other to create unconventional and innovative within the tradition.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3BdjiapC#L2yW58sPutoIiVh6LwrSkw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T00:00:25.846Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T23:29:23.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>b9845a688f7705fd79b5961c0618b044be8c976c450a2d0848eeb4eaa7a7f9de</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nouveau Lacquerware: Vibrant, Dazzling Beauty</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T04:53:28.963Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/w58Q0TzL#2CVMrscBkMsYZq4B3SWvbQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>147</airingId>
    <content>Hosoo Masataka, the 12th-generation of a Nishijin brocade producer, is making waves abroad as he updates the Nishijin brand with new technology and textiles. Tokyo-based architect Aoki Jun is director of the Kyoto City KYOCERA Museum of Art that reopened in 2020. His renovations introduced an open-plan that blends in with the surroundings and encourages interaction among visitors. Both share a deep appreciation of Kyoto aesthetics: one from within the city and the other from outside.</content>
    <description>Hosoo Masataka is a 12-generation producer of traditional Nishijin textiles. Architect Aoki Jun oversaw renovations at the Kyocera Museum of Art. They discuss the aesthetic sensibilities of Kyoto.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-21T06:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AvgwCISQ#9EPazJDuk8schGokay49KQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-21T06:00:31.354Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-21T05:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>913ead11cfd532055e50758d58a3ecf208cde9dae901b46164f46acaf833021a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-21T05:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Conversations: A Nishijin Textile Producer &amp; An Architect</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-21T06:49:32.646Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7dlUAAqL#jvP7L08n4phPlZ3ZvVTZnw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>148</airingId>
    <content>Mountainous Keihoku in Kyoto's north is more than 90% woodlands. The drastic temperature differences and the frequent rain and mist are ideal conditions for forestry. For more than 1,200 years the area supported the ancient capital's prosperity, supplying it with raw materials and food supplies. Residents carry on the trades of their ancestors, coexisting with nature. Discover how Keihoku is attracting attention from people wanting to learn the customs of old to build a sustainable future.</content>
    <description>Keihoku, an hour from the city, is 90 percent forest and was imperial land for 1,000 years. Take a look at rural life in Kyoto and how the township supported life and culture in the ancient capital.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-04T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/JMMh2aRJ#_0o2-fZnBZ9eGEDQqjm1Zg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-04T00:00:30.110Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-03T23:29:20.127Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>9ed598642aa15ec38c51531a9c2c7c9378ce815c77a278b4b78946df6c5e160c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-03T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Forests of Keihoku: Nature's Blessings Sustain the Ancient Capital</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-04T23:59:33.959Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gIgg2LCC#M4gObHK8RDWtZ6eYuTTlsw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>149</airingId>
    <content>Reizei Kimiko is the daughter of the 24th head of a once aristocratic family. Together with her husband, she upholds traditions in Waka poetry and other court rituals. Sugimoto Setsuko, the 10th generation of a former merchant family, preserves their Machiya townhouse for posterity and promotes the Obanzai style of cooking. Maintaining their family foundations, they both have faced adversity with the current pandemic. Discover the joy, pride and responsibility of carrying on family traditions.</content>
    <description>Reizei Kimiko belongs to a noble family that dates back 800 years. Sugimoto Setsuko comes from a 300-year-old kimono merchant family. These scions discuss the joy and hardship of upholding tradition.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-18T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/g5tVUI4a#OwpJK8_diPpADycN9NIBWA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-18T00:00:29.569Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-17T23:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>43dcfe501fcc532d3460dbc3c989e832ddb8394b87b511b84e20db191b3c8439</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-17T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Conversations: The Enduring Pride of Two Venerable Families</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-18T00:59:50.957Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tdgw3Taa#uXEijY1mHWs84pEj0eLC4A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>150</airingId>
    <content>The traditional, wooden townhouses built prior to 1950 that dot the downtown area of Kyoto served as both living and work spaces. American Jeff Berglund, university professor and Kyoto tourism ambassador, lives in one built 160 years ago. A Japan resident for 50 years, Berglund aspires to living in harmony with nature. He honors the customs of old that are still practiced today and promotes Japan's culture abroad. Discover the pleasures of living in a Machiya through Berglund's daily encounters.</content>
    <description>American Jeff Berglund, a university professor, lives in a Kyoto machiya townhouse, built 160 years ago. He shows us around his home and discusses the pleasures of living in a traditional setting.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-18T00:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2lciVRJB#GVFYrKT7Ol4t1ilObVLesw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-18T00:00:26.112Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-17T23:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2029</seriesId>
    <sha256>f1d6435b9dc1af38ee33c82112ee5817e3b0588850d4dfe228b7517ac2e0d66a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-17T23:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Life in a Machiya: The Appreciation of Nature and Time</subtitle>
    <title>Core Kyoto</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T01:19:26.498Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/B0wiDC4I#w7j30q_leT8rZFA4CexYBw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>