<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-26T17:10:03.695Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>80c159d773764353</seriesId>
  <title>A*B*C Tours</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>093</airingId>
    <content>CLASH, a rock band from Thailand, set the music video for their song "LONELY" in Yamaguchi Prefecture and Fukuoka Prefecture. This time, we travel with Bank, the lead singer of CLASH, on a tour highlighting both prefectures' great local food, scenery and music. On day 1, we enjoy the island of Tsunoshima by rental cycle, then visit Moji Port, which features great local ramen and a traditional banana auction. We also visit a jazz cafe and even see Bank perform a jazz version of "LONELY" with some local musicians.</content>
    <description>We travel with Bank, the lead singer of Thai band CLASH, on a tour of Yamaguchi and Fukuoka. On day 1, a scenic island, great local ramen and a port with famous jazz and banana-selling traditions.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/a1cQnJrS#Q-sJO-qBcMyWEsdpCtoo_g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T01:00:32.443Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T00:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>616676ea0154f05525c8e1e882e22872a6d799aa7e79e137938316affc43bb08</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Thai Rock Star in Yamaguchi &amp; Fukuoka Part 1</subtitle>
    <title>A*B*C Tours</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T23:44:00.528Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/zsEh0SgL#WZSSONWtMUiOmBr5ucSzlg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>094</airingId>
    <content>CLASH, a rock band from Thailand, set the music video for their song "LONELY" in Yamaguchi Prefecture and Fukuoka Prefecture. This time, we travel with Bank, the lead singer of CLASH, on a tour highlighting both prefectures' great local food, scenery and music. On day 2, the castle town of Kokura, where Bank tries on a kimono, experiences the city's long taiko drum tradition and visits a food market. Next, a taste of Kitakyushu's high-tech robot industry. Finally, we wrap up with a look at some great scenery.</content>
    <description>We travel with Bank, the lead singer of Thai band CLASH, on a tour of Yamaguchi and Fukuoka. On day 2, a castle town with kimono, great food and taiko drums, plus high-tech robots and amazing views.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/N5FQiTYL#h1oNmhAm2vz3BnBp5Rrd6w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T01:00:25.266Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T00:44:20.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>e1012ea2f33cb5752abbe4a2ae70c759b398fdf30ef9ba6163fdb00458fcc614</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Thai Rock Star in Yamaguchi &amp; Fukuoka Part 2</subtitle>
    <title>A*B*C Tours</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T17:45:11.405Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7x9ThIQZ#Q8WAHwz5B3pbBqQ2b118lA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>137</airingId>
    <content>The music video for the hit "Won't Cry" by Jay Chou with Mayday Ashin was set in Tokyo. We visit locations used in the video with Miyoshi Ayaka, one of its stars, and see how the coronavirus pandemic has affected the city. First, to a spot where you can see Tokyo Tower. Next, to trendy Harajuku, where we try a popular Taiwanese dessert. Then to hip Shimokitazawa, where Miyoshi tries a festival dance, visits a new open-air space and learns how the pandemic is affecting locals.</content>
    <description>We visit locations from the Jay Chou with Mayday Ashin "Won't Cry" music video with Miyoshi Ayaka, one of its stars. It was set in Tokyo: we see how the coronavirus pandemic has affected things.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-10T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZpJmTDZY#WS_BFEgjgZLxqqMsq-eD5g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-10T01:00:27.198Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-10T00:44:23.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>189fad6825aa500b9aa497a74141a5dd035855be74cdc5a1966ba7f6c3eec788</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-10T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Japanese Star Explores Pandemic Tokyo Part 1</subtitle>
    <title>A*B*C Tours</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-10T21:18:01.008Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yJ8GgTqR#42m1tHuTu-6fztzOa_VZlw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>138</airingId>
    <content>The music video for "Won't Cry" by Jay Chou with Mayday Ashin was set in Tokyo. In our second episode, we continue to visit locations used in the video with its star Miyoshi Ayaka and see how the coronavirus pandemic has affected the city. First, to upscale Ginza to see a vintage camera store and learn from a pro photographer. Next, to a sweets store that's launched a project helping local businesses during the pandemic. Finally, to Yanaka to meet a bamboo artisan and eat fermented foods.</content>
    <description>We visit locations from the Jay Chou with Mayday Ashin "Won't Cry" music video with Miyoshi Ayaka, one of its stars. It was set in Tokyo: we see how the coronavirus pandemic has affected things.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-17T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RcRgRJDQ#fTRK94L0AHGS6y9l9Y2YFQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-17T01:00:27.425Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-17T00:44:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>9b7f7b5d9a5273b74bb978a82e2047bfff54d2d58adee9950f4fc883bc124c15</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-17T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Japanese Star Explores Pandemic Tokyo Part 2</subtitle>
    <title>A*B*C Tours</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-17T01:25:46.519Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Y4M0mbhI#zvXKTqmhZWhl3C4Sh9DknA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>