<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-25T03:40:04.144Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>849018bc46f056a7</seriesId>
  <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>001</airingId>
    <content>How can we associate better with COVID-19? Let's find the key by learning about the history of the infectious diseases Japan has experienced.
Drawing Yokai, supernatural creatures like goblins, together to get rid of an epidemic was a typical way to provide relief in the Edo period (1603-1868). Dr. ISO shows examples such as Amabie.</content>
    <description>How can we associate better with COVID-19? Let's find the key by learning about the history of the infectious diseases Japan has experienced. This time: Expelling Epidemics with Yokai.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/XI9B0AIY#vGi_Gwf-dwRvE6E0oAdjwQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T15:45:26.659Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T15:39:20.027Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>6036</seriesId>
    <sha256>1fd378b2ca405851466b8302fb9288ddd65f024a65271ebf57e7df0791e729d5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T15:40:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dr. ISO's Pandemic History, Info &amp; Tips: Expelling Epidemics with Yokai</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T16:00:04.416Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/asllyQzR#bvE5WFhT29odHQHMwlV8Cw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>002</airingId>
    <content>A popular Japanese tourist spot, the Great Buddha at Todaiji Temple, is said to be constructed because of a major outbreak of smallpox. Dr. ISO explains why it occurred in the Nara period (710-794).</content>
    <description>How can we associate better with COVID-19? Let's find the key by learning about the history of the infectious diseases Japan has experienced. This time: Epidemics in the Nara Period.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-13T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FFsgyTzC#XOgqlRjEGIf17E5pBDroWw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-13T15:45:32.318Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-13T15:39:20.041Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>6036</seriesId>
    <sha256>75df7dc832d9ddaa161e2a9bbd5fede83210a2ce100b76591d3e30701205ccd3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-13T15:40:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dr. ISO's Pandemic History, Info &amp; Tips: Epidemics in the Nara Period</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T19:50:56.652Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/KV8iSDzR#0ihyLUJjpN7dLehkG2-Sfw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>003</airingId>
    <content>Girls brought up protectively in good families in the Heian period (794-late 12th) basically stayed socially distanced. Dr. ISO talks about the "zoning concept" of Japanese people.</content>
    <description>How can we associate better with COVID-19? Let's find the key by learning about the history of the infectious diseases Japan has experienced. This time: Social Distancing in the Heian Period.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-03T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/A0UmURia#aU5hz7i12XsUkPkn-v6B6w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-03T15:45:24.415Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-03T15:39:20.029Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>6036</seriesId>
    <sha256>b1ffe086bbf15512d139f3027c3e1be7020bdee05a6a4986209330046620076f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-03T15:40:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dr. ISO's Pandemic History, Info &amp; Tips: Social Distancing in the Heian Period</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-16T04:36:52.574Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/9840DZZa#BeFyXpmYt4Ppx4UCsh78vQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>004</airingId>
    <content>Would you know what to do in an earthquake in a crowded city? Learn the keys to survival in the life-or-death 72-hour period after an urban earthquake through a hands-on tour at SONA AREA TOKYO.</content>
    <description>Would you know what to do in an earthquake in a crowded city? Learn the keys to survival in the life-or-death 72-hour period after an urban earthquake through a hands-on tour at SONA AREA TOKYO.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T15:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wx1FBYLa#ZL3uxERtJzN_WsewUTnH1A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T15:40:28.706Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T15:29:20.096Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2084</seriesId>
    <sha256>2cd50919094408e4e3e8836c99018b3bea3a0c544e37fc1aaa195382e5276167</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>BOSAI: Be Prepared - What to Do in an Urban Earthquake</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:29:56.575Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/PJtHWKwZ#u0lWQEmR_agwX6EnomJkWA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>005</airingId>
    <content>When homes are lost or when danger comes, community-run evacuation centers are there. But who's eligible? What about provisions? And what are the rules? We'll take a closer look to find the answers.</content>
    <description>When homes are lost or when danger comes, community-run evacuation centers are there. But who's eligible? What about provisions? And what are the rules? We'll take a closer look to find the answers.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T15:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/DJ1FQaxL#JykULipHNZO2bo_Ryzem4Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T15:40:32.686Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T15:29:20.154Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2084</seriesId>
    <sha256>f2e9b090ba0ac6071f4176cde508a1e630a109ed0fde3e54a042e9a3f5492279</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>BOSAI: Be Prepared - Evacuation Shelters</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T16:14:08.110Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/QN4hRSra#uFMDTDQDnvdNTg2-eY5gmg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>006</airingId>
    <content>A 1995 earthquake caused widescale destruction across Japan's Kansai region, resulting in the creation of a small broadcast FM station. We examine the role of such local broadcast systems.</content>
    <description>As a series in Culture Crossroads, BOSAI: BE PREPARED provides practical knowledge to save yourself from natural disaster. In this episode, we learn from Great Hanshin Earthquake in 1995 in Kobe.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-13T15:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Tk9RFKxC#KryU7d5WAOSjL6BRSLmRBw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-13T15:40:41.008Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-13T15:29:20.097Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2084</seriesId>
    <sha256>1ba21dc1b13e6ab8d092f50b4b428150d990462f42301af0aca8cb828dc8682f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-13T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>BOSAI: Be Prepared - Learning from the Great Hanshin-Awaji Earthquake</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T18:05:38.555Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/T08RxC5L#JPEgLxurtWRjhqrAa7PNaQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>007</airingId>
    <content>In a disaster, with concerns over infectious disease or personal privacy, at-home evacuation is a consideration. We look at how to prepare your home and what supplies you need to have on hand.</content>
    <description>As a series in Culture Crossroads, BOSAI: BE PREPARED provides practical knowledge to save yourself from natural disaster. In this episode, we learn concrete tips for home evacuation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-03T15:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0Ik02J5Z#Dl88ZqNEu4YKzHze0yh9BA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-03T15:40:27.312Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-03T15:29:20.147Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2084</seriesId>
    <sha256>cd09585fdf8843267c2ba70fdd871129b067f7f1c43e97e5fc33eee3f7a3feb5</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-03T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>BOSAI: Be Prepared - At-home Evacuation</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-05T23:07:56.491Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1PwWHZqZ#ABvYEvLR72hvn2yEpmQyzg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>012</airingId>
    <content>The COVID-19 has affected everyone, especially for foreigners. For example, the situation coincided with Ramadan. Most years it's a time when Muslims fast during the day, joining friends and relatives after sunset to share a meal. However, self-isolation made it impossible. For another example, Bangladeshi community in Japan made up a network to help with each other. In this program, we focus on Muslim and Bangladeshi communities to have a look at their efforts to overcome the difficulties.</content>
    <description>The COVID-19 has affected Muslims in Japan. The situation coincided with Ramadan, making it tougher due to self-isolation. We link up with some of Muslims to find how they coped with the situation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-17T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zt820aoD#LTd4ggU08vUosWIw6kMXZw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-17T15:45:26.273Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-17T15:29:23.109Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>83d3bbfe141725053cf51d59cb78dfbbfa20f2a246f36d7ce488099a7ad08d42</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-17T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Linking Hands in Times of Crisis</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-17T16:28:31.741Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/L09wnYSB#xeHCN4cnfkJwhpACEfLsUg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>013</airingId>
    <content>Over 300,000 foreign students are currently in Japan pursuing studies and looking for work after graduation. However, like many others, they too are being severely affected by the coronavirus pandemic. This program focuses on the efforts of a Japanese language school and an employment agency as they take on new approaches to help students from abroad overcome the crisis.</content>
    <description>As foreign students in Japan struggle to overcome the crisis brought on by the pandemic, a Japanese language school and an employment agency take on new approaches to provide them with support.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7lknnQBB#4RNLRPANnyDRv62GXomCIA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T15:45:29.037Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T15:29:22.921Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>ac35bc6a15c2626132c5145d425eb97bd5d37bd9b3ebeeb96e9bb4c0f25cc4d9</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Foreign Students - Japan's Future</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:43:36.210Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UVxCATDC#iTxgubHKaV0t3WapzWw2ww</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>Pandemic-era Japan's foreign residents are more isolated than ever. We look at the efforts of Kalakasan, a group empowering immigrant women, and a teacher who supports foreign students in Yamaguchi Prefecture.</content>
    <description>Pandemic-era Japan's foreign residents are more isolated than ever. We look at the efforts of Kalakasan, a group empowering immigrant women, and a teacher who supports foreign students in Yamaguchi.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ocMFkaDB#q8xxscHf_P64p-dyvEsy8w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T15:45:26.178Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T15:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>c8bfc7cd918169a7372f6ce9bbca9f72027fb14374836ec511e2ee299fed4868</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Finding a Place to Belong</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-23T22:48:45.697Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HosyiZQL#TQqX2XgB9K9BiUkpEe7WUg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>In this episode, we answer a question from a viewer living in Russia, "Can you tell me what is happening with plastic waste in such a technologically advanced country?" Our reporter is Russian broadcast announcer Anastasia Monakova. Japan is advanced in separating and recycling trash, but it also produces a significant portion of the world's plastic waste. To reduce waste, shops started charging for plastic shopping bags in July. But the amount of plastic waste generated by households is increasing due to COVID-19. We visit Kamakura, which was the first city in Japan to make a "zero plastic waste" declaration. In addition, bioplastics are attracting attention as they are kind to nature and recyclable options. Some are made from plant-derived materials and some are decomposed by microorganisms. We visit the laboratory of Professor Iwata Tadahisa of the University of Tokyo, who is a leader in this field. We cover the professor's work at the forefront of bioplastic research.</content>
    <description>Plastic waste is a problem worldwide and Japan is one of the worst offenders. What is happening in Kamakura with its "zero plastic waste" policy? And what is the future of bioplastic?</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T21:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FRwExZzL#3BCEOUgcp8S3mzfYDsa6cA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T21:45:27.648Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T21:29:20.130Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>b210b251e4dd27c41506929401aacda3cf4231263b0a54f8b4e4db28fe98beb2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T21:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>WHAT'S YOUR CONNECTION?: Aiming for Coexistence with Plastic</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:46:03.534Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/y8cVTayL#PZcsggvFdaWFdU6iFay9HA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>016</airingId>
    <content/>
    <description>Our theme is Japanese kite culture. We look at their history through a Niigata kite battle and a craftsman in a traditional shop. Our reporter tries to make and fly a kite. Will it get off the ground?</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-24T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/pVFRAaJR#hgUmYqpVmteYLerlc6uEKw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-24T15:45:27.183Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-24T15:29:23.007Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>cc8ebda001c82e63c4dd7e619e4c3e246be58d804e7161f3dc694d41dc921ab1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-24T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle/>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-24T16:29:52.945Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/QJdFVa4D#imbkpLhDG-EvoCTudRhfmw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>017</airingId>
    <content>In the wake of the 2011 Great East Japan Earthquake, the song "Flowers Will Bloom" was created in support of those affected by the disaster. Now, 10 years later, it is reborn in 11 languages with performances by artists such as May J., Ono Lisa, and Morisaki Win who generously offered their voices. Can the song carry its prayer of hope across the globe? Join us as we learn the story behind the song's inception, look at the disaster area today, and introduce messages from around the world.</content>
    <description>After the Great East Japan Earthquake on 2011, the song "Flowers Will Bloom" was created in support of those affected by the disaster. Now the song is about to be reborn in 11 languages!</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-10T15:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FGxUURrB#0LWsZ4teGKJBIKnNgHN6Kw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-10T15:45:27.127Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-10T15:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2083</seriesId>
    <sha256>9aeb910078e23d7762bcffbff82afe1b7333262ccc9c2b38e106d1b08e82aa39</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-10T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Flowers Will Bloom Beyond Borders</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-10T19:37:00.023Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/iJk2RBxa#hxrRZfdz7rqa8_RsPb_I7w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>023</airingId>
    <content>This time, we answer a question from carpet designer Abdelilah Boubchir, a resident of Algeria, who wants to know about Japanese carpet making and the history. Our reporter is Karima Elsamny, an Arabic broadcast announcer from Egypt. In Okayama Prefecture's Kurashiki area, local Igusa rush grass is used to produce Hanagoza mats and Igusa carpets called Kurashiki Dantsu. Both were once exported overseas. Made of dyed Igusa rush grass woven into patterns, Hanagoza mats were especially popular. Igusa can absorb moisture and thus be used in hot, humid Japanese summers. We explore the appeal of rugs and carpets designed for the climate of Japan.</content>
    <description>We explore the world of rugs created for hot, humid Japan. Okayama Prefecture produces rugs and woven carpets made of Igusa rush grass. We report on their export history and local popularity.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-09T15:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qwt0XJCY#qcUXKQGsToxDvtpBjZ0b9Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-09T15:40:32.683Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-09T15:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2076</seriesId>
    <sha256>3b37e6442d11e1e50d938772efb1eb80e454832cf20155ba95ae3d8285f12fc5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-09T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>WHAT'S YOUR CONNECTION?: Japanese Grass Mats</subtitle>
    <title>Culture Crossroads</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:38:37.202Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/rwETDYYA#vIcwUuN0PWkKGYe2PJzvkA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>