<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-26T16:10:02.872Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>93f1898b227dbd5d</seriesId>
  <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>131</airingId>
    <content>In the midst of a global pandemic, the world is reexamining social mechanisms and values. Meanwhile, creators are looking to ancient civilizations and lifestyles to see what we can learn, and their designs have won acclaim. Architect Tsuyoshi Tane explores designs for the future that were inspired by ancient history.</content>
    <description>Today's theme: Ancient Design. At a time when we're reexamining our values some creators are inspired by ancient life and civilizations. Architect Tsuyoshi Tane explores the future through our past.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/up0wWC6S#lsLBVRlKJOkcpxmYNRmBVw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T01:00:24.741Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T00:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>21a7c353209bb31786edd3f387d807154d9b2fbae77660c00d85304b27e53519</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ancient Design</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T04:41:46.569Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>133</airingId>
    <content>A special two-part series of discussions between leading Japanese product designer Naoto Fukasawa and top interface designer Yugo Nakamura. In part 1, Nakamura dives into the extraordinary forms and simple beauty of Fukasawa's designs. 2 cutting-edge designers outline their thoughts on the future of creativity.</content>
    <description>Top Japanese product designer Naoto Fukasawa and global interface designer Yugo Nakamura discuss their experiences and philosophies in a two-part special! In part one we explore Fukasawa's designs.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-19T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/n4V1kYJZ#MLgEBZAlf9efTIutWHAbrA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-19T01:00:27.109Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-19T00:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>0aca64882a8b010ff317e7cfc4ce1e274e3751a999cc8e444237e954c2855ef4</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-19T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Designing Emergence: Part 1</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T13:28:29.813Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>134</airingId>
    <content>A special two-part series of discussions between leading Japanese product designer Naoto Fukasawa and top interface designer Yugo Nakamura. In part 2, Fukasawa explores Nakamura's intriguing interfaces which connect the virtual and physical worlds. 2 cutting-edge designers outline their thoughts on the future of creativity.</content>
    <description>Top Japanese product designer Naoto Fukasawa and global interface designer Yugo Nakamura discuss their experiences and philosophies in a two-part special! In part two dive into Nakamura's designs.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-26T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2gkFiaLB#F6AQ_OrOf0rngP5bT8c7sA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-26T07:00:29.571Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-26T06:29:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>b773c797282e2c8d69bcec4927ed1d42bee7a63b8864adf8b411e172b2e73729</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-26T06:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Designing Emergence: Part 2</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T13:37:50.156Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>135</airingId>
    <content>On Design Hunts Andy and Shaula search for designs rooted in regional history and climates. This time they visit Ishikawa Prefecture. In the first episode, they explore the historic city of Kanazawa and its many traditions. A castle town and stronghold of the Kaga domain, it flourished under the Maeda family as the home of traditional arts, crafts and foods. Today structures such as the glass dome and Noh drum gate of Kanazawa station, and the 21st Century Museum of Contemporary Art have also put it on the map for cutting-edge design. Discover how the city is still creating arts and crafts while shaping a future for regional culture. Join us on a design hunt in Kanazawa!</content>
    <description>Today's theme: Design Hunting in Kanazawa, Ishikawa prefecture. This historic castle town is home to a variety of traditional arts, crafts, and food as well as dazzling modern architecture and design.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-03T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/6slAQBYA#aydP7p-51TwIup3g6VGLqQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-03T01:00:29.728Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-03T00:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>809c7a1cc1e0cafea08b2806f7b0c0ba251ded231736cf8aaec9b1ec7f60ca2d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-03T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Design Hunting in Kanazawa, Ishikawa Prefecture</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:57:57.196Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>137</airingId>
    <content>Humanity has always dreamed of the future and the many forms it might take. Designers and artists have been inspired by its possibilities and used their imaginations to create artworks and products. What kind of future can we create during the coronavirus pandemic? Architect Toyoda Keisuke explores a world of new designs.</content>
    <description>Today's theme: The Future II. The future has always inspired designers and artists. What kind of future can we build during a pandemic? Architect Toyoda Keisuke explores a world of new designs.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SF0EwT5J#fkqV0JbvomnENr4Xs3Fzlw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T01:00:22.385Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T00:29:22.943Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>5847d645f9c1f226bb60ce0185185d5f2e7d30503a72e1460a25fde7a8917eff</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Future II</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:47:48.438Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>