<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-26T02:50:03.437Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>93f1898b227dbd5d</seriesId>
  <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>131</airingId>
    <content>In the midst of a global pandemic, the world is reexamining social mechanisms and values. Meanwhile, creators are looking to ancient civilizations and lifestyles to see what we can learn, and their designs have won acclaim. Architect Tsuyoshi Tane explores designs for the future that were inspired by ancient history.</content>
    <description>Today's theme: Ancient Design. At a time when we're reexamining our values some creators are inspired by ancient life and civilizations. Architect Tsuyoshi Tane explores the future through our past.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-24T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/up0wWC6S#lsLBVRlKJOkcpxmYNRmBVw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-24T01:00:24.741Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-24T00:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>21a7c353209bb31786edd3f387d807154d9b2fbae77660c00d85304b27e53519</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-24T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ancient Design</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T04:41:46.569Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>137</airingId>
    <content>Humanity has always dreamed of the future and the many forms it might take. Designers and artists have been inspired by its possibilities and used their imaginations to create artworks and products. What kind of future can we create during the coronavirus pandemic? Architect Toyoda Keisuke explores a world of new designs.</content>
    <description>Today's theme: The Future II. The future has always inspired designers and artists. What kind of future can we build during a pandemic? Architect Toyoda Keisuke explores a world of new designs.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-17T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SF0EwT5J#fkqV0JbvomnENr4Xs3Fzlw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-17T01:00:22.385Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-17T00:29:22.943Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2046</seriesId>
    <sha256>5847d645f9c1f226bb60ce0185185d5f2e7d30503a72e1460a25fde7a8917eff</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-17T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Future II</subtitle>
    <title>DESIGN TALKS plus</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:47:48.438Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>