<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-26T16:05:03.150Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>a5fed3c217d7b7f6</seriesId>
  <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>808</airingId>
    <content>The coronavirus has led to a rise in home dining. And as a result people are more concerned about what they put into their bodies. Amid this trend, produce from small scale farms is becoming increasingly popular. Consumers are able to buy fresh vegetables direct from farmers, via the Internet. And the products are often grown in a safer, more environmentally friendly way than those that are mass-produced. For farmers, the system not only offers greater profits, but the opportunity to make a contribution toward a sustainable future for society. We take a look at some examples in Japan.
Guests:
Akimoto Rina (Founder of a direct sales platform for produce)
Miyata Hiroaki (Professor, Keio University)
Sekine Kae (Associate Professor, Aichi Gakuin University)
*Today's Close-Up will continue to report on COVID-19.</content>
    <description>As the pandemic changes societal values, small scale farming is increasingly seen as a viable new lifestyle. We look at how the agriculture sector is leading the push for a sustainable world.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T20:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sF0T2CSY#o1nl93ds1cLKYrVecDT3Aw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T20:30:28.439Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T19:59:20.167Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>653aea9b3353826f05d45bdd6a8b8ae7e1ec13c86d12c5ff2d6268cba28c57e6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T20:00:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Small Scale Farming: A Lifestyle for the Post-Pandemic World</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T07:01:04.699Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OpkWySIJ#DbGfBmI8WhpXDNrZ58Gd-A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>809</airingId>
    <content>Japan's hanko seals have been an essential requirement for day-to-day documents and official forms for many years. But a government push to bring workplace practices and administrative procedures fully into the digital era has put pressure on businesses and city authorities to eliminate the seals from most paperwork. We look at what the shift away from this long-running custom means for Japan, and some of the hurdles that are presenting themselves along the way.
Guests:
Atsugiri Jason (Tech firm executive/Comedian)
Watanabe Yuichiro (Member of the Board, Japan In-House Lawyers Association)
Miyata Hiroaki (Professor, Keio University)</content>
    <description>The use of hanko seals on official forms and documents is deeply ingrained in Japanese culture. But a society-wide shift to digital work practices is forcing many to question the need for them.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-20T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vR0DQQIa#cLY0NjKVJHi_Hzg72zHIGg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-20T16:00:28.713Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-20T15:29:22.754Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>6b943be88c209c8f63271de717ad5dce10d4e82da84d15a4bbee6f262264e697</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-20T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Will Japan Change Without "Hanko"?</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T07:02:22.420Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FVkASCrS#EyFybDVqwBuTFAc5tZkdjg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>810</airingId>
    <content>The Tokyo Olympic Games are due to open in eight months' time, but can they really be held while the coronavirus pandemic shows no sign of ending? An international gymnastics competition held in Tokyo in early November was used as a test event. The organizers took strict anti-infection measures, but were troubled by a series of unexpected problems. NHK went behind the scenes to see what will be necessary to safely hold the Tokyo 2020 Olympic Games.
Guest:
Kaku Mitsuo (Specially Appointed Professor, Tohoku Medical and Pharmaceutical University)</content>
    <description>What difficulties await the organizers of the Tokyo Olympic Games next year because of the coronavirus pandemic? We look behind the scenes of an international gymnastics meet held as a test in Tokyo.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-27T22:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ocQGgTIC#9zi3R8FgQcerk8k6XzT60A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-27T22:00:32.665Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-27T21:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>3bf6f259ea0ec44ad1c5bb90b928046f77856629251dcb0be05c803bf50db17f</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-27T21:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Are the Tokyo Games Possible? - Int'l Gymnastics Meet Held as Test</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:32:12.742Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tgtSUQID#r_xpY3mk-uJDIy9Am4EwzA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>811</airingId>
    <content>In the latest Global Gender Gap Index survey, Japan came 121st out of 153 countries, and was the lowest among major advanced nations. The government is aiming to have women in 30 percent of leadership roles by 2020, but the figure currently stands at just 14.8 percent. What does Japanese society need to do to change this? Overcoming "unconscious bias" might be the answer. NHK took a close look at how some companies are trying to tackle this issue to find out the key to creating a workplace where women can shine.
Guests:
Takeishi Emiko (Professor, Hosei University)
Miyata Hiroaki (Professor, Keio University)</content>
    <description>Unconscious biases are regarded as one of the main factors behind the struggle to get women to play more active roles in Japanese companies. We take a look at the effort to overcome them.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-04T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/dABEgZzA#ssYcbCWBnowUk8KtIxVg6g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-04T16:00:29.689Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-04T15:29:22.949Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>0b973b8f03f45940dab536cc803a0023a097b7915f8e8bc6a4333d0010d7e373</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-04T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Workplace Where Women Can Shine: Overcoming Innate Gender Bias</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:29:21.467Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/REkkmApD#g6SIWsgOZiPTWBFP_ZH0Gg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>812</airingId>
    <content>More than 1,300 farm animals, including pigs, calves, and goats, were stolen this summer in Japan's Kanto region. During the investigation, local police arrested a group of Vietnamese nationals on suspicion of overstaying their visas. Their connection to the thefts is still unclear but NHK followed a trail of social media posts advertising butchered pigs. We learned about the tough situation faced by Vietnamese technical trainees, and how the pandemic is making things even more difficult.</content>
    <description>Recent reports of stolen farm animals north of Tokyo shed light on the increasingly tough situation faced by Vietnamese technical trainees in Japan. We take a deeper look at their plight.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-11T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/CgdSjJCa#CSk8oj3Zb-Slgk5ggmH0iA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-11T16:00:24.491Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-11T15:29:23.044Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>cc7e030c8b6fc3cce739da9025958b6c5058e145ee882dc71706b66cf8748193</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-11T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>In Search of the Stolen Pigs: The Plight of Vietnamese Technical Trainees</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T06:29:11.438Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IQQ2GbLK#olxh1X6uJvbiGAvJ4-5RHA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>813</airingId>
    <content>On December 6, Japan's Hayabusa2 probe successfully returned a capsule to Earth after a six-year voyage through space. It is believed to contain sub-surface materials collected on Ryugu, an asteroid some 300-million kilometers away. They may shed light on the origins of life on Earth. The mission faced a series of unexpected challenges and NHK went behind the scenes to see how the team achieved the extraordinary feat of two touchdowns on Ryugu and the safe return of the sample container.
Guests:
Tsuda Yuichi (Hayabusa2 Project Manager)
Terazono Junya (Former member, Hayabusa project team)</content>
    <description>Japan's Hayabusa2 mission has achieved a world-first by returning samples of sub-surface material from an asteroid. We take an in-depth look at how the project team overcame unexpected difficulties.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-18T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/WcsFkCaZ#J-Rrt-aOp0qDZZ22bKIzoA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-18T16:00:26.291Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-18T15:29:22.735Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>2563d6a90ae1103cdb7f8053104bb0b5ec94f5b34df50602e8589d8a9d6d6fe5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-18T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hayabusa2: Secrets of Japan's Asteroid Mission</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T15:56:28.169Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/tcdkFLJK#_M94VSUIXlovR_YnQ5m5mg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>814</airingId>
    <content>Japan is currently experiencing a sharp spike in coronavirus infections, leading the government to declare a second state of emergency. Hospital beds are filling up and in one case, a patient was rejected by 24 emergency care facilities. At the same time, new strains from around the world present the threat of a further surge. We take a look at how experts are using the latest data and technology to avoid a worst-case scenario.
Guest: 
Hamada Atsuo (Professor, Tokyo Medical University)
*Today's Close-Up will continue to report on COVID-19.</content>
    <description>As coronavirus strains from around the world threaten an unprecedented surge in cases, experts in Japan are struggling to come up with adequate preventive measures. We take a look at their efforts.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-15T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vyoilYQb#fDX93qgb-3VxhdDMQ5MDtQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-15T16:00:24.414Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-15T15:29:24.216Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>34e1798501ca961286f609e1166f2b9d3ee6334efe94508ff2309474f08c64e1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-15T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How to Prevent Worst-Case COVID-19 Surge: Latest Findings Provide the Key</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T08:23:08.423Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/eI0AxQoI#y65ja-PIE3FRznf-hN3avw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>815</airingId>
    <content>Japan is in the midst of a third wave of coronavirus infections, the worst yet. The collapse of the medical system could soon become reality. With beds in short supply, ambulances transporting patients are increasingly being turned away from hospitals. Many people have no choice but to recuperate at home, anxiously monitoring for a sudden deterioration in their conditions. We ask medical experts how Japan can bring the situation under control.
Guest:
Ogura Takayuki (COO, Japan ECMOnet for COVID-19)
*Today's Close-Up will continue to report on COVID-19.</content>
    <description>A surge in COVID-19 cases across Japan is straining hospitals and pushing the medical system to the brink of collapse. We ask experts what the government can do to avert a crisis and save lives.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-22T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/XqI21ZCK#dbMujC_qOE-vkzOLzl_g0w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-22T16:00:23.477Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-22T15:29:23.086Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>b7bf8a2375fa3f05216acd3904683a5cbaebd40285315f71d7e930a702ca4cb1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-22T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Frontline of COVID-19 Fight: An Escalating Medical Crisis</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-22T17:44:11.561Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oWYADLaQ#1FqS2YGsK56y-XM0wAbifQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>816</airingId>
    <content>Japan's izakaya dining bars have always been places for people to enjoy a cozy drink and a bite to eat with friends. It's a dining culture that attracts overseas tourists too. But the coronavirus pandemic has the industry up against a wall. Some izakaya have transitioned into barbecue restaurants with robot servers, while others now specialize in take-out and delivery. A major worry is how to safeguard jobs in an industry where most of the workers are part-timers. NHK's cameras followed one major izakaya chain to document its efforts to survive.
Guests:
Asagi Kuniko (TV personality)
Ishii Kota (Writer)</content>
    <description>Japan's izakaya dining bars are loved by workers and students alike, but the ongoing pandemic has put business at risk. We go behind the scenes of a major chain as it works out a way to survive.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-29T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/lBZxRSra#el--DjTUTZV1h2wTYPnaBQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-29T16:00:27.661Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-29T15:29:22.842Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>c4e403d0d908a1a34688afbcc7ab983c9f43b44a3514db5ebbafd00b06d6c363</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-29T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Goodbye, Izakaya? Japanese Pubs at Crossroads</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-29T18:17:24.212Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/0c421bjB#XQuMgwo67ISXge8jfRWnGg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>817</airingId>
    <content>Stock investment apps are becoming popular in Japan as share prices surge during the pandemic. Some even allow people to use reward points earned through everyday cashless payments to become shareholders. Such mobile investors could become a driving force in the market, as the case of Robinhood showed in the US. How will this new trend change our lives and the economy at a time when the world is trying to bounce back from the coronavirus?
Guests:
Nagi Rei (Researcher, Youth research unit, Dentsu)
Iwashita Naoyuki (Professor, Kyoto University School of Government)</content>
    <description>A vast range of financial services from payments and loan financing to investment is becoming available through smartphone apps. We take a look at these developments being accelerated by the pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-05T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/dIoFDa5L#rKNjKzQav1lQlmg_m0_2qg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-05T16:00:31.466Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-05T15:29:23.503Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>a43b0992c20b2815e80c808baeb3b3bb11c9a7c611d6f4af44d2eae353ae58d6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-05T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mobile Finance Revolution Driven by Pandemic</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-05T21:52:22.604Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oZhB2I7Z#scA8NUbxUQ8fkIWgQQvh5A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>818</airingId>
    <content>The coronavirus pandemic has hit Japan's vulnerable teenagers especially hard. Some have been forced to take jobs to support their cash-strapped parents. Others have found themselves cooped up in stressful home environments as a result of stay-at-home requests. We spent time at a school attended by many struggling teens and documented the efforts of teachers and other staff to assist them as they make the transition beyond graduation into society.
Guest:
Ishii Kota (Writer)</content>
    <description>The pandemic has hit vulnerable teenagers hard, forcing them to work to support their parents and to spend more time in troubled home environments. We look at what some schools are doing to help.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-19T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/41lQUYYK#MrjzMUcR-i-t1aAa-XC-Yw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-19T16:00:27.091Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-19T15:29:22.751Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4002</seriesId>
    <sha256>62761da9c4dc989e1e1da14b2bdda600d369f1bef168bdd6c51f67e052250f2a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-19T15:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Pandemic Hits Troubled Teens</subtitle>
    <title>Today's Close-Up</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-19T17:12:59.321Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cxFiiLCY#K6P5a8vCPaCHEbVjKOTxsQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>