<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-31T08:05:03.259Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>ac0dc75327258b51</seriesId>
  <title>The Professionals</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>133</airingId>
    <content>We follow Imoto Haruhisa, a 50-year-old maths teacher so famous people come from across the nation to observe his classroom. From a top-level school to a foster care facility, he encourages students to shine in classes praised as "magical" and "miraculous." His unorthodox lessons never use textbooks or require taking notes. How does this approach help students build their thinking skills? Through Imoto's "ultimate philosophy of learning," we find many hints applicable not only in education, but for raising children and personnel development as well.</content>
    <description>We follow Imoto Haruhisa, a famous maths teacher whose lessons never use textbooks or notes. Instead, he encourages children to develop thinking skills through his "ultimate philosophy of learning."</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8d4GQCRA#qAhTARoRbUXX_9_phv-FZQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T14:00:22.498Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T13:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>3bb9e936e904de0e133532f3854f23dbf80e0432bffd79853092b9bebc7dc711</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T13:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Children Have the Answers: Imoto Haruhisa, Maths Teacher</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:04:43.194Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cJ8DlYoY#jAMnmkesgBwS3oTorvaJFQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>135</airingId>
    <content>We spent several months following plant breeder Washizawa Koji, known as "The God of Dahlias." In his dahlia garden on the outskirts of Akita City, he's created innovative new varieties of dahlia that have shaken up the flower industry. Once considered plain, the dahlia has become a bright flower, popular for special occasions thanks to Washizawa's efforts. Though he spends his days walking the fields barefoot and sleeping in a hut nearby, he has led an incredible life. In his devotion to dahlias, he ended up sacrificing his family; now, his thoughts once again turn to them. This is the story of a man enthralled by the magic of dahlias, and the family that was torn apart.</content>
    <description>Plant breeder Washizawa Koji has created innovative new dahlias that have shaken up the flower industry. We look at the story of his devotion to dahlias, and the family that he ended up sacrificing.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-06T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zdtyGZYa#hus-TiSMhzNcm3-0q1zUJg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-06T02:00:26.118Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-06T01:09:20.066Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>103d401ff13fc30f620c5bb12b83a8c0cec7108b16ac91871b5a9a6e3e8d34c5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-06T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Charmed by a Magical Flower: Washizawa Koji, Plant Breeder</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:20:10.031Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5ZtV3KJA#eqXvZ1i-ncTCBeRhmqP27Q</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>