<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-16T02:35:03.595Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>ac0dc75327258b51</seriesId>
  <title>The Professionals</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>133</airingId>
    <content>We follow Imoto Haruhisa, a 50-year-old maths teacher so famous people come from across the nation to observe his classroom. From a top-level school to a foster care facility, he encourages students to shine in classes praised as "magical" and "miraculous." His unorthodox lessons never use textbooks or require taking notes. How does this approach help students build their thinking skills? Through Imoto's "ultimate philosophy of learning," we find many hints applicable not only in education, but for raising children and personnel development as well.</content>
    <description>We follow Imoto Haruhisa, a famous maths teacher whose lessons never use textbooks or notes. Instead, he encourages children to develop thinking skills through his "ultimate philosophy of learning."</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T14:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8d4GQCRA#qAhTARoRbUXX_9_phv-FZQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T14:00:22.498Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T13:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>3bb9e936e904de0e133532f3854f23dbf80e0432bffd79853092b9bebc7dc711</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T13:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Children Have the Answers: Imoto Haruhisa, Maths Teacher</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:04:43.194Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cJ8DlYoY#jAMnmkesgBwS3oTorvaJFQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>135</airingId>
    <content>We spent several months following plant breeder Washizawa Koji, known as "The God of Dahlias." In his dahlia garden on the outskirts of Akita City, he's created innovative new varieties of dahlia that have shaken up the flower industry. Once considered plain, the dahlia has become a bright flower, popular for special occasions thanks to Washizawa's efforts. Though he spends his days walking the fields barefoot and sleeping in a hut nearby, he has led an incredible life. In his devotion to dahlias, he ended up sacrificing his family; now, his thoughts once again turn to them. This is the story of a man enthralled by the magic of dahlias, and the family that was torn apart.</content>
    <description>Plant breeder Washizawa Koji has created innovative new dahlias that have shaken up the flower industry. We look at the story of his devotion to dahlias, and the family that he ended up sacrificing.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-06T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zdtyGZYa#hus-TiSMhzNcm3-0q1zUJg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-06T02:00:26.118Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-06T01:09:20.066Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>103d401ff13fc30f620c5bb12b83a8c0cec7108b16ac91871b5a9a6e3e8d34c5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-06T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Charmed by a Magical Flower: Washizawa Koji, Plant Breeder</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:20:10.031Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5ZtV3KJA#eqXvZ1i-ncTCBeRhmqP27Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>136</airingId>
    <content>At Japan's department stores, no event is more popular than the Hokkaido Products Fair. And the charismatic man behind the scenes is Honda Daisuke. As the industry's only Hokkaido-based buyer, he taps into his extensive network of contacts to discover food and ingredients that surprise and delight customers all over the country. What's more, he teams up with chefs and other food experts to turn those ingredients into original products, from sweets to sushi bowls. For the last few years Hokkaido's catches of winter salmon and crab have been declining. We follow Honda as he attempts to use a certain fish to create a new hit item for the fair. In 2020, he returns to Hokkaido Prefecture, which is struggling with earthquake recovery as well as poor fishing catches, to find new ways to promote the area.</content>
    <description>Honda Daisuke is a department store buyer based in Hokkaido. He creates hit items for a popular event: the Hokkaido Products Fair. In 2020, he tries to find new ways to promote the area.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-03T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1YV0FT4Q#QYoL_tU9sMjIjeIN2N4rwg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-03T01:55:29.077Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-03T01:09:20.066Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>74db7f8ea1d2e398176e3c3a571dd7f692059b9e816900bd696eb69a6330bcc0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-03T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Career Built on Passion and Connections 2020: Honda Daisuke, Department Store Buyer</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T11:31:34.247Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jdsyGY6I#ekn91ILD-SdiirX4yNYyyw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>142</airingId>
    <content>The Tsugaru peninsula lies on the northern part of Japan's main island, and is home to some of the country's most untamed landscapes. For more than 30 years, 93-year-old Kuwata Misao has made over 50,000 Sasa-mochi rice cakes every year here, all on her own. She goes into the wilderness to find bamboo leaves, and grows her own azuki beans to ensure the perfect ingredients for her delicious mochi. What is the meaning of work? Of life? Of happiness? Granny Mochi's quiet, delightful tale warms the heart.</content>
    <description>93-year-old Kuwata Misao makes 50,000 sasa mochi rice cakes every year, all on her own. What is the meaning of work? Of life? Of happiness? Granny Mochi's quiet, delightful tale warms the heart.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-14T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OUhiiAoC#rvq4LFU-fsVeFDbQ4rfUBA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-14T01:55:29.213Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-14T01:09:20.132Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>6681bbc4e0fd8ead0ca2fc122b8eeb76fa04b2a3515f5d871885c80af57d8951</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-14T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Tale of Granny Mochi: Kuwata Misao</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T12:34:19.476Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/T9hWDATb#VrSW6UvE-9WiFqTSi_7k9g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>143</airingId>
    <content>53-year-old Iwasa Toru is a chief editor of a popular magazine conveying the appeal of rural Japan. Flooded with requests from across Japan, he works on rebuilding inns and revitalizing towns as "a master of rural restoration" and "a key figure in rural development." Having moved his entire company from Tokyo to a rural village in Niigata Prefecture, Iwasa has been gaining popularity through his approach to work. We follow him over time as he works on a project to revive a long-running inn and the surrounding hot spring town. Iwasa's insight on rural restoration may provide the key to revitalizing Japan as a whole.</content>
    <description>Iwasa Toru is both the chief editor of a popular magazine, and a constantly-in-demand master of revitalizing rural towns. We take a look at his unique approach to work.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-10T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/TJ8g2Jpb#ooB25yDGT7A_B7IfO14Jyg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-10T01:56:11.649Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-10T01:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>3fd488860b765717547a62009176b1d9a930f8a55ad20c7b12e9bf330e509935</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-10T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Starting a Rural Revolution: Iwasa Toru, Editor</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T19:42:13.309Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/2JUhQaDB#2bCpBVCYlu_sxyw7ObB-IA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>144</airingId>
    <content>Okonomiyaki is a popular street food in Hiroshima. Lauded as the best Okonomiyaki chef of his generation, Ichii Kaoru (66) owns the first Okonomiyaki restaurant to be listed in a world-renowned restaurant guidebook. He's elevated this former street food into top-flight cuisine. His secret is using a steaming technique that maximizes the sweetness of the cabbage; high-speed cameras reveal the expertise required to manipulate this steam. But Ichii had to follow a rocky road to reach his current heights. Discover how one man dedicated himself to an obsession with Okonomiyaki.</content>
    <description>Okonomiyaki is a popular street food in Hiroshima. One chef, Ichii Kaoru (66), is even listed in a world-renowned restaurant guidebook. Learn how one man discovered his passion for okonomiyaki.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-07T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/asUFFITZ#ncMl3wFWnXea-zPXPqO_QQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-07T01:55:22.406Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-07T01:09:20.129Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>a8f974f60c6ac90304914a8337eb6f2ca6b4d9f8fe41b7d60ceff88847b87079</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-07T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Savory Pancake Greater Than Its Parts: Ichii Kaoru, Okonomiyaki Chef</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T23:39:45.873Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wwtCVAjY#CV2ea9Mci8DmOCv5TdNmIw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>148</airingId>
    <content>Sudden firings and contract cancellations. The pandemic has caused a downturn that's leaving workers in dire straits. Many have turned to a safe haven: a labor union that's open to all. It's run by 56-year-old Sekine Shuichiro, who set up temporary shelters after the 2008 financial crisis, and has supported countless casual workers. Sekine can't bear to see workers being mistreated. We follow his efforts to help temporary and casual workers over 5 difficult months.</content>
    <description>Sudden firings and contract cancellations. Unions have become a safe haven for people suffering in the pandemic. Follow five months of battling for all workers, including temporary and contract staff.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-17T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sQQnAKLZ#ypChU1ledWs27Y5SWvtv3Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-17T01:55:28.589Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-17T01:09:23.710Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>0798d414d1e74bce060231ebbd0c957d909d821e956228ebdec0818db3378f30</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-17T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>One Step Forward, Together: Sekine Shuichiro, Labor Union Manager</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T06:32:22.922Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/KUtClCaQ#unRWehDP1Mf4TxAhPlU4ZA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>149</airingId>
    <content>This time, we focus on Hasegawa Hiroki, a fish broker who has charmed many a top-class chef. Finding value in fish that are normally thrown away, he brings out their true flavor as if by magic. What he seeks is "vitality." In pursuit of the finest fish, he even takes to the sea himself, free-diving in order to catch the expensive leopard coral grouper. Despite being a broker, he throws himself into the depths to experience the ultimate battle with fish. However, there was once a time when Hasegawa roamed the city with "the eyes of a dead fish." Spend a summer with this one-of-a-kind broker -- he'll light a fire in your heart!</content>
    <description>Favored by top chefs, fish broker Hasegawa Hiroki magically brings out the value in disregarded fish. We spend a summer with him as he pursues fish with vitality, even taking to the sea himself.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-14T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wIo30C5R#zXMalZD32GdhowGgsU05lg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-14T01:55:27.449Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-14T01:09:20.131Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>c755846ed6a88ab12c0e7495517cbcfc6441dd357dbce5d6534fe71077a4bf4f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-14T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Living Life Feeling Alive: Hasegawa Hiroki, Fish Broker</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T04:27:21.922Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FEwHlA4Z#_-1HtcZLI2RYhWldbZh_EQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>150</airingId>
    <content>Meet a famous Hakone bus driver! Omori Toru (62) has 40 years of driving experience. He has the technical skills to navigate Hakone's sharp curves and steep hills, and a warm consideration for his passengers' needs. He's been a part of the region's public transport network for decades and is proud of supporting everyday life. As the pandemic turns our attention to the essential workers we've long overlooked, meet a man who quietly dedicated his career to supporting the truly important aspects of our day-to-day lives.</content>
    <description>Omori Toru is a 40-year veteran bus driver who navigates sharp curves and steep hills and offers warm consideration to his passengers. He's proud of supporting everyday life in spite of the pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-07T01:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Sog2CBBS#hnbsKSEM2HDfMgtuFiwJvQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-07T01:55:27.922Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-07T01:09:20.151Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>8332dc705e15ab1d272d92af3a6b1eef15a6cf72a12cbcd982791c6d05258e0f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-07T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Keeping Things Running: Omori Toru, Bus Driver</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-07T03:11:26.106Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ZTgwWBhJ#pukgQJElHHKGh9BjLcHoHw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>151</airingId>
    <content>We follow Kawada Tomoya (37), an up-and-coming Chinese cuisine chef with rave reviews by 3-star chefs! Blending traditional Chinese cooking with Japanese techniques, he's gaining fame worldwide with a new Chinese cuisine that epitomizes "Japanese spirit, Chinese learning." In order to serve customers dishes at the best possible moment, the staff rush about the kitchen, never wasting even a single minute or second. What inspired this was a meal by a master chef that changed Kawada's life. We follow this passionate man for a summer as he takes on a challenge, tirelessly trying new experiments and pursuing cuisine with wholehearted honesty.</content>
    <description>3-star chefs approve! This up-and-coming chef is gaining fame worldwide by blending Chinese cuisine with Japanese techniques. What beliefs inspire his honest approach to cooking and drive to improve?</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-04T09:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Kd9ygZ4R#giSGlq6FkLpRQ8OCnGyR4Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-04T09:55:30.607Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-04T09:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>936dd9018534b841c7691ab03368bf4a9e363a202840e90adc082b2c5cae96e8</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-04T09:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>For a Dish That Will Fill Hearts with Wonder: Kawada Tomoya, Chinese Cuisine Chef</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-04T13:29:19.316Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/49YB1AYK#BqpZ7ONc0OuroeBTfpeJ5w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>152</airingId>
    <content>Yokohama produces 1.22 million tons of garbage a year, the most of any municipality in Japan. Collection expert Take Yusuke is the ace of the city's biggest waste collection firm. He spends hours every day picking up over 3 tons of garbage a day from businesses like restaurants and hospitals. He has various tricks to prioritize efficiency, but that's not all that matters to him. Discover his essential work behind the scenes of our daily lives.</content>
    <description>Yokohama produces 1.22 million tons of garbage a year. Take Yusuke is a garbage collector who picks up over 3 tons a day on his own. Discover his work behind the scenes of our daily lives.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-11T02:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/nAwV3SAS#Z292m_m6ji38HulBA_vZVw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-11T02:55:29.636Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-11T02:09:22.553Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4003</seriesId>
    <sha256>19f78be3752761c340cb3249f2c909e6f8d673ce8e3041650575fd20f6445eb3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-11T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Picking Yourself Up to Carry Dreams: Garbage Collector, Take Yusuke</subtitle>
    <title>The Professionals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-11T08:08:57.770Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jVBn2CTR#wOz6rW3eYjX2d1sIergTqw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>