<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-24T00:00:04.206Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>aca3c5281f781918</seriesId>
  <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>This episode features Ekiben, the boxed meals sold at railroad stations that add flavor, beauty and fun to a journey. The meals tend to feature local ingredients and come in a range of distinctive containers and wrapping papers. We look at an aficionado who has sampled all 4,500 different versions of Ekiben around Japan, and who makes a point of savoring these meals as the scenery unfolds from the train window. We focus on a homely version of Ekiben from the Tsugaru region of northern Honshu, and delve into history of some other famous versions from around Japan. Along the way, we introduce you to specialists crafting the wrapping papers.</content>
    <description>Take a trip on a railroad and revel in the ever-changing scenery. Perfect to complement such a trip is Ekiben, or box lunch sold at stations. Join us as we set out to enjoy flavors across Japan.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-01T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VZ13ECAA#ukyenze1APPuCWlctF7rDw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-01T05:00:28.862Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-01T04:29:20.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>6f0e08ca290669668b49f10290f58e903ee7c7e917dde997cf4d4616120b5481</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-01T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ekiben Box Lunch</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-01T06:00:17.305Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/88x0WIRb#jHnSZBuq360srADQltU5Gg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>085</airingId>
    <content>Bashofu is a traditional Okinawan fabric, which originated about 600 years ago when the islands formed the independent Ryukyu Kingdom. The stalks of a species of banana plant are the source of the fibers, which are painstakingly knotted together into longer strands of thread. The knots are visible in the woven fabric. Bashofu is ideal for the local climate and is treasured by kimono buffs across Japan. This episode looks at some of the distinctive local Kasuri designs in which different colored fibers are used to create patterns and images in the fabric. We also introduce attempts to reproduce the fabric of the old kingdom from precious remaining samples.</content>
    <description>Bashofu is a fabric born in Okinawa with 600 years of history. The light and airy fabric is perfect for the hot and humid climate of the islands. Let us weave our way through its charms.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T17:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/YMwS2ITb#c68hTzGarbJXN4VESprBnA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T17:00:28.119Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-23T16:29:20.142Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>d3dcd4b9f2955a8c4bfb69c05c9afa8a2731d8bc5ddde9c000a097124b7f09d0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-23T16:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bashofu Fabric</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:05:53.594Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jNNRCI5b#Q7ZdQUvLKkTydyzDz17V-Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>087</airingId>
    <content>Japan is home to all kinds of libraries. The episode features some unique examples across the country, including some historic structuring giving a sense of the periods in which they were built, as well as some futuristic facilities. We visit a library resembling a spaceship amongst trees. Inside is a forest of books stretching for 200m. We look at a university library shaped like the Colosseum of Rome, a place where the intellect engages in combat. Wonder at the futuristic library designed by Shigeru Ban that looks like something out of a science-fiction film. And we look at the transformation of an old spinning mill and an old primary school, the former of brick construction and the latter built entirely from cypress wood, into reading spaces.</content>
    <description>The library offers much more than just books; it is a place that satisfies intellectual curiosity and one that enriches people's lives in many ways. Tune in for a chapter on the library.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-08T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ippiCa6Q#r7miZRl8K7ia45oBPeG7pA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-08T05:00:33.071Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-08T04:29:20.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>c528595e224337b57865b9535403b9ba866dc0edbe024178fe59e23a86d680d6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-08T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Library</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-08T06:30:54.334Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jk9FlKrJ#GnDX0zHuw8DLgPg_4yTUVg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>109</airingId>
    <content>This episode provides a taste of sake, or Japanese rice wine. It visits an old, traditional-style earthen-walled brewery, looking at the reason for its high ceilings, and the role played by the inner storeroom. Elsewhere, a brewery whose history spans more than 250 years is maturing its sake in a disused railway tunnel. Also featured is the traditional method for producing the koji mold essential to sake brewing, and the new sake aromas resulting from koji obtained from flowers. There are some new and daring pairings of sake, food and tableware as well.</content>
    <description>The craft of brewing sake, Japan's very own alcoholic drink goes back centuries. While traditional techniques continue to be used, there are those who are making new sake for the people of today.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SQkXjIAQ#du70aqz2pHnRQhgd6I_BOg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T05:01:00.908Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-21T04:29:22.782Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>b8bb627001e790e1367508e2cebed5a5bfe00586dca6163b770731161c8ceb6e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-21T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sake</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T07:50:26.906Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/J9lCVazZ#YcORI54VqF92cl0jdd99kg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>111</airingId>
    <content>This episode features fragrances that can immediately evoke spring. We focus on the lavish bouquets of a Paris-based floral artist that look and smell like a spring garden, as well as pretty art nouveau-style perfume bottles and the quest to produce unique fragrances that express the motions of this season. In Japan, where the appreciation of fragrances has developed into an art form, devotees rely on small fragrant pieces of wood to evoke the plum blossoms that appear in spring. The knack is sensing the plum blossoms without them actually being there. Various smells in the woods and mountains herald the arrival of spring, stirring memories of home, as well as stirring the appetite.</content>
    <description>The arrival of spring is always signaled by the fresh scents that waft from nature. This episode shines light on kodo, the Japanese art of recreating, appreciating and describing such fragrances.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4dYwjLSa#rXeihGDMvZ98fFj2xbRysA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T05:00:29.795Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-28T04:29:22.568Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>bba6de7f94633a2503f1fecf65672e0e672ad9ab8eab33c07051b11b59934e55</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-28T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fragrances of Early Spring</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T22:30:08.080Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5dFwgTpI#qj9VE1e0n5Sok1PeFPsLGg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>112</airingId>
    <content>This episode features earth globes. The copywriter Itoi Shigesato tells us what inspired him to develop a state-of-the-art version relying on augmented reality. The astronaut Mori Mamoru shows a treasured globe he used during his training, and talks about a massive version measuring more than 6m across fashioned from organic light-emitting diode panels. And we take a look at some extraordinary, fold-up versions inspired by traditional-style umbrellas from the Edo period (1603-1868), and a firm that has been handcrafting globes for more than 80 years.</content>
    <description>For centuries, people have made globes, not just as an educational tool, but also as an item to feel closer to the world. This episode features handcrafted globes to the latest high-tech globes.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-04T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/U59AXIIZ#LnOdhtQjhILIGpf2iJRE2g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-04T05:00:33.305Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-04T04:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>4877bb78313fa6d142f25c2e5155232d603e143a6ace83f86e5ba1fb3a5fb083</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-04T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Globe</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T08:10:24.003Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gQ1QFIbb#UwjqvrgCJ0A4x9ngCCHl_A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>114</airingId>
    <content>This episode takes us on a journey into some of the little known aspects of Shigaraki ware. This pottery was featured in the NHK morning drama series "Scarlet." Shigaraki jars, both of the narrow- and wide-mouthed kind, have been praised by devotees of the tea ceremony as espousing the aesthetics of "hie" (chill) and "kare" (wither). The best examples of Shigaraki ware are said to have been produced prior to circa 1700. They are distinguished by their firing techniques called "yaki-shime." Kawase Toshiro, a master of flower arrangement, produces some floral displays using antique Shigaraki vases. We look at the versatile nature of the clay used in Shigaraki ware that potters find so attractive, and also feature a Shigaraki-ware bath soothing to body and soul.</content>
    <description>The Shigaraki ware is pottery that originated in 13th century Japan. Its rustic appeal has long been adored by tea ceremony practitioners and everyday people alike for ages; tune in to find out why.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-25T17:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/l74kyCba#fVnQhAcRqPy0dgkX_9LGQw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-25T17:00:41.869Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-25T16:29:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>6861b71a62e17a3f5942f1873c833bf11ff154eae2c346e46567550c9591419c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-25T16:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shigaraki Ware</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-26T00:24:47.301Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/NRpxzYpA#UdlPwLoUXqk9f4ZQHGPyVw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>115</airingId>
    <content>Small things are always somehow enchanting. This episode explores the whimsy world of miniatures. We delve into the astonishing skill required to fashion a tiny bowl of noodles that can be perched on a finger. It looks just like the real thing, even down to the glistening noodles and soup. And we take a look at a range of tiny toys, which came about after the 18th century Shogun issued an edict against extravagance and luxury, as well as a witty health charm in the shape of a red owl. Emperor Napoleon was among those fascinated by miniature books - they resemble tiny works of art. We peek inside what appears to be just an ordinary wall socket to see what is causing such a sensation on social media. Also featured is miniature scenery in pots and tiny bonsai that give a soothing touch to any surroundings.</content>
    <description>From small toys, to recreations of epic scenery on a tray, miniature items have a powerful, timeless appeal. Join us for this episode as we shrink into the fascinating world of miniatures.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-15T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/nN9SmKhD#AD9oX-8gzBAv2apmhwbiVA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-15T05:00:29.097Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-15T04:29:20.070Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>c029fd30f45da7bc60289394bb9d52f2e294f8a23501dbe8a8741424658d2b04</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-15T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miniatures</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T06:07:47.151Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/O4RDGIAL#oWkixb5czqMfhQhAU8-t3g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>116</airingId>
    <content>This episode features staircases of the kind that somehow beckon people to ascend them. Architect Ando Tadao keenly describes his ideal stairs. A visit is made to some staircases highly recommended by fans. We take a look at a large theatrical set of stairs that has appeared in Tokyo's Kyobashi district. And we delve into the intricacies of the traditional-style stairs at the teahouse in Yokohama's Sankeien Garden and Nijojinya, which was the home of a rich merchant in Kyoto. Viewers can admire the beauty of the drawers and shelving that built into the stairs in the smaller townhouses of other Kyoto merchants to make effective use of the limited amount of space in the city. The craftsmen who fashioned such staircases had an eye for detail. We look at the skill that produced the beautiful curves in the wooden handrails and the clever way in which the stairs were organized to accommodate drawers and shelving.</content>
    <description>Stairways are very practical, but that's not all they are. At times, they can be exciting gateways that lead us into the unknown. Join us for a climb up the magnificent world of stairs.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-22T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/lZ9wxQpZ#MFEY0UYnaMXlNTw-KxUcsg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-22T05:00:31.622Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-22T04:29:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>9c2b48c3edeae52d38f91776ea5a7cb9a9d46a8d484a1c18f0518bff75cca76a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-22T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Stairs</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-22T06:28:14.358Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/PFkQ0CxD#6jW0wK6bEStZMNhL5aOecA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>117</airingId>
    <content>This episode features Bingata, the Okinawan dyed fabrics renowned for their vivid patterns and vibrant colors. We look at some examples, listed as national treasures, which recall the splendor and pomp of the Ryukyu Kingdom. Only royalty was granted the privilege of wearing one particular color. We look at the techniques for producing the vivid reds and the motifs inspired by the natural surroundings. After the devastating Battle of Okinawa in 1945, people resorted to some unexpected things for dyeing scarce fabrics. And we feature the tapestries fashioned by a 16th generation artisan committed to reviving Bingata. The 2019 fire which destroyed Shuri Castle, the seat of the Ryukyu Kingdom, has prompted the artisan to break new ground.</content>
    <description>Bingata, the Okinawan dyed fabric, has stayed relevant in its homeland for over 500 years. Its vivid colors and delicate patterns are manifestations of the beautiful climate and culture of Okinawa.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-30T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4M0lFYSD#mhg1iqSk7KNBfI0rv2pFAg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-30T05:00:33.095Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-30T04:29:20.060Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>d732268bc4496e7588b1b5ec7071f3a3cf229cb229b5bb2c384994e13bafe8ba</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-30T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bingata</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T07:49:16.266Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wVkXVYDK#WpGJH_nzVPvOhpNLPJx69Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>118</airingId>
    <content>This episode features Wasarasa, or Japanese-style chintz. These printed fabrics originated in India, and subsequently evolved into unique styles in Japan. We take part in a tea ceremony performed by the Issa-an school of sencha tea ceremony that makes lavish use of chintz. And we look at the pattern sheets (more than 200 of them!) and the brushwork required for a premium-quality chintz kimono. We meet an up-and-coming artisan who is reviving 1,400-year-old designs. Also featured is the chintz supplied to the Nabeshima clan, which ruled over what is now Saga Prefecture. The techniques were kept secret and were only rediscovered again when certain texts came to light in the Showa period (1926-1989). We admire some woodblock-printed examples of the Nabeshima-style chintz produced by an artisan designated as a National Living Treasure.</content>
    <description>Wasarasa is Japanese dyed fabric inspired by Indian chintz, and often necessitates the use of many stencils. With its exotic look, it continues to charm, especially sencha tea ceremony practitioners.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-05T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0UEHCaKa#txeybItFAApSppMN-aa0fA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-05T05:00:27.931Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-05T04:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>b61f2a5d1a385fb79bb491f679f97a4c3a1bb1e86b7911098ee57f459b00c2af</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-05T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Wasarasa</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-05T06:12:19.758Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YME3HY4b#SxWEMGmRmhiuamR5e6_HUA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>120</airingId>
    <content>This episode features Japanese swords. We look at Chikakage, a sword of the 16th-century warlord Akechi Mitsuhide, which was discovered in 2019, and ponder what he might have thought about this weapon. We delve into the fascinating craftsmanship that goes into forging the ultimate sword. The Hon'ami Family has been polishing and sharpening swords since the Muromachi Period (1336-1573). The current head of the family, who has been designated as one of Japan's Living Treasures, shows us what this craft involves. An accomplished sword drawer shows off his swordsmanship and how the forms of swords have evolved over the ages. Also featured is a sword dating from the Heian Period (794-1185). Its scabbard, featuring the oldest extant feline motif in Japan, is a national treasure. A fictional swordsman and computer game character Mikazuki Munechika, who has taken his name from another well-known weapon, makes his appearance.</content>
    <description>The Japanese sword has long been admired across the world as both an excellent weapon and an exquisite work of art. Tune in to find out the secret behind its beautiful glow.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-07T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xclznS4J#TuGobn_VTlvheJpAuZKY5Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-07T05:00:16.282Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-07T04:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>a2dcb4b96afd74fbf79746a505fe71c835aab617b9951dd1b4d9dca74463013d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-07T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Japanese Sword</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T06:10:31.908Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JM9nBYZb#3fqPrX8WR3IpkFG0xOSFtw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>121</airingId>
    <content>This episode features zori, or the flat, thonged sandals that have evolved with the Japanese lifestyle. The variety of materials used for the soles and the thong straps provide limitless opportunities for design. Dr. Robert Campbell, an authority on Japanese literature, describes how this footwear is a living tradition. 2 brothers, who have been crafting zori for 60 years, show us sandals offering the ultimate in comfort. And a Kyoto-based footwear store, which has been in business for more than 100 years, shows how it produces its beautifully crafted and functional thong straps. Also featured are the tatami-padded sandals with straw straps, which are worn by the referees for sumo bouts.</content>
    <description>Zori sandals have long kept Japanese feet happy. Not only is it a fashion item that comes in many styles, it also has a cultural role. Tune in to step into the comfy appeal of zori sandals.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/DkECXZRK#d7IuPDeEgAc4SfmKA5xr0A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T05:00:28.105Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-14T04:29:22.775Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>206a34e1cbedd200f9ea4e68a8f263d3f1f4fd20980e1543fa64e955a6056c80</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-14T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Zori Sandals</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T03:07:46.408Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/RNM2kTgI#IPassARFF51oUMPQ0k271w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>122</airingId>
    <content>This episode features mushrooms, which have been part of the Japanese diet since pre-historic times. We look at some exquisite dishes from a French restaurant that is fussy about its mushrooms, as well as a superb mushroom hotpot of the kind prepared by the hunters who move through the mountain forests in the Tohoku region. An expert shows some unusual fungi, including a species on Hachijo Island that glows in the dark. An internationally renowned botanical artist specializing in fungi reveals the intricacies of these organisms, and takes us through the illustrated encyclopedia compiled by the great polymath Minakata Kumagusu (1867-1941) that features 4,000 different specimens. The Kyogen performer Nomura Mansai visits the home of our host Kusakari Masao in the guise of a mountain hermit.</content>
    <description>Japan is home to a variety of mushrooms. From those that look like eggs to those resemble corals, mushrooms come in many shapes and colors. Tune in to find out what make them so special.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-01T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/gm43wSzA#WiKS5D9e-s1GhAidAkmbjg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-01T05:00:28.976Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-01T04:29:23.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>b94de70532855084a2b69795b5ccfe06e271d12cb5c0b8395b0023391ac0ddc0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-01T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mushrooms of Japan</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-01T06:14:16.353Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/2mIxDaiS#HDdzS21Zmhc3US3sWu8Suw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>123</airingId>
    <content>This episode looks at Japanese-style check patterns (Ichimatsu-moyo). The Kyogen performer Shigeyama Ippei is a great fan. His daily wardrobe, from his suits to his socks, features checks. He shows us some of his favorite items that have been with him for 20 years. Check patterns appear on pottery vessels and figures from Japan's pre-historic era, as well as in the prints of the ukiyo-e artist Toshusai Sharaku, who was active in the late 18th century. We take a look at some stylish black-checked glassware, as well as some examples of Kutani ware. The check patterns of the latter, made up of 3,500 tiny squares, appear to move. The grandson of the landscaper Shigemori Mirei (1896-1975) tells us about the check-pattern garden his grandfather designed for Tofuku-ji Temple in Kyoto Prefecture. And we take a look at some check-pattern sliding doors in an old house.</content>
    <description>The Ichimatsu, or check pattern is seen on ukiyo-e and older works of art, as well as on the latest pieces of Japanese modern art. Tune in to find out the timeless appeal of this  pattern.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-08T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/x1pGSZpb#_WTxzqDjVXnmg8A6nDz3aA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-08T05:00:28.554Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-08T04:29:20.028Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>25ead9125e5aabce390d6fabe26e242a8ebf7affd6f351820564a49a065cc312</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-08T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ichimatsu Pattern</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-09T08:11:33.045Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5tonkAba#qlRO9OGqLY438nDrIGuW0A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>124</airingId>
    <content>Urushi or Japanese lacquer combines beauty and utility. It has been recognized as an intangible cultural asset by UNESCO. The Joboji-machi district in Iwate Prefecture is a source for high-quality, domestically produced lacquer. It is a scarce commodity, accounting for only 2% of the lacquer used in Japan. According to the lacquer tappers, a drop of lacquer sap is as precious as a drop of human blood. The area is famous for the lacquerware bowls associated with the local Joboji Temple. Also featured are some lacquerware speakers. They look good and sound good too! We visit a house in Sabae, Fukui Prefecture being decorated with lacquered walls and floors, which are likely to take one hundred years to complete. We also take a look at the amazingly designed round lacquerware lunchboxes traditionally used by the timber merchants in the Owase area in Mie Prefecture. And we feature the conservation work on the lacquered surfaces of the Toshogu Shrine in Nikko, which has been ongoing since the complex was built in the Edo period.</content>
    <description>Lacquer,the oldest varnish in Japan, has long been used for a variety of items. It offers not only beautiful gloss, but also practical advantages. Come and experience the world of Japanese lacquer.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-29T17:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/S45S3AhB#di99fGgsNKDyPg5nqUl1pQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-29T17:00:29.681Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-29T16:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>774dc1b87e517029a948063d866f369fcc622ea4c843012c4bedd7c5739d31b8</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-29T16:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Japanese Lacquer</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-29T19:24:07.893Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6YEBhKCL#9fE5QVBsnet5E7I1pi_wZg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>125</airingId>
    <content>This episode provides a behind-the-scenes look at maiko or the apprentice geisha of Kyoto's Gion district. We look at various aspects of their attire. Why, for example, do they only apply rouge to their bottom lip? Unlike geisha, maiko do not wear wigs; their elaborate hairstyle is done with their own hair. We see maiko undergoing an arduous dance lesson presided over by Inoue Yachiyo V, a master of dance and designated National Treasure. In the last 10 days of their apprenticeship, the maiko wear particular kimono and hairstyles and do special dances. We look at why they blacken their teeth. And we follow maiko on the final day of their apprenticeship when they take part in a ceremony to mark their transition to geisha.</content>
    <description>Maikos, or apprentice geishas, bestow elegance upon Kyoto. They wear traditional Japanese hairstyles and kimono as they train for years in performing arts to one day become professional entertainers.</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-03T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/GrZGHTAB#2HV51EstFJDulTv5zm_G0Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-03T05:00:33.662Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-03T04:29:20.042Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>9df39b533abcb0667cd6d45666bc85e2b318ece9e2a5055531937ccb373da1f2</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-03T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Maiko</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-03T06:15:48.035Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/LmRSULRK#JmMXBJRCGZIqRu10wN_99A</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>