<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T05:40:02.596Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>aca3c5281f781918</seriesId>
  <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>085</airingId>
    <content>Bashofu is a traditional Okinawan fabric, which originated about 600 years ago when the islands formed the independent Ryukyu Kingdom. The stalks of a species of banana plant are the source of the fibers, which are painstakingly knotted together into longer strands of thread. The knots are visible in the woven fabric. Bashofu is ideal for the local climate and is treasured by kimono buffs across Japan. This episode looks at some of the distinctive local Kasuri designs in which different colored fibers are used to create patterns and images in the fabric. We also introduce attempts to reproduce the fabric of the old kingdom from precious remaining samples.</content>
    <description>Bashofu is a fabric born in Okinawa with 600 years of history. The light and airy fabric is perfect for the hot and humid climate of the islands. Let us weave our way through its charms.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T17:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/YMwS2ITb#c68hTzGarbJXN4VESprBnA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T17:00:28.119Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-23T16:29:20.142Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>d3dcd4b9f2955a8c4bfb69c05c9afa8a2731d8bc5ddde9c000a097124b7f09d0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-23T16:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bashofu Fabric</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T08:05:53.594Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/jNNRCI5b#Q7ZdQUvLKkTydyzDz17V-Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>109</airingId>
    <content>This episode provides a taste of sake, or Japanese rice wine. It visits an old, traditional-style earthen-walled brewery, looking at the reason for its high ceilings, and the role played by the inner storeroom. Elsewhere, a brewery whose history spans more than 250 years is maturing its sake in a disused railway tunnel. Also featured is the traditional method for producing the koji mold essential to sake brewing, and the new sake aromas resulting from koji obtained from flowers. There are some new and daring pairings of sake, food and tableware as well.</content>
    <description>The craft of brewing sake, Japan's very own alcoholic drink goes back centuries. While traditional techniques continue to be used, there are those who are making new sake for the people of today.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-21T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SQkXjIAQ#du70aqz2pHnRQhgd6I_BOg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-21T05:01:00.908Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-21T04:29:22.782Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>b8bb627001e790e1367508e2cebed5a5bfe00586dca6163b770731161c8ceb6e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-21T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sake</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T07:50:26.906Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>111</airingId>
    <content>This episode features fragrances that can immediately evoke spring. We focus on the lavish bouquets of a Paris-based floral artist that look and smell like a spring garden, as well as pretty art nouveau-style perfume bottles and the quest to produce unique fragrances that express the motions of this season. In Japan, where the appreciation of fragrances has developed into an art form, devotees rely on small fragrant pieces of wood to evoke the plum blossoms that appear in spring. The knack is sensing the plum blossoms without them actually being there. Various smells in the woods and mountains herald the arrival of spring, stirring memories of home, as well as stirring the appetite.</content>
    <description>The arrival of spring is always signaled by the fresh scents that waft from nature. This episode shines light on kodo, the Japanese art of recreating, appreciating and describing such fragrances.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-28T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4dYwjLSa#rXeihGDMvZ98fFj2xbRysA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-28T05:00:29.795Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-28T04:29:22.568Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>bba6de7f94633a2503f1fecf65672e0e672ad9ab8eab33c07051b11b59934e55</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-28T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fragrances of Early Spring</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T22:30:08.080Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5dFwgTpI#qj9VE1e0n5Sok1PeFPsLGg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>121</airingId>
    <content>This episode features zori, or the flat, thonged sandals that have evolved with the Japanese lifestyle. The variety of materials used for the soles and the thong straps provide limitless opportunities for design. Dr. Robert Campbell, an authority on Japanese literature, describes how this footwear is a living tradition. 2 brothers, who have been crafting zori for 60 years, show us sandals offering the ultimate in comfort. And a Kyoto-based footwear store, which has been in business for more than 100 years, shows how it produces its beautifully crafted and functional thong straps. Also featured are the tatami-padded sandals with straw straps, which are worn by the referees for sumo bouts.</content>
    <description>Zori sandals have long kept Japanese feet happy. Not only is it a fashion item that comes in many styles, it also has a cultural role. Tune in to step into the comfy appeal of zori sandals.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-14T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/DkECXZRK#d7IuPDeEgAc4SfmKA5xr0A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-14T05:00:28.105Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-14T04:29:22.775Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4018</seriesId>
    <sha256>206a34e1cbedd200f9ea4e68a8f263d3f1f4fd20980e1543fa64e955a6056c80</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-14T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Zori Sandals</subtitle>
    <title>The Mark of Beauty</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T03:07:46.408Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/RNM2kTgI#IPassARFF51oUMPQ0k271w</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>