<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-01T07:15:03.999Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>aefa3128a4eaf8eb</seriesId>
  <title>Somewhere Street</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>053</airingId>
    <content>Hakodate is the entryway to Japan's northern island, Hokkaido and it's around 4 hours from Tokyo by Shinkansen. It was one of the first ports in Japan to be built for international trade. This program will take you to the beautiful streets in Hakodate!</content>
    <description>Hakodate is the entryway to Japan's northern island, Hokkaido and it was one of the first ports in Japan to be built for international trade. Let's stroll about through Hakodate's streets!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-29T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Cp8V3QBa#mXqykb7vhN8LxZuteuGf2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-29T15:00:26.275Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T14:09:20.061Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>f995946035d3df66ad14bb09e13b4c0a704f432bcd63f0f67af5bb1ba70701f8</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hakodate, Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T09:26:24.721Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/EZhAhS6Y#oKJhRnCsM8jLqNkXL9ER7Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>054</airingId>
    <content>San Marino is the capital of the Republic of San Marino, which lies in the middle of the Italian peninsula. It's the oldest surviving republic in the world with a medieval feel and its town atop the cliff is registered as a World Heritage Site. Although it's surrounded by Italy, San Marino has maintained its independence for 1,700 years. Let's take a stroll in San Marino streets!</content>
    <description>San Marino is the capital of the Republic of San Marino and the oldest surviving republic in the world, lying in the middle of the Italian peninsula. Let's take a stroll in San Marino streets!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-27T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KA0h2IrK#Ubj-YsUGkTGUucAEKeAX6g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-27T05:00:22.851Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T04:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>3e796faf6e2bf8d2d64b9160dc9d22327e5a02d41ada353855ce7189746be0e6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>San Marino</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:00:55.161Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/59EBQSba#acaXOKcpGARa8t-yxAAG0w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>082</airingId>
    <content>Centrally located with an easily accessible port, Vietnam's Da Nang is one of the country's most popular beach resorts. During the Vietnam War, it served as an important base of operations for the U.S. Forces until the war ended in 1975. The city experienced difficulty with its recovery after the war, until the year 2000, when the city was redeveloped as a beach resort. Da Nang is now a dream vacation spot for international travelers. In this episode we walk around exploring the Da Nang, meeting its inhabitants who love their traditions and are also delighted with the new face of the city.</content>
    <description>A recent development boom has contributed to Da Nang's rise as one of Vietnam's most popular beach resorts. In this episode we explore the city while meeting with residents enjoying life in Da Nang.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/tAoTmYKB#uciPF_3Ph6dgH68MGtRuBA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T15:00:25.499Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T14:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>7b2e8a8bbbf6216175eeba73f1a6e0092a9bc983d2827288e6a8e890fbf357b1</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Da Nang, Vietnam</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T09:27:28.463Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ZA1g3JLQ#NraimKbWEWsl19GkVldMuA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>Venice is a beachfront neighborhood located on the west side of Los Angeles, California. Known for its beaches, canals that were created in imitation of Venice, Italy, and Ocean Front Walk that attracts the young and trendy who love sports, the arts and the free-wheeling atmosphere, Venice is one of LA's most free spirited and forward-thinking areas. In this episode we stroll through the neighborhood meeting locals who share the lifestyles that they enjoy as residents of Venice.</content>
    <description>Venice, a beachfront neighborhood on the west side of Los Angeles, is one of LA's most popular neighborhoods. In this episode we explore the town, meeting residents who enjoy their Venice lifestyle.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-22T15:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/C4Vk3bTb#F2Fq-6l4uBAptjSlt2PsQw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-22T15:00:25.101Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T14:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>83974d2b09d0ecf634a46927fc039a6a003b99b62bee16dd2cfdfa78cd09b6c0</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T14:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Venice, Los Angeles, US</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:54:09.042Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/z0UylJbA#nM_PuT4A9P7agX6ZWgCNfg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>107</airingId>
    <content>The city of Zanzibar is the heart of Zanzibar, an island in Tanzania on the east coast of Africa. A trade hub for India, Arabia and Europe, in the 19th century it became a British protectorate. The protectorate ended in 1963 and the following year Zanzibar joined the United Republic of Tanzania. It's a place of diverse cultures living together in harmony. Its historic Stone Town is a World Heritage Site. The beautiful beaches in this Indian Ocean attract tourists from all over the world.</content>
    <description>The city of Zanzibar is the heart of Zanzibar, an island in Tanzania on the east coast of Africa. A famed hub for trade from India, Arabia and Europe, its historic Stone Town is a World Heritage Site.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-06T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hk9Q3SRR#e1H9grQqlWug6p25_ICALw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-06T05:00:23.324Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-06T04:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>80d34354a04c4ea6518569a5072dd7d83ad19f413195d533fe5647eff3f746c1</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-06T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Zanzibar, Tanzania</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T09:16:33.151Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/pZpGWRoT#aRUeoHZbnI0Uy2BXgwNUTg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>109</airingId>
    <content>Located 1,500 meters above sea level in Vietnam's Central Highlands, the city of Da Lat was developed in the 19th century by the French as a "heavenly paradise" resort. It is now a favorite honeymoon destination and resort center welcoming over 5 million visitors every year. With an average temperature of about 20 degrees Celsius, the climate is favorable for cultivating domestic and foreign flowers. Due to the number of beautiful flowers adorning the city, Da Lat is known as a romantic flower paradise.</content>
    <description>Located 1,500 meters above sea level in Vietnam's Central Highlands, Da Lat was developed in the 19th century by the French as a "heavenly paradise" resort. It welcomes over 5 million visitors a year.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-20T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/m4sDXSSD#F0bJ3EHLuaXoF35N9aiFbQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-20T05:01:09.868Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T04:09:23.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4017</seriesId>
    <sha256>7ebedb786b6c7e2e66885d996ba2db7685f470916bbc891b31e0756bf9fc8cbb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Da Lat, Vietnam</subtitle>
    <title>Somewhere Street</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T09:27:31.745Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Z91z1SwL#TNYzITNvXydYY4LR05W2AA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>