<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-25T01:55:03.227Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>b2d48e71e072a1aa</seriesId>
  <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>049</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Tokachi Plain in eastern Hokkaido Prefecture. The plain is one of the largest dry field farming lands in Japan and is covered in snow during the wintertime. Our program host, Charlotte Kate Fox, tries dog sledding for the first time, and races through the snowy landscape pulled by dogs. She also tries famous soba noodles made with buckwheat grown during the season without snow, encounters squirrels in a park, and enjoys the charms of the Tokachi Plain to its fullest. Additionally, we show you valuable footage of animals living in windbreaks.</content>
    <description>Tokachi Plain in eastern Hokkaido is one of the largest dry field farming lands in Japan and is covered in snow during the wintertime. Our program host tries dog sledding for the first time.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-21T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/x9MF1CzZ#hKh9bnq2c5UgbFg9cPY-_w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-21T01:00:23.863Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-21T00:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>3e5dede5d7d6b37ec22afde660a322a25134adc4ce1d34f2f910211f44bb92e0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-21T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Tokachi Plain in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-21T01:49:53.598Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TBEDnYLZ#Po5TSQ9cZPUV-cNEgLHFCA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>050</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Kushiro Wetland, Japan's largest wetland. Our program host, Charlotte Kate Fox, rides a canoe to explore the river that never freezes even in winter because of the abundant springs. She encounters Japan's largest bird of prey, the Steller's sea eagle, and sees a dynamic view of the frozen lake, where ice cracks have risen up. Additionally, we show you precious footage of red-crowned cranes that live in the wetlands.</content>
    <description>Kushiro Wetland is Japan's largest wetland. Our program host rides a canoe to explore the river that never freezes even in winter, and  encounters a large bird of prey, the Stellar's Sea Eagle.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-28T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SxF0QRZY#iIMUs-HuaaF-qBlrNnY5nQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-28T01:00:24.444Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-28T00:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>fa29bba1da5268f646a5ec8560e6769f8219cb02f82c939a5eb7d588342302ee</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-28T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kushiro Wetland in Harsh Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-28T01:56:16.568Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/kkB0FTZK#13R_K2GEkMtlqguaVo0dNA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>051</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Mt. Tomuraushi in the very center of Hokkaido Prefecture. It's considered impassable during the harsh winter months, while the forest at its foot is good for trekking. Our program host, Charlotte Kate Fox, dons snow shoes and treks the forest covered with a blanket of snow. On her way to the waterfall that never freezes even during winter, she also observes snow crystals and bear claw scratches on a tree. In addition, we show you rare footage of spotted nutcracker dwelling in the forest.</content>
    <description>Mt. Tomuraushi is considered impassable during the winter months, while the forest at its foot is good for trekking. Our program host dons snow shoes and treks the forest covered with snow.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-21T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/v5kU3K5Q#WIby3BA4COl4QZCTXWQTew</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-21T01:00:30.361Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-21T00:44:20.108Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>250873a3fbd1a1931e7b80d804d3d33f1c2f6001c9f6724970142db1878bae6c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-21T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mt. Tomuraushi in Harsh Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T16:37:45.253Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>060</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Mashu, a caldera lake and its surrounds in eastern Hokkaido Prefecture. Our program host climbs Mt. Mashudake near the lake. On his way to the summit of the mountain, he comes across some summertime alpine flowers. After walking for about 4 hours, he finally reaches the summit, where a superb view overlooking Lake Mashu spreads out before his eyes. Later, we show you rare footage of a variety of creatures that survive in the plentiful spring water in the forest surrounding Lake Mashu.</content>
    <description>Our stage this time is Lake Mashu, a caldera lake and its surrounds in eastern Hokkaido Prefecture. Our program host climbs Mt. Mashudake near the lake, enjoying some summertime alpine flowers.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-15T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7YskwLaA#foe5SvlDNbuVEi6_7QRkWg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-15T07:00:27.954Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-15T06:44:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>db9288ed70e4ae2d87fad64ceb600a5375d812c3454b1ae24bc183878acbdb28</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-15T06:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mashu</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T01:00:59.077Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IQlS0CqA#r2r9SPuNiWCDvN-HyFXYvA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>061</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Sapporo, a capital city of Hokkaido Prefecture. To the west of Sapporo's city center are many mountains, where you can fully enjoy its rich nature. Our program host treks through the mountain path that leads from locally popular Mt. Sankakuyama to Mt. Okurayama, and encounters a variety of plants as well as wildlife along the way. Further, a spectacular view awaits him at the summit. Later, we show you rare footage of local wildlife in the Toyohira River, which flows through the city and is a source of sustenance for them.</content>
    <description>To the west of Sapporo's city center are many mountains, where you can fully enjoy its rich nature. Our program host treks through the mountain path, and encounters a variety of wildlife.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-22T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ydlkDJSR#AJasCVG8PmjdMI7XB_5GAA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-22T07:00:26.781Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-22T06:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>fa49814f462df10a5c8e3ed0aaf6d897be51a7683152467b3ad1cf1cef0bc623</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-22T06:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sapporo</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T01:00:07.598Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YRYRHYwZ#aw7qUSj1JJNlICCrwqZVpw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>062</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is the Taisetsu Mountain Range, which is consisting of several peaks over 2,000 meters above sea level and designated a national park, the largest in Japan. Our program host explores the numerous ponds located at the mountainside. Autumn arrives early here in the Taisetsu Mountain Range, where the fall foliage is at its most beautiful in late September, and magnificent scenery colored in bright red and yellow spreads out. Later, we show you rare footage of some wildlife that inhabits near the summit, preparing for the winter.</content>
    <description>Our program host explores the numerous ponds located at the Taisetsu Mountain Range. The fall foliage is at its most beautiful in late September, and magnificent scenery spreads out.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-29T07:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wB9ERDjI#dsNx_ZJaWfydKQqdpt0_ZQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-29T07:00:29.812Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T06:44:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>0c0cfcc6dff446b9af72b6e7afa7ae77f42383fe930273a6f27b8968a9304a72</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T06:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Autumn in the Taisetsu Mountain Range</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T00:47:00.007Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/FVMDmKwB#hqSehRc2DIkQsad-zPfp1Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>064</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is the Notsuke Peninsula that stretches approximately 26 kilometers in the east of Hokkaido Prefecture. Its curvature is the result of sand and rocks deposited by the tides, and the natural environment found here is even rare in Hokkaido. Our program host takes a boat to places you cannot reach on foot, encountering the unique and strange landscape as well as its wild inhabitants. Furthermore, our camera crew dives into the shallow ocean surrounding the peninsula, and introduces you to the underwater forest of seaweed and its precious ecology.</content>
    <description>Our stage this time is the Notsuke Peninsula that stretches approximately 26 kilometers in the east of Hokkaido Prefecture. Its natural environment found here is even rare in Hokkaido.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-20T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/b510gTaA#BR4QEjLgZqbDgF9trytM9w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-20T01:01:04.908Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T00:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>013914cd35866aef53a44e68d8040043c49e7672b85cb270101c8e561592ea13</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Notsuke Peninsula</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T01:00:48.967Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/VJpygI5A#2OI5330sOh9ZrH_H20e4Ag</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>066</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Kiritappu in the eastern part of Hokkaido Prefecture. Here, you will find the unique natural environment created by the Pacific Ocean, coastal wetland and forest. Our program host explores the vast wetland, and observes a variety of wildlife as well as plants during winter. In addition, he joins a tour to fully enjoy the seafood of Kiritappu, where fishing industry is thriving. Later, we show you rare footage of wildlife that strives to secure food, in order to survive the harsh winter.</content>
    <description>Our stage this time is Kiritappu in the eastern part of Hokkaido Prefecture. Our program host explores the vast wetland, and observes a variety of wildlife as well as plants during winter.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-27T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PZVVGChI#eUkgH9ZqNifxkHK0_4dgIg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-27T01:00:27.786Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T00:44:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>278428239715f45ec9997c4efff1e4be5fc24191f3e86f730ed648ce6c32c04c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kiritappu in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-27T23:00:51.006Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MENxGIRK#CWoi9FBNRnQ82Baq28GrcA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>067</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Akkeshi in eastern part of Hokkaido Prefecture. It is a brackish-water lake which connects to the Pacific Ocean. A variety of wildlife inhabits here, but during the coldest period in winter, almost the entirety of Lake Akkeshi turns to ice. Our program host attempts to catch fish on the frozen river that pours into Lake Akkeshi, at temperatures below freezing. His aim is to catch the delicious and popular Japanese smelt. Is he able to achieve the result he wants? Later, we show you footage of migratory birds on Lake Akkeshi.</content>
    <description>Lake Akkeshi is a brackish-water lake which connects to the Pacific ocean. Our program host attempts to catch delicious fish on the frozen river that pours into Lake Akkeshi.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-03T13:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9ot0xKzZ#lH0IFdKlOUZRi13Uv55XnA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-03T13:00:26.950Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-03T12:44:20.119Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>e9eefa1c7e3595816ac9604b8007ede7bd629fae5a128eb2fd59e5288724ceb7</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-03T12:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lake Akkeshi in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T08:09:36.384Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1coQxSSB#EyB7mGpm7HlS4gX4qvSqyA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>068</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Biei in the center of Hokkaido Prefecture. It is a town with hills created by ancient volcanic activity. Our program host, together with a professional photographer, tries his hand at scenic photography. There are snow-covered hills and forests with the Tokachi mountain range in the background. They go around to a number of photography points to get creative and crop the magnificent scenery. Later, we show you rare footage of wildlife, such as red fox, surviving the harsh winter in the hills.</content>
    <description>Biei is a town with hills created by ancient volcanic activity. Our program host, together with a professional photographer, tries his hand at scenic photography of snow-covered hills.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-24T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/nEFjkAJZ#XwDfUzktyvW8uNYv70wIow</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-24T01:00:29.082Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-24T00:44:20.009Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>8ed3eb2363b1f62a4cb13a70921a6661478dec0f852707f80acb81d6734cb528</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-24T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Hills of Biei in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-24T02:36:03.380Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/NX52EKBL#F_v2cXTlLb7aGnQnf54Hwg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>069</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Kussharo in the eastern part of Hokkaido Prefecture. There are still a number of places to witness displays of the energy of volcanoes. Our program host walks through the forest in mid-winter, and discovers traces of surviving wild animals. Further, they head to the place where an unusual environment is kept due to the geothermal activity. Later, we show you rare footage of some striking scenery created by the extreme winter conditions on Lake Kussharo, as well as a unique hot spring at the lakeside where migratory birds gather.</content>
    <description>Our stage this time is Lake Kussharo. There are still a number of places to witness displays of the energy of volcanoes, and traces of surviving wild animals even in mid-winter.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-31T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/AmwQELKA#iFpekH8JtFBBrUItldJwoQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-31T01:00:29.684Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-31T00:44:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>c05e3f69c660889b619d7cf5741273aca35a6a77a7565889a1ac97089a810bfa</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-31T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lake Kussharo in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-31T06:27:50.705Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/quoXgSLS#PfIwvJeknwY26hFduyIsVw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>077</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Saroma, the largest lake in Hokkaido Prefecture, facing the Sea of Okhotsk. Seawater and fresh water are mixed together in this lake, and when the tide is low, tidal flats are revealed, attracting wild birds in search of food. The program host enjoys bird watching in the lake where various wild birds gather. Some rare birds are also seen here, taking a break during their migration. Later, we show you some footage of the wildflowers that bloom in the lake's sandy soil of the wildflower park, as well as the wild birds that raise their young.</content>
    <description>Lake Saroma is the largest lake in Hokkaido. Seawater and fresh water are mixed together in this lake. The program host enjoys bird watching in the lake where various wild birds gather.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-06T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qV1FSA7I#JQhIxEFJqFJ1AwoaG4457w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-06T01:00:28.356Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-06T00:44:20.011Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>4e54a161917e98e70690e3f8fd2f5f87858bde9faa0ae86069d172be6cd9a727</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-06T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lake Saroma</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T04:29:50.159Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ZRQiHBgB#bdW4P2NSQpK3y3U6T--1Tw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>078</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Sounkyo. It is located in the Daisetsu mountain range, almost in the center of Hokkaido Prefecture. It is a ravine with cliffs as high as 200 meters, created by volcanic activities that occurred 30,000 years ago. In autumn, the area is beautifully colored with autumn leaves. The program host rides a bicycle and encounters the beautiful scenery that the ravine offers. Further, he climbs Mt. Kurodake, which is over 1,900 meters above sea level, to fully enjoy its scenery as autumn deepens. Later, we show you some footage of wildlife inhabiting this area, filmed during fall and winter.</content>
    <description>Sounkyo is a ravine with cliffs, created by volcanic activities. The program host rides a bicycle and climbs mountain to enjoy its scenery, beautifully colored with autumn leaves.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-13T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/LR8SzLpI#PupL3i1risp4LQ1C9SJEUQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-13T01:00:21.919Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-13T00:44:22.306Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>d9a11517a271d946d13af11690f0867f810e01ae5aafa0e8e3b6b3d228352cf9</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-13T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sounkyo in Autumn</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T00:51:08.793Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1lNE0byB#VrfObeGmIpVUBfM3NTSmig</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>079</airingId>
    <content>The volcanic Mt. Furanodake rises in the south of the Taisetsu Mountain Range with a diverse environment. The program host sets out on a hike through a deep forest, crossing streams and enjoying beautiful waterfalls. After 2 hours of walking, he reaches an open space. It is a marshland formed by rainwater collecting on top of the lava. Later, we show you some footage of Northern Pika that stores leaves in its den to survive the long winter in an alpine zone, where not many plants are able to grow.</content>
    <description>The volcanic Mt. Furanodake rises with a diverse environment. The program host sets out on a hike through a deep forest, and reaches a marshland formed by rainwater collecting on top of the lava.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-10T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/SI0AiAgI#XDe7uaMxVFgi-GmP3INc9A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-10T01:00:31.183Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-10T00:44:20.082Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>c0609316d189b81a3197b9bdccd1fa74cb6622bd51c5e070ecb11ba37b2447f8</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-10T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Mt. Furanodake in Autumn</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T15:34:05.659Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ZEkyVabD#_RpgAKTfCKgfxp9Twy9alg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>080</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Furen which is connected to the Sea of Okhotsk in eastern Hokkaido Prefecture. It is a brackish lake with a circumference of 65km. The program host canoes down the river that flows into the lake, and enjoys watching white-tailed eagles and other birds. In the marshland facing the sea, he also observes sika deer at close range. Later, we show you some footage of red-crowned cranes raising their young by the lake where tide ebbs and flows, as well as red fox feeding on fish left on the tidal flats.</content>
    <description>Lake Furen is a brackish lake which is connected to the Sea of Okhotsk in eastern Hokkaido. The program host canoes down the river that flows into the lake, and enjoys watching birds.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-17T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/NV5QHCiJ#TBRgq7y1Hv-aL0pcFu8EnA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-17T01:00:29.723Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-17T00:44:20.023Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>54ec8c4a0c3d5213d48975fcb6666140e9cfc0bd4a1c9f6620238b4ccdcaf547</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-17T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Lake Furen in Autumn</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-19T05:54:34.382Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/W7oykASY#Fe_DEdijbx9Z9WErkktmqw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>081</airingId>
    <content>Shimukappu is located almost in the center of Hokkaido Prefecture. It is an area that gets severely cold in winter, where the snow-covered deep forest stretches. The program host explores the forest on a fat bike, which can be ridden easily through snowy terrain. He enjoys the spectacular scenery and the fluffy fresh snow as if he were a little child again. Later, we also show you the life of Siberian flying squirrels, which congregate in large groups only during winter by building a nest inside the hollow of a tree trunk.</content>
    <description>Shimukappu is an area that gets severely cold. The program host explores the forest on a fat bike, which can be ridden easily through snowy terrain and enjoys the scenery and fresh snow.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-07T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QYIDUK6B#QNDB-rhIkGJYMdQHpgHDNw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-07T01:00:25.163Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-07T00:44:23.717Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>f0f0e017e2cd644a68ec97ab9f57b6bf1234d35ae28221e6fd285aafa1f6bc26</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-07T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Simukappu in Winter</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T18:16:13.055Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/XA8UXSBY#KL5AjYpXMVr7AuEeP2HfRA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>082</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Akan in the eastern part of Hokkaido Prefecture. It is a caldera lake created as a result of ancient volcanic activity. In the dead of winter, the lake is completely frozen over. Our program host walks around the surrounding forests inhabited by a variety of wild fauna, as well as over the frozen lake to experience the flourishing forest and the energy of the volcano, which is still active today. Later, we show you rare footage of the lakeside facility of the Ainu, the indigenous people of Hokkaido, as well as some mysterious phenomena created in the lake by the intense winter conditions.</content>
    <description>In the dead of winter, Lake Akan is completely frozen over. Our program host walks around the surrounding forests inhabited by a variety of wild fauna.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-14T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/upZygJ6I#vWagg6MnywUjkvRRQgXILA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-14T01:00:27.731Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-14T00:44:23.000Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>18589884ce32312481db7eac19dec967aa75cea20ac473af208d33bc45b685bd</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-14T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Winter in Lake Akan</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T03:27:38.258Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/bBsy2TgJ#uNku_-4GjpYyREj4q423-Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>083</airingId>
    <content>Our stage this time is Lake Shikotsu, located about an hour's drive from Hokkaido Prefecture's capital city of Sapporo with a population of over 1.9 million. Although the lake does not freeze over even during the harsh winter, its shores are decorated with beautiful ice formations. Our program host takes a canoe trip along Lake Shikotsu and the Chitose River, which flows out of the lake, to enjoy the beauty of the icy landscapes and wildlife encounters on the water. Later, we show you some footage of the creatures that survive the winter at Lake Shikotsu.</content>
    <description>Lake Shikotsu does not freeze over even during the winter. Its shores are decorated with beautiful ice formations. Our program host takes a canoe trip along the lake and the river.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-07T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZW5HgQQK#qPWRUd6nZCrJeCbGfqf5Bg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-07T01:00:27.976Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-07T00:44:23.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>1a067793f36ada2548c616d64d8a62b50c61d85cc457e3c59d26c84c00574605</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-07T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Harsh Winter in Lake Shikotsu</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-07T02:02:24.943Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/b44XXQwT#kIW-jGxCLvc-ybIeAhll3w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>084</airingId>
    <content>Skiers and snowboarders from all over the world come in search of Japan's finest snow, Japan Powder Snow, or "Japow" for short. We hope you will thoroughly enjoy this special episode of Wild Hokkaido, introducing you to Japow. Our stage this time is Niseko, one of the top resort destinations in all of Hokkaido Prefecture, where fresh snow piles up almost every day during winter. The program host enjoys the great outdoors through a variety of fun winter activities, aside from skiing and snowboarding.</content>
    <description>Niseko is one of the top winter resort destinations in all of Hokkaido. The program host enjoys the great outdoors through a variety of fun winter activities, aside from skiing.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-14T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/z4ZyzLaT#hcNMd7HuYIJu2xWn-97N3A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-14T01:00:23.329Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-14T00:44:22.565Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2069</seriesId>
    <sha256>b70125d38eb0a61406945d99335b981ffb69f84b3dedb4e99d21a1ec263e868e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-14T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Enjoy Japow: Niseko Area</subtitle>
    <title>Wild Hokkaido!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T08:57:11.245Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/71p2GarL#LBgCD5KLvi2jVnA6BlWoEw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>