<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-01-06T07:05:02.621Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>b6a4aecdfcf53169</seriesId>
  <title>Asia Insight</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>277</airingId>
    <content>The ancient city of Bagan in central Myanmar was registered as a World Heritage Site in July 2019. The religious city is home to some 3,000 Buddhist pagodas and temples -- and now, a new clothing brand: "Cotton Bagan" is attracting attention from foreign visitors and local customers alike. 22-year-old Pyay Soe Hein founded the brand 2 years ago. The company uses locally grown cotton, woven, cut, and sewn by local artisans. He hopes to promote and encourage the country's textile industry by providing 100% Myanmar-made clothes. Discover how a young entrepreneur and his partners are making waves in this new market.</content>
    <description>Dynamic Asia. Stories behind the world's largest continent as it faces political, economic, cultural, and technological change. Today: Homegrown Cotton for a Homegrown Brand - Myanmar.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-20T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/kUAQgJDC#pNm2rgwtzEVsQ0XbPi2OkQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-20T02:00:24.459Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-20T01:29:20.110Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>aa222b2db1e7fdd751792b0a2a0a92439d0655b73d64aacad85b1a7124501cca</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-20T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Homegrown Cotton for a Homegrown Brand: Myanmar</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T17:29:27.089Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/XJk2VBKZ#Yz6zMKdoWCTkECvrgw0lOQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>278</airingId>
    <content>In July of 2018, a new theater group was formed in the southern Chinese city of Guangzhou. The subject of their performances is their own audience: Through improvisational theater, they express personal experiences suggested by the audience members, helping to give voices to the struggles of average people. However, they hit a major setback when a show was halted by the police, after which almost no theater would consent to renting them space. Now the group pushes on to find a new place in their home city, where they work to increase understanding and empathy among both loyal fans and new audience members.</content>
    <description>This episode follows a theater group in China, that improvises shows based on audience members' stories. Despite being shut down, they are determined to express the voices of their supporters.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-04T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ppNWBLaI#IbHwmr-yHXcg23DpXPfMWQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-04T02:00:30.217Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-04T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>25de2e88ddb8f2a37bc1833bd7777be1f7a3a1522a86a65bcd27a2b5281cd530</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-04T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Performing Your Story in China</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T16:05:24.387Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/xYlQQD7Q#5I5is15poxICD0DiALxcVQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>279</airingId>
    <content>Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam, is home to the Center for Disability Research and Capacity Development (DRD), an NGO led by Vo Thi Hoang Yen. As well as providing university scholarships and support for job-searching, Yen and her 13 staff are developing a digital map with detailed accessibility information for locations around Vietnam. Many people in Vietnam believe that people with disabilities are being punished for transgressions in a past life, leaving them marginalized and unable to find work. By encouraging Vietnam's disabled population to become independent, Yen and the DRD are looking to change Vietnam's attitude towards disability.</content>
    <description>Dynamic Asia. Stories behind the world's largest continent as it faces political, economic, and technological change. Today: Opening Doors to Independence - Disabilities in Vietnam.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-11T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZB90Va5J#6-ZsaAQXMMQ0FwmFvt-TVw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-11T02:00:27.362Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-11T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>72f40825b4cd0709776ea17233a88bb9e6d8865fb2b4eb7f110c8d79ba7cd836</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-11T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Opening Doors to Independence - Disabilities in Vietnam</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T15:33:54.070Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Nd9k1AQZ#ZlJbO5ktzmy_JR9DqXLtIg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>280</airingId>
    <content>China's Yangtze River has seen a decline in species due to pollution and overfishing, which the government responded to with a ban on industrial fishing. Although intended to improve the local environment, this measure had the side effect of taking away the livelihoods of the fishermen living around the river. Now, desperately seeking the means to support their families, some of the fishermen have begun utilizing their knowledge through conservationist work to preserve vulnerable species such as the finless porpoises of the Yangtze River.</content>
    <description>Fishing is now banned in many parts of the Yangtze River due to overfishing and pollution. Many out-of-work fishermen are now trying to find new jobs in environmental preservation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-01T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/GgU1iKYY#b4j4cNUTrFeINHtDGLm9WA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-01T02:00:29.008Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-01T01:29:22.587Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>5e897b23921d766738f094d9a72ee76d8ddb8e99cd71c72a8d1f32f185ec4f3a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-01T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Changing Lives of Fishermen on the Yangtze River</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-01T03:23:41.780Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ftERla5A#zxtiKa-PgHebg_gMkVJM7A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>317</airingId>
    <content>The Altai mountains in western Mongolia are home to many folk music traditions. Although traditional Mongolian arts have been swept away by modernization in many regions, this area has carefully maintained them as part of a nomadic lifestyle. From the world-famous Khoomei throat singing to the ikhel, from which all Mongolian string instruments are said to have evolved, this region is a historic treasure trove of the musical arts. 12 years ago, a 1,300-year-old wooden instrument was discovered in a cave burial in the region, with markings that prove the long association between local nomads and music. Discover how locals are keeping ancient arts alive today and continuing to worship nature through song and music.</content>
    <description>The Altai mountains in western Mongolia are home to a strong tradition of folk music, from throat singing to ancient string instruments. Meet the Altai folk keeping Mongolian music tradition alive.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-27T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/sZlUjDLJ#r_wAE-9uypOabOE3Y5nP_g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-27T02:00:24.551Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-27T01:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>97bb713930616b2b0f581126ffab2ba514fbd7cbc8710cdc83017e78a818c39c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-27T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Echoes of Musical Tradition: Mongolia</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T16:48:15.859Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HE8GiCQJ#-lVsz_uhyrOJBzPsQn9XvA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>318</airingId>
    <content>Thailand was the first country outside of China to detect cases of COVID-19. However, with less than 4,000 infections and 60 deaths as of the end of November, the measures they have taken are drawing global attention. The unsung heroes behind the scenes are the 1.2 million Health Volunteers who work closely with the local community, doing everything from distributing masks to monitoring those who may be infected. We find out who they are and why they are so devoted to defeating the virus.</content>
    <description>One of Thailand's unique measures against the novel Coronavirus is the 1.2 million health volunteers providing masks and safety to their community. We follow the efforts of these unsung heroes.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-18T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/NkV00biT#krwJkIBJcW1AEGBfFnpIpg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-18T02:00:31.125Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-18T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>57b6d95111a224ac122dc64906ec4798d9f934c88355d3ea4add38cb77370fc5</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-18T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Unsung Heroes Fighting the Coronavirus: Thailand</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:35:57.031Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/wQpEXbYa#aCNyhC1yDXADGRa5pPa7BA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>319</airingId>
    <content>The inland province of Guizhou had once been ranked among China's most impoverished, but change was shown by completion of a huge housing complex there 5 years ago. Now young entrepreneurs are staking their dreams on the region, drawn by the affordable housing costs and convenient infrastructure. From internet business CEOs to school owners, a wave of creative young men and women undeterred by the pandemic are seeking out new opportunities in Guizhou.</content>
    <description>China's once impoverished Guizhou province has built a large housing complex drawing many young entrepreneurs, particularly in internet businesses, who dream big even in the wake of the pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-25T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Z4lB1S7S#oLKyyEvwgNhbqX3vWb1jMw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-25T02:00:27.922Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-25T01:29:22.683Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2022</seriesId>
    <sha256>c4b01a12c2273680599f63bac5f5190e12534132a15fc490589eb7feea6d5fb6</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-25T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Entrepreneurs of the Massive Housing Complex: Guizhou, China</subtitle>
    <title>Asia Insight</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T16:51:15.088Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/r9tAhD7T#HRfGW1sDwN7p96DsMXw6YA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>