<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-20T23:40:04.193Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>b70d3103ab6de48b</seriesId>
  <title>Home Sweet Tokyo</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>021</airingId>
    <content>When a Japanese tea ceremony master with a connection to Itsuki's late mother shows up, the family goes on a journey that takes in a busy work schedule, missed dance recitals and a bizarre English afternoon tea party! Throughout it all, the Japanese phrase "Ichi-go Ichi-e" keeps popping up, which Bryan is told means "once in a lifetime." When the family finally slows down enough to appreciate a quiet moment, he realizes that it has a far deeper meaning than he first thought.</content>
    <description>When Itsuki's mom's tea ceremony master shows up, Bryan is challenged to throw a typical English afternoon tea party. But later the master's true intention is revealed.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-23T00:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/h88UGboa#MJ3KGoMMg6rkhS48x3vknw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-23T00:30:30.413Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-23T00:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>48fc38c44b509b1f74ec7a2192cfacff5b73ff9e38429a64ca500fd5f1edb547</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-23T00:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.3 Mom's Tea Cup</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 3</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T04:03:28.581Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4VQw3bQT#Gm-xCNwjn3G8RELe4Lcjlw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>022</airingId>
    <content/>
    <description>When Bryan serves one baked potato too many for Tsuneo, the family set off for a farm to taste Japanese soul food, rice. Tsuneo's twin sister is too happy to welcome them!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-29T09:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/IRRS2JxK#MnKSS9x5C8sG0tH_wWMd4w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-29T09:00:33.157Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T08:39:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>025128c2460e8d44c0240ceb1e15233e7d13c745597ea78b4916c827a3a659cb</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T08:40:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.4 Rice Pot Buddies</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 3</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T18:44:29.456Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YZQwRLyA#FJTtQtLgvdEB2TkjmEk3kA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>023</airingId>
    <content>With his wife Itsuki on a business trip abroad, Bryan and Tsuneo set about preparing the Matsuyama-Jenkins household for an incoming typhoon. However, nothing could prepare them for the arrival of Tsuneo's great-niece, Setsuko. Having spent time in the US, "Sets" is not the quiet little girl that Tsuneo remembers and Bryan starts to feel jealous of Alice's "new best friend"! To bring the family together, they dust off his box of Japanese games, but this just brings out everyone's competitive spirit!</content>
    <description>A typhoon is coming! And so is Tsuneo's great-niece, Setsuko! With Bryan feeling jealous of Alice's "new best friend," Tsuneo tries to bring the family together with some traditional Japanese games.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-04T23:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/rpEmARpC#udz_aLABAXnOpGIJL608HA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-04T23:30:32.847Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-04T23:09:20.084Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>bab3799241d63b427d83ab1e25ecd91cdf0f837ac68e469f8b48fdca20ea469e</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-04T23:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.1 Here Comes the Typhoon!</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 4</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T03:41:11.608Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/hZJwBBYR#fOR3RprD7l9yZqj1mgf36w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>024</airingId>
    <content>With new-arrival Setsuko taking over cooking and baby-sitting duties, Bryan is enjoying life! That is until Alice starts to miss her mum's special ramen dish and is forced to confront a previous traumatic noodle experience! With the help of a grumpy ramen shop owner and his wife, Bryan learns that there is more to ramen than meets the eye, that slurping is encouraged and that, above all in Japan, the customer is a god!</content>
    <description>With Setsuko taking over cooking and baby-sitting duties, Bryan is enjoying life! That is until Alice starts to miss her mum's special noodle dish and he has to confront his own fear of ramen!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-05T23:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/bhsF0azL#9mJWOHEDNk5439jox39eng</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-05T23:30:29.100Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-05T23:09:22.476Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>4c01c2379297b421058a2744b49f4314b194e3b7ae516f15705f9270787502cc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-05T23:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.2 Ramen Rhapsody</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 4</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T03:37:10.482Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/bc0VQKqR#zfDwmZZw6-wf5nysx440Ng</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>025</airingId>
    <content>Tsuneo is none too happy that Setsuko's focus has shifted from job-hunting to her new boyfriend, Sho. Especially as his style is a little too funky for Tsuneo's tastes. His overreaction causes a rift in the Matsuyama-Jenkins household, so, while Setsuko does finally attend an interview, Bryan and Tsuneo head to Sho's hometown to repair the damage. Bryan discovers a new local side to Japan, and Tsuneo learns not to judge a book by its cover - nor a boyfriend by his funky jacket!</content>
    <description>After booting out Setsuko's new boyfriend, Tsuneo has to make amends. While Bryan discovers a local side to Japan, Tsuneo learns not to judge a book by its cover - nor a man by his funky jacket!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-12T10:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/FR81WK7Q#DT00--5mr9c6ZgGjLGECwA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-12T10:30:27.555Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-12T10:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>5f98828528acb22ab6d1a062082ff0743f926c62e7ca6a4447007a08d433b64c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-12T10:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.3 Time to Say Yabai!</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 4</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T07:58:02.651Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3YlnSIZB#Lzd5NjOiUEeTXhY7K_gGwg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>026</airingId>
    <content>As the traditional spring equinox approaches, Bryan learns what Oni (Japanese demons) are, but Alice and Setsuko have to face up to real-life challenges far scarier than an angry, red mask. With some inspiration from the tale of Momotaro (The Peach Boy), and some symbolic soybeans, the Matsuyama-Jenkins family come together to drive their demons out and keep their good luck in!</content>
    <description>As the traditonal Spring equinox approaches, Bryan learns what oni (Japanese demons) are, but Alice and Setsuko have to face up to real-life challenges far scarier than an angry, red mask.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-12T23:30:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/b09GwRSb#7q_HqTdkM407LkqIf3daBQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-12T23:30:29.139Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-12T23:09:22.685Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3018</seriesId>
    <sha256>90fe5302e0ba3ce7b6952c9ff17870ef1d2d8c0299e724ba355a87cbc3eaaf0d</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-12T23:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ep.4 Facing Your Demons!</subtitle>
    <title>Home Sweet Tokyo Season 4</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T03:33:55.274Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/P1lREQzT#4U2_ob742kNUbVTxQJYeKg</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>