<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T04:00:03.036Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>be55ba93c748813c</seriesId>
  <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>212</airingId>
    <content>With a desire to do hanami in Japan, foreign tourists who come to Japan just as cherry blossoms go into full bloom are increasing. This time's theme is "Flowers" that color Japan's four seasons. What are the appeals of flower parks that many foreigners have been visiting in recent years? Giant ikebana that greet people at entrances -- how are they different from flower arrangements overseas? With a focus on the relationship between Japanese people and flowers, such as flowers that show up in daily life, we close in on their cools.</content>
    <description>Foreigners marvel at the Japanese affinity for flowers, from traditional flower arrangement art to meticulously managed flower parks. The panelists explore the key roles flowers play in Japanese life.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T11:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qMsyEJLA#5117j3V6YeRC4B997ja7fw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T11:55:28.363Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T11:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>70fd0e80a377ce8e9ed2b785631b2072c5222a0a90bf0e04cfac39bb28e42ac3</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Flowers</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:03:31.669Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oc00iI4I#-P-gCmYacHWLVhTzNQorjw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>221</airingId>
    <content>The 7th COOL JAPAN Outing is in Nara Prefecture. It has the most national treasures and important cultural properties in Japan and, along with Kyoto Prefecture, it is a common destination for school excursions for Japanese people. The number of foreign tourists is increasing every year. However, about 80% of foreigners go to Nara to see deer and the Great Buddha. The average number of nights and money spent by foreigners at the destination are at the lowest level in Japan. So this time we gathered 8 foreigners living there. We investigated the surprising appeals and spots of Nara that the world considers to be cool and that Japanese people haven't noticed, and thoroughly discuss them.</content>
    <description>Nara Prefecture, with its many historical edifices and art, draws many foreign tourists but does not quite succeed in keeping them long. The panelists discuss how the visitors' stays can be extended.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/B4sARIgS#w0E9wWcwUslkXhCUqHYl0w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T05:01:17.084Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T04:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>313a4013bd31c8c69067118d263558d0ed0768fd94b55009de6c339a65f8d1bd</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nara Prefecture</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T01:18:39.590Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>246</airingId>
    <content>Historical plays have become rarer on terrestrial TV. In fact, they are very popular on satellite TV and specialized channels. Japanese people love historical plays. When the hero of a large-scale TV series is announced, related locations are enlivened and people get excited about revitalization. Are there any other countries that love historical plays as much as Japan? We investigate the cools of Japanese historical plays in Japanese people whose hearts are captivated by historical plays and their productions sites at the end of this year in which they were a hot topic.</content>
    <description>The panelists explore how historical plays continue to entertain audiences of all ages in Japan, and how regional communities strive to promote their ties with historical heroes portrayed in TV drama.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/h51nECYB#gRT0Hk2G1LVe01cpcX6tGg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T04:55:25.357Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T04:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>d7fded1a7a9abed8b748948ecbecc167f06b48dcbd28d64a10bba54fd9829126</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Historical Plays</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T00:27:45.849Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/vFE3QCwK#zr9hJznvCWTiJN0Xyki7fQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>