<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-20T06:50:03.908Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>be55ba93c748813c</seriesId>
  <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>212</airingId>
    <content>With a desire to do hanami in Japan, foreign tourists who come to Japan just as cherry blossoms go into full bloom are increasing. This time's theme is "Flowers" that color Japan's four seasons. What are the appeals of flower parks that many foreigners have been visiting in recent years? Giant ikebana that greet people at entrances -- how are they different from flower arrangements overseas? With a focus on the relationship between Japanese people and flowers, such as flowers that show up in daily life, we close in on their cools.</content>
    <description>Foreigners marvel at the Japanese affinity for flowers, from traditional flower arrangement art to meticulously managed flower parks. The panelists explore the key roles flowers play in Japanese life.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T11:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qMsyEJLA#5117j3V6YeRC4B997ja7fw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T11:55:28.363Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T11:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>70fd0e80a377ce8e9ed2b785631b2072c5222a0a90bf0e04cfac39bb28e42ac3</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Flowers</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:03:31.669Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oc00iI4I#-P-gCmYacHWLVhTzNQorjw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>215</airingId>
    <content>Gyoza originated in China. However, grilled gyoza is now becoming popular around the world as a Japanese food. A gyoza bar where people line up appeared in France, and in China, its birthplace, grilled gyoza at a Japanese chain restaurant is very popular as "Japanese-style." With stylish evolved types and local gyoza, Japanese gyoza continues to evolve daily. We close in on the secret to the popularity of Japanese-style gyoza, which captivates foreigners.</content>
    <description>Gyoza is originally Chinese, but the grilled gyoza of Japan is gaining worldwide recognition. The panelists explore its current development, its perception overseas, and the latest grilling equipment.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZQgm0BxY#xp9Fr4tJFb9Dqpg3RDStsg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T04:55:25.202Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T04:09:20.144Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>e1667acd048c670afb1df1348a8c71b3e0614e11448caeec6980cbc759c04121</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Gyoza</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T16:31:21.481Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/c0k0kTSC#b8zhC5uZmNAGZxVwxms67g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>217</airingId>
    <content>The thing that foreigners living in Japan are incomparably impressed by is repairs. Is it only Japan that responds to lock and plumbing repairs 24/7? The passion of Japanese people for repairs is amazing; fixing clothes so that holes cannot be seen and thoroughly training new employees at a road service company. How do foreigners view the Japanese culture of using and fixing things with care?</content>
    <description>Foreigners marvel at the range of repairing goods and the high level of service available in Japan. The panelists discuss the various disciplines and philosophies that sustain Japanese repair quality.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-16T11:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/mkMDjIYB#EOi4FUiXv6WHWOFI1KX9Pw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-16T11:55:40.800Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-16T11:09:20.194Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>c0658472b7b0b848bdc444bd8d7e7ff063732dd1b66b310846c270bf12967aca</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-16T11:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Repairing</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-16T22:39:00.566Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JbpE3aQS#RtRvQqnP1w1bWpDu4r76Dg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>221</airingId>
    <content>The 7th COOL JAPAN Outing is in Nara Prefecture. It has the most national treasures and important cultural properties in Japan and, along with Kyoto Prefecture, it is a common destination for school excursions for Japanese people. The number of foreign tourists is increasing every year. However, about 80% of foreigners go to Nara to see deer and the Great Buddha. The average number of nights and money spent by foreigners at the destination are at the lowest level in Japan. So this time we gathered 8 foreigners living there. We investigated the surprising appeals and spots of Nara that the world considers to be cool and that Japanese people haven't noticed, and thoroughly discuss them.</content>
    <description>Nara Prefecture, with its many historical edifices and art, draws many foreign tourists but does not quite succeed in keeping them long. The panelists discuss how the visitors' stays can be extended.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/B4sARIgS#w0E9wWcwUslkXhCUqHYl0w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T05:01:17.084Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T04:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>313a4013bd31c8c69067118d263558d0ed0768fd94b55009de6c339a65f8d1bd</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nara Prefecture</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T01:18:39.590Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/w4F2XTgL#-wEA1yGNZ-0wDIe5iNwNvw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>225</airingId>
    <content>The 5th COOL JAPAN Outing is in Yamaguchi Prefecture. Tourist spots such as Akiyoshidai and Kintai Bridge are known among Japanese people, but foreigners have a different perspective. Motonosumi Inari Shrine, with its torii lined up along the coast, was chosen by an overseas broadcasting station as one of the most beautiful places in Japan. 8 foreigners who live in Yamaguchi gathered to search for surprising appeals of Yamaguchi. We thoroughly discuss cool spots that the world will understand.</content>
    <description>Yamaguchi Prefecture ranks 43rd out of 47 in overnight stays by foreign visitors. 8 foreigners residing in Yamaguchi review its attractions and discuss how they can be promoted to draw more visitors.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-20T05:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0JUhlY7I#DHJpTera6oBUOSx1_v1x7w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-20T05:00:27.651Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-20T04:09:20.056Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>766a62f48c85f08eb973a5d415b5e15cf7322f48749ee7871e74eecb036f98af</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-20T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yamaguchi Prefecture</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-20T06:45:43.515Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>229</airingId>
    <content>Foreigners say that fruit sandwiches are inconceivable and sandwiching side dishes between bread is strange. However, people who become hooked on cutlet sandwiches once they eat them are rapidly increasing. What's the aesthetic of Moedan sandwiches that are particular about the beauty of cross sections? Following ramen, sushi, and tempura, will they see a boom that spreads to the world? We investigate the cools of Japan's sandwiches.</content>
    <description>Sandwiches have evolved uniquely in Japan, originating various styles and configurations. The panelists discuss the potential for Japanese sandwiches to follow sushi and ramen in global appreciation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-30T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QD4WjIqR#uQs0AIizwdBpcHqMPkb4WA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-30T04:55:23.345Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-30T04:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>f80247a8391f272711767cf84de69c3d89f0930346dc84d76f1b1aaf3466535b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-30T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sandwiches</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-31T09:20:20.714Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/imgmVTyJ#fMapMoQX0Ak9nuTmliyLxg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>246</airingId>
    <content>Historical plays have become rarer on terrestrial TV. In fact, they are very popular on satellite TV and specialized channels. Japanese people love historical plays. When the hero of a large-scale TV series is announced, related locations are enlivened and people get excited about revitalization. Are there any other countries that love historical plays as much as Japan? We investigate the cools of Japanese historical plays in Japanese people whose hearts are captivated by historical plays and their productions sites at the end of this year in which they were a hot topic.</content>
    <description>The panelists explore how historical plays continue to entertain audiences of all ages in Japan, and how regional communities strive to promote their ties with historical heroes portrayed in TV drama.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/h51nECYB#gRT0Hk2G1LVe01cpcX6tGg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T04:55:25.357Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T04:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>d7fded1a7a9abed8b748948ecbecc167f06b48dcbd28d64a10bba54fd9829126</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Historical Plays</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T00:27:45.849Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/vFE3QCwK#zr9hJznvCWTiJN0Xyki7fQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>247</airingId>
    <content>Fruits produced in Japan are attracting the world right now. The secret to their popularity is their superior sweetness. In America, Japanese strawberries are cultivated in greenhouses and sold at multiples of the price that they are sold in Japan. Russian tourists take back mountains of strawberries on airplanes as souvenirs. However, foreigners find it strange that Japanese people don't eat the skin of fruits. Our foreign guests report on Japan's dried persimmons, whose popularity in Europe is quickly rising, and the strawberry development wars, in which sweetness and appearance are pursued. Will Japan's fruits become the next flavor of the world?</content>
    <description>The panelists evaluate the unique customs of enjoying fruits in Japan, including the competitive breeding of superior products, traditional fruit-drying methods, and the habitual peeling of the skins.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-09T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/P81CwA7L#I1fTW572UAJI8NurifZOOw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-09T04:55:27.502Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-09T04:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>25098459d3ecfbad3860c8863eda915a397cce1c6655cb842c253148ceee1a3a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-09T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fruits</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T17:32:34.836Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3wo2BYyD#7zLzXYeIb4QyIvZD4QgJTw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>248</airingId>
    <content>Japan is an Osozai heaven where you can easily find Osozai anywhere, including convenience stores, supermarkets and basement floors of department stores. Osozai has recently been popular among foreigners too due to its wide variety, deliciousness and healthiness. There are many foreign tourists who not only go to restaurants but go out to buy popular Osozai, and some basement floors of department stores have become tourist locations. At the front lines of Osozai, which is bound to become increasingly popular in the future, we close in on the capabilities of Japan's Osozai, including container technology that supports it in the background.</content>
    <description>Osozai are Japan's unique range of prepared and ready-to-eat food. The panelists look at popular traditional dishes as well as some recent innovations, and discuss whether they have global potential.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-13T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/z5VmAbzC#WhN5of7xKB5scHVYl8-S_Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-13T04:55:25.925Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-13T04:09:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4008</seriesId>
    <sha256>6d8c0d6733622f83259e8ca96cb201035df577a4a87aa1030f2180a182f91358</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-13T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Osozai</subtitle>
    <title>COOL JAPAN</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-15T07:51:27.318Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IQghXAwJ#xN87mivENNSyec2Ifg61JQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>