<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-25T06:05:04.946Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>c1616c758db95ac6</seriesId>
  <title>GATTEN!</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>277</airingId>
    <content>Red miso from the Tokai region of Japan is famous as an ingredient in dishes such as Miso-katsu (pork cutlet covered in miso) and Miso-nikomi udon (udon noodles simmered in red miso broth). But when we asked people in Tokyo what they thought of it, their responses were far from positive. "The color is too dark." "I think of it as really salty." Little did they know that Tokai red miso is a versatile ingredient that can add rich flavor to all sorts of cuisine! It also has a chemical composition that makes food tastier the longer it's boiled -- a surprising trait among miso varieties. And despite its extremely dark color and deep flavor, it's actually relatively low in sodium. We explore the amazing, little-known power of red miso!</content>
    <description>A lot of people in Japan say they avoid cooking with red miso, but it's actually a versatile ingredient that can add rich flavor to all sorts of cuisine, all the while being low in sodium.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-02T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/x8FgmZ4D#GXOvgKftNU84j57Qt509uw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-02T04:55:44.410Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-02T04:09:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>5001</seriesId>
    <sha256>45eee8a071313ef50a71ee9b7f17df6ed7a5c58878bdc27963ca4492ee0ac8eb</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-02T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The Unknown Power of Red Miso</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T14:32:46.832Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/hEMUSDjS#Lg5uqXTFFSwfuemTZ5Dsmw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>282</airingId>
    <content>At every annual checkup, you can bet they're going to measure your cholesterol. And cholesterol comes in 2 main types: LDL (bad) and HDL (good). We know that if your bad cholesterol is high, you are at higher risk of stroke and heart attack. Meanwhile, good cholesterol works to absorb excess cholesterol in your arteries. So you might think the more good cholesterol you have the better. But new research has revealed that the issue isn't quite so simple. How well good cholesterol absorbs excess cholesterol varies from person to person, and if this absorbency is low, you may be at increased risk of stroke. How can you increase your absorbency? We'll show you how!</content>
    <description>Good cholesterol absorbs excess cholesterol in your blood. But new research shows that this absorbency varies from person to person - and you don't want it to be low! We'll show you how to raise it.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-06T04:55:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/texhCQTI#5KQk2A_tZS3lPVM4NR59dA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-06T04:55:26.940Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-06T04:09:20.101Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>5001</seriesId>
    <sha256>4cd6705448bb3b82ed06ed54260f97a4f773f2f489facaa326ba1061c8411ab3</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-06T04:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>The New Cholesterol Battle! Keep Those Arteries Clean</subtitle>
    <title>GATTEN!</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-06T07:11:00.081Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/e45xUSwK#QVXQrgFAqHg58Ypru8CUFw</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>