<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-04-27T03:55:03.267Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>c2cfe904ce7ecfa5</seriesId>
  <title>Face To Face</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>037</airingId>
    <content>The destruction of natural habitats in the name of economic growth has made a once common bird an endangered species. In June 2018, however, 19 "toki," or Japanese crested ibis were reintroduced into the wild, thanks to a breeding and release program led by veterinarian Yoshinori Kaneko. He says it's been a process of trial and error that includes working with Chinese researchers and calling on local farmers to cut back on pesticides. He talks about what it takes to live in harmony with nature.</content>
    <description>Veterinarian Yoshinori Kaneko aims to save the "toki," or Japanese crested ibis from extinction by breeding and releasing them into the wild. He talks about his work and his vision on Face To Face.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-20T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Fxd1SITA#smbs_yQSzPrYVBLV7Cor1Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-20T01:41:11.474Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T01:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>931940f6c6efe65accaef26947e08e9abc6ca85e30964b17383e319513a912e7</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yoshinori Kaneko: Bringing Back from Extinction</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T05:35:01.857Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4ZZ0TbID#Ag8AlgM4S-pzQj2hvNlrMg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>039</airingId>
    <content>The 2018 Hans Christian Andersen Award for Writing, aka the Little Nobel Prize for Literature, went to Eiko Kadono (83), author of "Kiki's Delivery Service." She won acclaim for her inspirational portrayal of a girl who makes her own way through life. Recently, she started to write stories about her own wartime experiences in a way that transcends time and space. She also gives monthly public readings and provides insight into her magical world, inspiring children with imagination and courage.</content>
    <description>The 2018 Hans Christian Andersen Award for Writing, aka the Little Nobel Prize for Literature, went to Eiko Kadono (83), author of "Kiki's Delivery Service." She talks about the magic of imagination.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-21T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/pAwW1R5C#7zYKc9zOu4vw66dXYJ3O5g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-21T01:40:29.552Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-21T01:09:22.590Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>cb944f590b6ce294b47916904bc0e8d3ed7fb7f48a98ad860f0810ea2e2631ae</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-21T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eiko Kadono: Weaving Magic with Words</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T03:20:32.139Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/rgIBlSgK#T1oa-Jmb3RnwTHoGQQOO5w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>040</airingId>
    <content>Eiichi Saitoh is a pioneering figure in rehabilitation medicine and man behind the development of cutting-edge braces and robots. Stricken by polio as a child, his right leg is paralyzed. But he turns this into an advantage to develop and test his inventions on himself. His aim is to help people remember and relearn how to walk. To this end, his robots cause the wearer to stumble without falling, if he or she loses balance. The key to recovery, he says, is to promote resilience and self-help.</content>
    <description>Eiichi Saitoh is a pioneer in rehabilitation medicine. His cutting-edge robots are designed to support and motivate patients, which, he says, is the key to promoting resilience and self-help.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-28T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/0l4QkJSK#pynE92r30wonaqAPVAfPeA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-28T01:40:28.188Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-28T01:09:22.517Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>e37bbb34933f5787495cf329bc6f8dc2725e0718198cc4625693082ad6e2cfec</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-28T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Eiichi Saitoh: Resilience and Recovery Come in Pairs</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-28T02:52:23.825Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/AoxSxSYQ#ZxYPne2NJw0NgVQXySmcJA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>055</airingId>
    <content>Kodan is a traditional storytelling art that is enjoying a spectacular revival thanks to Kanda Hakuzan (36). Although he made his debut just 13 years ago, tickets to his performances sell out in no time. He manages to bring historic characters to life with his energetic performances that are grounded in solid technique and style. In February 2020, he assumed the highest rank possible in Kodan, the fastest rise in history. He joins us for a chat on Japanese culture as reflected in Kodan.</content>
    <description>The traditional storytelling art of kodan is enjoying a spectacular revival thanks to rising star Kanda Hakuzan. Tickets to his performances sell out in no time. He shares with us his love of kodan.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-27T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/uxFkQJKI#pWfebEab2MRw-AZmP_G3aA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-27T01:40:26.550Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T01:09:23.361Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>4099e26912d7064701eee5fc1508950d80fe1ea905d3d70958a9b2609e8997cc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kanda Hakuzan: Championing the Art of Kodan</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T23:43:10.813Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qtNwlLzI#IHHT6clPFPKUPjXQFZhPKA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>056</airingId>
    <content>An illustrated book that explains the law in simple terms has sold over 500,000 copies in just over 6 months. Aimed at children, the author Soichiro Yamasaki hopes that understanding the law will help address the ongoing issue of bullying. Yamasaki is not a legal expert. Instead, he draws on his own experiences to drive home the point that bullying is a crime. He talks about how he hopes that the book will not only discourage kids from becoming bullies but also help kids protect themselves.</content>
    <description>A book on law for kids has become a best-seller. The author, Yamasaki Soichiro, talks about his hopes for addressing the on-going issue of bullying by explaining the law in simple terms to kids.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-21T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Rk5SARZY#tnwwlk0LfjAlV8ThbYfNxw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-21T01:40:26.601Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-21T01:09:20.092Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>06d6e0fe216e128667db6ce757018fda863b61aa82e4188273626e5eb312148e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-21T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Soichiro Yamasaki: Helping Kids Protect Themselves</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-22T00:54:08.544Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/bIlRHYbT#8OCnE-CF6lLjMlW9xVOD9A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>057</airingId>
    <content>Symbolic of Japanese tradition and culture and imbued with the spirit of the samurai, the Japanese sword is both a deadly weapon and a work of art. Yoshihara Yoshindo is considered to be the greatest swordsmith alive. His works are displayed at New York's Metropolitan Museum of Art and Boston's Museum of Fine Arts. Using techniques developed 1,000 years ago, he continues to forge swords at his small workshop in Tokyo. Why? Find out the answer to this and more on Face To Face.</content>
    <description>Yoshihara Yoshindo is considered to be the greatest swordsmith alive. He forges masterpieces using techniques developed 1,000 years ago. He shares his thoughts on the art of the Japanese sword.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-18T02:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7FkGFAjb#liFOEF2IxHRj2gBLZ74JNw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-18T02:40:27.726Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-18T02:09:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>91eb232b6e215b2b2229ec1c6aaec7103806960072187c604e7fecbe492ff957</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-18T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yoshihara Yoshindo: The Art of the Japanese Sword</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-18T03:58:42.926Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/9AtEmKJC#w3y3AxbcfAnsre9n_JtDRA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>063</airingId>
    <content>Die-hard anime and manga fans are falling in love with 2.5D musicals. These are productions that exist somewhere between the 2D realm of anime and manga and the 3D realm of theater. Pioneering this new genre is theater producer Matsuda Makoto. He transposes the essence of the original manga or anime to live theater that far exceeds the expectations of fans. Matsuda provides us with an insight into what goes into the making of 2.5 musicals, and his belief in their universal appeal.</content>
    <description>2.5D musicals based on anime and manga are attracting audiences new to theater. Producer Matsuda Makoto provides an insight into this new genre that's on the fast track to international success.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-29T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VgVhmYYB#_Ew_dAwFVu9CfH5Kg-FTYA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-29T01:40:31.316Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T01:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>6880b19d85ad3d56e4473e4be48a367f0e719e464d9b7a59d2c761195fe555a2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Matsuda Makoto: The Pioneer of 2.5D Musicals</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T05:33:29.803Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7EcQ3R7R#5b2dc_-jq-pQTJeECG1R7A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>064</airingId>
    <content>A Japanese aquarium that was once in dire straits has become the world's center for jellyfish research, thanks to its current director, Okuizumi Kazuya. He proposed setting up a jellyfish exhibit many years ago. At the time, he was a young man with little self-esteem. But the success of the exhibit gave him a new perspective. Today, he's become a leading expert in jellyfish, and his fish tank designs have been adopted by aquariums world over. He shares his passion for jellyfish with our host, Robert Campbell.</content>
    <description>Okuizumi Kazuya is the director of an aquarium with the world's largest display of jellyfish. He talks about how his love for jellyfish helped him regain his self-esteem and find a purpose in life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-31T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QiID2YgJ#92hwQOrNTOge-riYj9IJNg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-31T01:40:28.354Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-31T01:09:23.146Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b69e7413cb7a33d47891876fa1b584056513542e033f860f0fe82aaa6509a95</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-31T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Okuizumi Kazuya: Lovestruck by Jellyfish</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-31T08:35:18.094Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cHYzDKaZ#1_4r1ypCrem1RhWt1Wp02w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>065</airingId>
    <content>The skills of Japan's craftsmen are indispensable in restoring and preserving Japan's traditional wooden architecture. At the end of 2020, these skills were listed as a UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage. David Atkinson, a former financial analyst from the UK, is the CEO of a 300-year-old company that has led the restoration of World Heritage sites such as Nikko Toshogu Shrine. Through bold reforms, he's managed to attract more young people into the field and is now seeking ways to secure funding through tourism.</content>
    <description>A former financial analyst from the UK, David Atkinson is the CEO of a company that specializes in restoring Japanese architectural heritage. He discusses ways to pass on tradition and ensure funding.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-28T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Op4wHaBA#D9McPJDKvwqSNiaPPU5l_Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-28T01:40:29.860Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-28T01:09:22.889Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>4ae5e76dc2346b0ca9e27dfcb589ead87179e2f707267c21c400496669f44926</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-28T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>David Atkinson: Preserving Craftsmanship for Posterity</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-28T03:09:35.989Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Et4iwBzL#j8eNpqH49vPG4YvFq0mEVQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>066</airingId>
    <content>Photographer Asada Masashi, who inspired the award-winning film, "The Asada Family, " is famous for taking unconventional family photos. One photo featuring his own family shows them dressed up as firefighters. Rather than traditional family portraits, Asada had his family take on fictional roles, such as that of a team of firefighters. Through his work and his experience of cleaning and returning family photos to the victims of a disaster, he's come to realize the power of photos that capture moments in everyday life, which he shares with us on Face To Face.</content>
    <description>Photographer Asada Masashi is famous for his unique family photos and receives requests from all over Japan. The subject of a hit movie, he talks about the possibilities presented by family photos.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-25T02:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/CghAXJBD#IQaecCJYPceAiNAWtNpMWg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-25T02:40:32.011Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-25T02:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>c55e68312d40d4f2d3bb4ae00058bb1fc79197202ad8e11d7dfb63502a24c7c2</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-25T02:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Photographing Family Bonds</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-25T09:19:41.163Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/JuB0zR4a#rhFDhHGajvLh0rwMnI7fBg</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>