<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-02-15T07:05:03.604Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>c2cfe904ce7ecfa5</seriesId>
  <title>Face To Face</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>037</airingId>
    <content>The destruction of natural habitats in the name of economic growth has made a once common bird an endangered species. In June 2018, however, 19 "toki," or Japanese crested ibis were reintroduced into the wild, thanks to a breeding and release program led by veterinarian Yoshinori Kaneko. He says it's been a process of trial and error that includes working with Chinese researchers and calling on local farmers to cut back on pesticides. He talks about what it takes to live in harmony with nature.</content>
    <description>Veterinarian Yoshinori Kaneko aims to save the "toki," or Japanese crested ibis from extinction by breeding and releasing them into the wild. He talks about his work and his vision on Face To Face.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-20T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Fxd1SITA#smbs_yQSzPrYVBLV7Cor1Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-20T01:41:11.474Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-20T01:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>931940f6c6efe65accaef26947e08e9abc6ca85e30964b17383e319513a912e7</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-20T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Yoshinori Kaneko: Bringing Back from Extinction</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T05:35:01.857Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4ZZ0TbID#Ag8AlgM4S-pzQj2hvNlrMg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>055</airingId>
    <content>Kodan is a traditional storytelling art that is enjoying a spectacular revival thanks to Kanda Hakuzan (36). Although he made his debut just 13 years ago, tickets to his performances sell out in no time. He manages to bring historic characters to life with his energetic performances that are grounded in solid technique and style. In February 2020, he assumed the highest rank possible in Kodan, the fastest rise in history. He joins us for a chat on Japanese culture as reflected in Kodan.</content>
    <description>The traditional storytelling art of kodan is enjoying a spectacular revival thanks to rising star Kanda Hakuzan. Tickets to his performances sell out in no time. He shares with us his love of kodan.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-27T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/uxFkQJKI#pWfebEab2MRw-AZmP_G3aA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-27T01:40:26.550Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-27T01:09:23.361Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>4099e26912d7064701eee5fc1508950d80fe1ea905d3d70958a9b2609e8997cc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-27T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kanda Hakuzan: Championing the Art of Kodan</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T23:43:10.813Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qtNwlLzI#IHHT6clPFPKUPjXQFZhPKA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>063</airingId>
    <content>Die-hard anime and manga fans are falling in love with 2.5D musicals. These are productions that exist somewhere between the 2D realm of anime and manga and the 3D realm of theater. Pioneering this new genre is theater producer Matsuda Makoto. He transposes the essence of the original manga or anime to live theater that far exceeds the expectations of fans. Matsuda provides us with an insight into what goes into the making of 2.5 musicals, and his belief in their universal appeal.</content>
    <description>2.5D musicals based on anime and manga are attracting audiences new to theater. Producer Matsuda Makoto provides an insight into this new genre that's on the fast track to international success.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-29T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/VgVhmYYB#_Ew_dAwFVu9CfH5Kg-FTYA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-29T01:40:31.316Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-29T01:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>6880b19d85ad3d56e4473e4be48a367f0e719e464d9b7a59d2c761195fe555a2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-29T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Matsuda Makoto: The Pioneer of 2.5D Musicals</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T05:33:29.803Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/7EcQ3R7R#5b2dc_-jq-pQTJeECG1R7A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>064</airingId>
    <content>A Japanese aquarium that was once in dire straits has become the world's center for jellyfish research, thanks to its current director, Okuizumi Kazuya. He proposed setting up a jellyfish exhibit many years ago. At the time, he was a young man with little self-esteem. But the success of the exhibit gave him a new perspective. Today, he's become a leading expert in jellyfish, and his fish tank designs have been adopted by aquariums world over. He shares his passion for jellyfish with our host, Robert Campbell.</content>
    <description>Okuizumi Kazuya is the director of an aquarium with the world's largest display of jellyfish. He talks about how his love for jellyfish helped him regain his self-esteem and find a purpose in life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-31T01:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/QiID2YgJ#92hwQOrNTOge-riYj9IJNg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-31T01:40:28.354Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-31T01:09:23.146Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2043</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b69e7413cb7a33d47891876fa1b584056513542e033f860f0fe82aaa6509a95</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-31T01:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Okuizumi Kazuya: Lovestruck by Jellyfish</subtitle>
    <title>Face To Face</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-31T08:35:18.094Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/cHYzDKaZ#1_4r1ypCrem1RhWt1Wp02w</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>