<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-29T00:45:03.628Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>c656328a0f33bc89</seriesId>
  <title>15 Minutes</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>006</airingId>
    <content>Recipes are often developed over several lifetimes of work, lovingly crafted and passed on from generation to generation. These dishes represent much more than home cooking. This program delves into traditional recipes to shine a light on unique food cultures across Japan, and discover the older generation's seasoned philosophies of life.
Tami Hiyama, 92 years old, lives alone in Fukuoka City, where she has taught home cooking for more than 60 years. We learn her recipe for "chirashi-zushi," a special kind of sushi eaten at family celebrations. Tami prepares the finest ingredients but she says mindset is just as important -- she cooks the dish imagining those who will soon enjoy it. What does "chirashi-zushi" mean to 92-year-old Tami? We discover her recipes for life and the secrets of her good health.</content>
    <description>We learn 92-year-old Tami Hiyama's recipe for "chirashi-zushi," a special kind of sushi eaten at family celebrations. What does "chirashi" mean to Tami? We discover her recipes for life.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-09T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qgcSzJpD#tHp89tQPVS1VdV6lWtAQFw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-09T01:00:32.316Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-09T00:44:23.000Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>8ba57baa39eed7b2cd5ecc09d257e1a91acaa15e5658083dac3a903e655b92ab</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-09T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Through the Kitchen Window: Tami Hiyama - Chirashi-Zushi, Home-party Sushi</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T15:08:40.092Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/dVxShTKb#bJCyr8Rg2C4Fv1gaGgkj0g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>117</airingId>
    <content>The coronavirus has changed everything. How can we overcome this crisis? How can we restore our normal lifestyles? In Japan, Tokyo had the largest number of coronavirus infections. In this series, we look inside 3 places in this megacity. Hotels, where many people stay. Schools, where young people gather. And airports, major transportation hubs. We'll bring you insight on how the people in these places are trying to recover.
Ever since Jiyu Gakuen opened in 1921, students had been preparing school lunches themselves. Preparing and sharing meals together is a valuable opportunity for students to socialize and bond. It's a tradition the school has proudly preserved over the years. Since the campus has been closed, naturally, the dining hall too remains empty. Can the school keep this legacy going in spite of the pandemic? As the school reopens after a period of about 6 months, the first phase of lunch preparation begins. We follow the challenges of students and teachers.</content>
    <description>Ever since Jiyu Gakuen opened in 1921, students had been preparing school lunches themselves. Can the school keep this legacy in spite of the pandemic? The first phase of lunch preparation begins.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T00:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hRx2DBKb#DfyD2tDzir8ZPj5QlO8DHA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T00:45:31.217Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T00:29:20.095Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>4005d7d06c136796b093ec1a946802633c9cb3fad4b852ef0654b27debff10c7</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Starting Over: Back to School Part 2</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T18:25:56.011Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>118</airingId>
    <content>The coronavirus has changed everything. How can we overcome this crisis? How can we restore our normal lifestyles? In Japan, Tokyo had the largest number of coronavirus infections. In this series, we look inside 3 places in this megacity. Hotels, where many people stay. Schools, where young people gather. And airports, major transportation hubs. We'll bring you insight on how the people in these places are trying to recover.
With 87 million passengers per year, Haneda Airport is one of the world's busiest. But with COVID-19 wiping out most of its sales, it is now struggling to stay afloat. The opening of Haneda Airport Garden, an adjoining multi-use complex with lodging and a bus terminal, originally scheduled for April of 2020, has now been indefinitely put on hold. In this program we focus on some of the key people fighting the uphill battle of restoring the airport to its former glory.</content>
    <description>In a normal year, Haneda Airport is one of the world's busiest airports, but COVID-19 has decimated its sales. We follow those who continue to work to restore it to its former glory.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T00:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9At0SAaZ#9svg9Ds_oV6nFgTZbUv-1g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T00:45:29.465Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T00:29:22.029Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>45b8b14304e349f324edac2890dfa9e880bc38d009c9fbcfc013a8de5a1be587</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Starting Over: The Flight Goes On Part 2</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T17:00:41.344Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Wl8AkAJL#8sWCFg1TMS23fC7SApJ5NA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>123</airingId>
    <content>Just north of Tokyo there's a place where whale fossils have been found on dry land! And the shaved ice desserts in that area taste amazing! Could those 2 facts be related? How can we find out? We'll need to call in an expert. We'll need to call ... Ground Detective Simon Wallis, a professor whose sideline is traveling around Japan solving geologic mysteries! In this episode, he travels to the Chichibu area in Saitama Prefecture to see just what makes their shaved ice so tasty!</content>
    <description>Ground Detective Simon Wallis travels around Japan solving geologic mysteries! In this episode, he travels to the Chichibu area in Saitama prefecture to see what makes their shaved ice so tasty!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T00:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KsNUGZJR#GnuCtIU0ChuEJc0prevpXw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T00:45:26.660Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T00:29:22.987Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>ffe2d5132f593c25a762ed0ef4ab7839d428eb1f6d54e0c61d4e6094f5b109a7</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ground Detective Simon Wallis: File #1 "The Case of the Kakigori"</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T17:29:51.058Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/8cliSTgT#P5ZaZqEAL3I64W-lfg4_Xw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>124</airingId>
    <content>Hayama, a seaside resort to the west of Tokyo, is known for its high-quality vegetables and beef ... but not its seafood. But it wasn't always this way. Hatakeyama Akira, born and raised in the town, is determined to restore the place of her childhood memories. As the only fisherwoman in the port, she is working to revive the fishing industry, establishing a direct sales shop and her own kitchen. Her goal -- to bring Hayama's rich seafood culture back to local dining tables.</content>
    <description>Hatakeyama Akira, the only fisherwoman in the port of Hayama - is determined to save the local fishing industry and bring the area's rich seafood culture back.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T00:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/xd4UAbwb#Tz6w1CBYvu-XIp5MvpPasw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T00:45:31.019Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T00:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>3f143edf4cd22493b4832b94f4128c57ca21278be1fff0982eef055e5f0552af</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T00:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Through the Kitchen Window: Hayama - Bringing Seafood Back</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-28T00:32:06.550Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MNoCWSRD#RHltHHuzg-P6IEli9wyHSw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>126</airingId>
    <content>Although the ninja are known for working in the shadows, the early Edo period found them serving in one-hundred-man units. Join Chris Glenn and Professor Yuji Yamada as they explore Tokyo and visit sites associated with the ninja. Their tour -- interspersed with reenactments -- reveals the deep connection between the ninja and Edo, the old name for Tokyo.</content>
    <description>Join Chris Glenn and Professor Yuji Yamada as they explore Tokyo and visit sites associated with the ninja. Their tour reveals the deep connection between the ninja and Edo, the old name for Tokyo.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T01:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ZE4w2IqL#1TdYc_DWNuN4jE_Wvo_Kog</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T01:00:29.987Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T00:44:20.073Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>3019</seriesId>
    <sha256>573d17413c7ddd5a7912bab590e5deddde6128b707347ec8a07282caa978497c</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T00:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>NINJA TRUTH Episode 14: Ninja in Tokyo</subtitle>
    <title>15 Minutes</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-24T16:59:27.993Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/CoNEnTZJ#YrbaEP8rb8h1bpfGM5_-fQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>