<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-30T04:15:03.840Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>da958502b69dde1e</seriesId>
  <title>Her Story</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>012</airingId>
    <content>Pham Thi Ngan owns Tohe, a Vietnamese art shop lifting disabled children out of poverty by selling clothes and accessories featuring children's artworks. The artists receive a copyright fee. The salon's success has helped establish social businesses in Vietnam and many companies now hope to collaborate with Tohe. Pham Thi Ngan helps children develop their talents, alleviating poverty while building a viable business. We look at the secret behind her success and the change she is achieving.</content>
    <description>Introducing Pham Thi Ngan who saves disabled Vietnamese children from poverty by commercializing their drawings and giving back some of its profit to them.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wBtS1L5B#UQmlT3HYYopM-amORElZ7A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T01:50:27.891Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T01:29:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>0c033061218713dbef86a7187e905ed3545f2f3ec7034ed4f4e86c3354d34369</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Work of Heart</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T04:03:03.479Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/g0siTbLJ#t0-pO_qh2yGyGTdGklu_GA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>There is a strong demand for prostheses in Cambodia, where more than 43,000 people are reported to have injuries caused by mines and unexploded ordnance, and children with polio and traffic accident victims also require prostheses. However, the country suffers from a shortage of prosthetists since the Pol Pot regime murdered many people with technical skills. Sisary Kheng is Cambodia's first female prosthetist. We examine some of the issues facing Cambodia as we look at her remarkable work.</content>
    <description>We introduce the work of Sisary Kheng, Cambodia's first female prosthetist, as she helps people with limb injuries, from mines, traffic accidents and other causes gain a new lease of life.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hFhwATZR#UzXp2tDCDsHf334pvf-HfQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T01:50:32.220Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T01:29:20.117Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>f95808b0350c5600df5285f92d1ec7af4f1e1d8e04ea53c30b21f7983992554a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Another Walk of Life</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T04:03:05.997Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IRlUCY5A#HU-gFdrZgH5Q4bu31dKkSA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>036</airingId>
    <content>Salinee Hurley sells solar generators to remote villages in Thailand, where there are still 2 million homes without electricity. Salinee offers affordable 5-year payment plans, and trains young villagers to provide maintenance to the equipment. Thanks to her, schools have been able to use computers, and villagers can work at night, giving an opportunity to increase their income. Salinee hopes that electricity will help people improve the quality of their lives.</content>
    <description>Salinee Hurley sells solar generators to Thai villages, allowing schools to use computers and locals to work at night to increase their incomes. She hopes electricity will improve people's lives.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PBlw2TgY#DeSt2jQ6wJJORZdN3p0Fyw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T01:50:28.788Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T01:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>78510e61d3f166a915e2ac3b6d66d71e04755fdb1d78c7b705928590ee67babc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Light Comes to Life</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T03:59:03.116Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/m18WGYgD#PxENMl0koeoRLZDWVjCD5g</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>