<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-01T07:20:03.346Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>da958502b69dde1e</seriesId>
  <title>Her Story</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>012</airingId>
    <content>Pham Thi Ngan owns Tohe, a Vietnamese art shop lifting disabled children out of poverty by selling clothes and accessories featuring children's artworks. The artists receive a copyright fee. The salon's success has helped establish social businesses in Vietnam and many companies now hope to collaborate with Tohe. Pham Thi Ngan helps children develop their talents, alleviating poverty while building a viable business. We look at the secret behind her success and the change she is achieving.</content>
    <description>Introducing Pham Thi Ngan who saves disabled Vietnamese children from poverty by commercializing their drawings and giving back some of its profit to them.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/wBtS1L5B#UQmlT3HYYopM-amORElZ7A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T01:50:27.891Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T01:29:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>0c033061218713dbef86a7187e905ed3545f2f3ec7034ed4f4e86c3354d34369</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Work of Heart</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T04:03:03.479Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/g0siTbLJ#t0-pO_qh2yGyGTdGklu_GA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>Lin Chinglan, a professional dancer from Taiwan, was born with hearing loss, but trained hard to teach herself to dance in time to floor vibrations caused by the beat. She established Taiwan's only dance group exclusively for members with hearing loss. Through their performances, the group hopes to challenge prejudice against people with disabilities, helping to create a more inclusive society.</content>
    <description>Lin Chinglan, from Taiwan, overcame hearing loss to become a professional dancer. We follow her efforts to combat prejudice against people with disabilities.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-20T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/7upAFRYK#uuw4oTYLSu0bR4lL9SKIJg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-20T01:50:30.133Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-20T01:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>58c46d926198cb4a144507354b0dd8fd8385857c0e1d63ec1cc2a064c4702bca</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-20T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Never Missing a Beat</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-20T02:39:00.854Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5Lh1zKjI#ER8A4UO4Du8x88DY2dTR6A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>There is a strong demand for prostheses in Cambodia, where more than 43,000 people are reported to have injuries caused by mines and unexploded ordnance, and children with polio and traffic accident victims also require prostheses. However, the country suffers from a shortage of prosthetists since the Pol Pot regime murdered many people with technical skills. Sisary Kheng is Cambodia's first female prosthetist. We examine some of the issues facing Cambodia as we look at her remarkable work.</content>
    <description>We introduce the work of Sisary Kheng, Cambodia's first female prosthetist, as she helps people with limb injuries, from mines, traffic accidents and other causes gain a new lease of life.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hFhwATZR#UzXp2tDCDsHf334pvf-HfQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T01:50:32.220Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T01:29:20.117Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>f95808b0350c5600df5285f92d1ec7af4f1e1d8e04ea53c30b21f7983992554a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Another Walk of Life</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T04:03:05.997Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/IRlUCY5A#HU-gFdrZgH5Q4bu31dKkSA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>In 2015, Evilita Adriani launched Ojesy, a motorbike-taxi dispatch service with only female drivers, providing safe transport for women in Indonesia, where around 90% of the population is Muslim. As it is taboo in Islam for women to touch men other than family members, it was difficult for women to use services with male drivers. Over its first year, the new service grew rapidly in popularity. Looking at the entrepreneurship of Evilita Adriani, we see how the lifestyles of Indonesian women are changing.</content>
    <description>We introduce Evilita Adriani, a university student from Indonesia who launched a motorcycle taxi dispatch service crewed entirely by female Muslim drivers.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-17T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RNwyjRLa#MVPlc6Vofp_bh6JIH0ErGw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-17T01:50:33.760Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-17T01:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>adc293f17e6bcfc694b051cfc2c7771bf199c2f1006b7088c78abd2b5dc49a1c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-17T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Starting a New Cycle</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-17T02:36:16.358Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/NQoBWSYC#guletFqWoQf6phgj8DQ5MA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>034</airingId>
    <content>Yang Hui Ling is a wheelchair user who researches restaurants and hotels in Taiwan to check how accessible they are to the disabled: whether they have barrier-free toilets or if the floors are flat. She then releases this information on an app. Hui Ling has employed 300 or more people with disabilities as researchers for information to be featured on the app, and helps them to participate in society. Hui Ling hopes for a society where the disabled can actively make use of the city.</content>
    <description>Yang Hui Ling researches restaurant and hotel accessibility for the disabled in Taiwan, and releases this information on an app. She hopes for a society in which the disabled can be actively involved.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-24T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/YGpXmaab#Mn6-JA0wdK5w1VnrOPZxKA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-24T01:50:30.742Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-24T01:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>16373710100e6f0155bb5147e81a236606904ea9ba2b40969b7dfc3e621fff35</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-24T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Out on the Town</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-24T02:35:14.458Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/8awFHYgS#mtd79R3qL-lAvNwVkr_aiQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>035</airingId>
    <content>Comma Leung is a designer from Hong Kong who creates items for everyday use that are geared for the physically disabled and the elderly. Her past work, such as wallets that allow blind people to differentiate bills, as well as coin purses that can be used without the fingers, have earned high praise. She also teaches the intellectually challenged the joys of designing by creating products from their own drawings. Comma hopes that the power of design can help people live more fulfilling lives.</content>
    <description>Comma Leung is a designer from Hong Kong. Her designs are characterized by the ideas she employs to make them useful for the disabled and the elderly, hoping to improve their quality of life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-27T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/hrYHEQBJ#55xfmw0Rt_3wJt9Si6L0nQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-27T01:50:31.497Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-27T01:29:20.164Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>bd1d5e4d3175e73e261059b2f9984ecf61a1ad8a5efa5da54a2a159d63051081</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-27T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Kind by Design</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-27T02:19:07.775Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/VjRjiKBI#brzTPBBqvxbM09FAuD-LWw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>036</airingId>
    <content>Salinee Hurley sells solar generators to remote villages in Thailand, where there are still 2 million homes without electricity. Salinee offers affordable 5-year payment plans, and trains young villagers to provide maintenance to the equipment. Thanks to her, schools have been able to use computers, and villagers can work at night, giving an opportunity to increase their income. Salinee hopes that electricity will help people improve the quality of their lives.</content>
    <description>Salinee Hurley sells solar generators to Thai villages, allowing schools to use computers and locals to work at night to increase their incomes. She hopes electricity will improve people's lives.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T01:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PBlw2TgY#DeSt2jQ6wJJORZdN3p0Fyw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T01:50:28.788Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T01:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>78510e61d3f166a915e2ac3b6d66d71e04755fdb1d78c7b705928590ee67babc</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Light Comes to Life</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T03:59:03.116Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/m18WGYgD#PxENMl0koeoRLZDWVjCD5g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>046</airingId>
    <content>Abe Noriko operates a hotel in Miyagi Prefecture's Minamisanriku, one of the areas hit hardest by the Great East Japan Earthquake in March, 2011. When reconstruction efforts began, Noriko focused on encouraging tourism in order to stimulate the local economy. But with the recent spread of COVID-19, tourism has all but vanished under self-imposed isolation, and the region faces a new crisis. Noriko draws upon her past experiences, proposing idea after idea to cheer on the local residents.</content>
    <description>Abe Noriko operates a hotel in Minamisanriku, one of the towns hit hardest by the 2011 disaster. As COVID-19 threatens the survival of local businesses, she does her all to keep the town active.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-17T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ugoU1Q7D#nCw0B8hO4VeC5rR0hFuOJQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-17T02:00:29.686Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-17T01:29:20.168Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>5b9f5956657e7cd6028ae48eb4096f540934757fe347b2109b5bfe61f508dc0e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-17T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Nine Years of Cheer</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T09:56:04.485Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/H0o2mIoL#VGsDVkKQVdufS0nOcVIpRg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>050</airingId>
    <content>Nantarika Chansue is a Thai veterinarian who specializes in aquatic animals. For over 30 years, she's treated everything from fish to turtles and even whales. She insists that no matter how grave the injury, all animals deserve a chance at recovery, so she's implemented medical techniques formerly used only with humans, such as casting prostheses. Many of the injuries sustained by the animals are due to human negligence, which Nantarika strongly opposes for the safety of aquatic life.</content>
    <description>Nantarika Chansue is a Thai veterinarian specializing in aquatic animals. Many of those she treats have been injured by fishermen or tourists, so she works to raise awareness of the sanctity of life.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/uZ0mSAiS#go9kYhb3l6Tgp5zb_IuoEQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T02:00:31.640Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T01:29:20.102Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>908771c57474e663ad62a6847e919d23d06a8c8dcc12d1c40b18d3f8a1604dae</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Healing Shells</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T07:43:33.333Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/YYlGwJaZ#_1lWFrPZgB-THD9jEXCWPQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>051</airingId>
    <content>The geographical conditions of the Philippines subject it to frequent earthquakes, volcanic eruptions, typhoons and floods that together claim over 2,000 lives each year, while the country still lacks adequate training in emergency management. In response, Sandy Montano began teaching courses on preparation of emergency bags, evacuation and first aid. She also started manufacturing unique emergency rations, using the process as a means to help disaster victims financially recover.</content>
    <description>In the Philippines, over 2,000 lives are lost each year to natural disasters. Sandy Montano teaches courses on emergency preparation while providing a way for disaster victims to financially recover.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-24T02:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fpoHTYRB#42qtWnGPtlshv_kM3CMS4A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-24T02:00:32.530Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-24T01:29:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2048</seriesId>
    <sha256>2dfae7671bfd59f7f76d269f35be9c34568b23d7d9bfb98a0e70b9e3d4e9911f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-24T01:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>A Natural Reaction</subtitle>
    <title>Her Story</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T04:25:02.975Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/sJhwWDCD#lexrCDof_XA0HaiRlVXVSA</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>