<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-28T15:50:02.922Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>de77f30c8ee5dd46</seriesId>
  <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>030</airingId>
    <content>Hundreds of thousands of insect species make their home in the jungles of Costa Rica. But it's a constant battle for survival. Bugs of all shapes and sizes have had to develop unique defensive strategies just to make it through the day. Some use color to advertise their venomous shield; others blend in by mimicking the natural environment. A few even resemble excrement to guard their privacy ... with great success! But none will capture your heart like a tiny yellow bug that smiles and dances!</content>
    <description>Survival is the name of the game in the insect kingdom of Costa Rica. Some use color to stand out; others resemble excrement to blend in. But all will woo you with their clever defensive strategies!</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-28T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/9RRBEapY#SxtNFpnVN0AUaCL2ZL1uIQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-28T00:50:26.467Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-28T00:24:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>12d5f433554bedac2b103efc78d38ea15c6637f717d04f5ba26d1b4c6bf9d494</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-28T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Masters of Disguise -- Rare Insects, Costa Rica</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T13:25:35.201Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/yAdxlaCZ#sFrNWcOCcXYqhOfPon42cw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>047</airingId>
    <content>Reaching 1.5 meters in length, the Japanese giant salamander will need more than its size to battle daunting odds. Environmental degradation and loss of habitat have led to a decline in these "living fossils" that have remained relatively unchanged in 170 million years. After heavy rains caused massive damage to one region's towns and rivers, a team of experts, assisted by local schoolchildren, launches a project to locate and return their amphibian neighbors that have been washed downstream.</content>
    <description>Japanese giant salamanders can reach 100 years of age and 1.5 meters in length. But these living fossils face environmental degradation and habitat loss. Luckily, schoolchildren are there to help.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OxsDgQJL#xhkXXwNiXGmP69ZfLmgReg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T00:50:16.412Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T00:24:22.821Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>1bc31b2b18a4ec0ce38f1953d018d96ee76094893795803b4d582b6fb180a527</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Neighbor Helping Neighbor -- Giant Salamander, Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:28:15.637Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/hp8AiYSR#KVEL9UcDyQbLOivgf9JZrg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>048</airingId>
    <content>The male Lawe's Parotia could make any ballerina blush. That ultra-black tuxedo-like plumage is known to absorb 99% of light, making him the blackest bird on earth. His courtship dance starts with a bow; the feathers extend into a tutu-like skirt while dancing on the tips of his toes. Ducking his black head onto iridescent breast feathers produces an eerie "smiley face." The performance ends with a rhythmic shaking of the head from side to side. But the finicky female may still peck and reject!</content>
    <description>The male Lawe's parotia is quite the catch with its ultra-black plumage, romantic courting dance and spotless performance stage. But the finicky female will peck and reject for the slightest offense.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1J4hDCSa#AFQXXYgEg383-JMTjC61Sg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T00:51:30.858Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T00:24:20.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>008479d809cf4a1622480858c3404690b376c8b1f063ee180507f44c4d631530</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ballet in Black -- Parotia, Papua New Guinea</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:16:17.659Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>049</airingId>
    <content>Dirty scavenger? Laughing opportunist? Oh, that's all a misunderstanding! The hyena clan is a marvel to behold. School starts early: just a few weeks after birth. The young are introduced to a strict matriarchal hierarchy where dissent is rare and males hardly register. Teamwork is an important subject for patrolling borders and stalking prey. But those first at the kill scene best get their fill before the clan's alpha female arrives. She eats uncontested. Her role? Simply producing offspring.</content>
    <description>School starts early for the hyena: just a few weeks after birth! It's introduced to a strict social system ensuring peace within the clan. The fact that males hardly register is no laughing matter!</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-26T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1ZkWnSCZ#s1xfa5jVvOQmhnaHTEJJPQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-26T00:50:27.320Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-26T00:24:24.502Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>45e960e6ce9d30f828a89b77fd98670deca9d683aed366f660761c53fa1db134</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-26T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Learning the System -- Spotted Hyena, Tanzania</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T09:40:51.493Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Ud8mnKwa#7qnXU8VbeT6EQgShjUbBQQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>