<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2020-12-26T07:15:03.872Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>de77f30c8ee5dd46</seriesId>
  <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>047</airingId>
    <content>Reaching 1.5 meters in length, the Japanese giant salamander will need more than its size to battle daunting odds. Environmental degradation and loss of habitat have led to a decline in these "living fossils" that have remained relatively unchanged in 170 million years. After heavy rains caused massive damage to one region's towns and rivers, a team of experts, assisted by local schoolchildren, launches a project to locate and return their amphibian neighbors that have been washed downstream.</content>
    <description>Japanese giant salamanders can reach 100 years of age and 1.5 meters in length. But these living fossils face environmental degradation and habitat loss. Luckily, schoolchildren are there to help.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-21T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/OxsDgQJL#xhkXXwNiXGmP69ZfLmgReg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-21T00:50:16.412Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-21T00:24:22.821Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>1bc31b2b18a4ec0ce38f1953d018d96ee76094893795803b4d582b6fb180a527</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-21T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Neighbor Helping Neighbor -- Giant Salamander, Japan</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:28:15.637Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>048</airingId>
    <content>The male Lawe's Parotia could make any ballerina blush. That ultra-black tuxedo-like plumage is known to absorb 99% of light, making him the blackest bird on earth. His courtship dance starts with a bow; the feathers extend into a tutu-like skirt while dancing on the tips of his toes. Ducking his black head onto iridescent breast feathers produces an eerie "smiley face." The performance ends with a rhythmic shaking of the head from side to side. But the finicky female may still peck and reject!</content>
    <description>The male Lawe's parotia is quite the catch with its ultra-black plumage, romantic courting dance and spotless performance stage. But the finicky female will peck and reject for the slightest offense.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-19T00:50:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/1J4hDCSa#AFQXXYgEg383-JMTjC61Sg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-19T00:51:30.858Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-19T00:24:20.005Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>4030</seriesId>
    <sha256>008479d809cf4a1622480858c3404690b376c8b1f063ee180507f44c4d631530</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-19T00:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Ballet in Black -- Parotia, Papua New Guinea</subtitle>
    <title>Darwin's Amazing Animals</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T03:16:17.659Z</uploadedDate>
  </episode>
</episodeList>