<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-03-19T12:20:03.295Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>f85084a2d40d190a</seriesId>
  <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>011</airingId>
    <content>As the Black Lives Matter protests continue across the U.S., there is another group fighting racism. Mirroring the spread of the coronavirus pandemic, the number of hate incidents against people of Asian descent has also increased, and slanderous rhetoric like "China Virus" and "Kung Flu" are stoking racial tensions. How can we combat this stigma, prejudice and racism? We asked Dr. Russell Jeung, founder of an online organization that keeps track of racial incidents in the U.S.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Prof. Russel Jeung at San Francisco State University talks about Anti-Asian Racism in US in the time of Coronavirus.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-08T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/actWzDbC#szWNz5c6nP5SveZ3KNZEaQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-08T04:45:29.522Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-08T04:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>f7c38ff0a996307bd97e4fa63713b4f3216294958180404f288e9fc7d6fdc212</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-08T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fighting Anti-Asian Racism: Russell Jeung / Professor of Asian American Studies, San Francisco State University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:58:23.806Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/aIkCQajD#JMsyH42z1yTt4MI_kNiDsA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>012</airingId>
    <content>This year, as countries continue to grapple with the pandemic, there are many discussions about whether or not it is the right time to return to school. In the U.S., images of high school hallways packed with students not wearing facemasks went viral on social media, and in some states, schools have been forced to shut down shortly after reopening. But on the flipside, many students and their families are already experiencing difficulties with online learning. So, is this the right time to reopen schools? We asked the director of education UNESCO, Dr. Borhene Chakroun who joins us from Paris, France.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, she talks with Dr. Borhene Chakroun, Director of the Division for Policies and Lifelong Learning Systems in UNESCO.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-22T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/M09xiIKC#Ob0NclSrJthA9mha53hOSg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-22T04:45:20.368Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-22T04:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>013cdfc8440bbfed13c3990debd699ada9b1fe770c62407bf4c386730d6502b2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-22T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Is it the Right Time to Reopen Schools?: Borhene Chakroun / Director, Division for Policies and Lifelong Learning Systems, UNESCO</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T07:10:29.581Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/hw1hTKRB#QQygKtJks8A040mBSTZ4mQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>Major League Baseball, National Basketball League, US Open Tennis and other major sports have resumed in the U.S. But with coronavirus safety restrictions in place, things are not the same, with fewer games, officials in masks, cardboard cutout fans and canned applause. Yet, despite these measures, some athletes have contracted the virus. So, is it worthwhile to hold sporting events, and what about the Tokyo Olympics and Paralympics next year? We asked Sports Journalist, Matthew Futterman.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Matthew Futterman, Deputy Sports Editor of New York Times, talks about how sports events will be like in the COVID-19 era.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-23T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/pxoAgLrQ#akCrqSK8YlBAsBfENF-s0g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-23T04:45:29.933Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-23T04:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>4f3ba9a1a0d89928cdc0669f8b2991a2733bd15b527d1e43779a9198ab61fa14</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-23T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Sports in the COVID-19 Era: Matthew Futterman / Sports Journalist, New York Times</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-23T05:14:40.431Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gZ1ESL7K#vVrBuIp4VmU7cZg4ilsbtg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>016</airingId>
    <content>Recently more athletes are using their platforms to make political statements. Naomi Osaka wore 7 different masks at the US Open to honor victims of police brutality. LeBron James, a top NBA player, took a knee with teammates during the US National Anthem. As athlete voices become more powerful, sports leagues and corporate sponsors face a tough challenge. How far should protests go? Can sports and activism be separated? What about the Tokyo Olympics and Paralympics? We asked sports journalist Matthew Futterman.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Matthew Futterman, a sports journalist at New York Times, talks about athletes and activism quoting a case like Naomi Osaka.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-02T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/4c9hmAgZ#uqgrnyeVPinT64zDMWbMWg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-02T04:45:28.581Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-02T04:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>8f0f33e8eb184363c51fca0643227c2b7afdc17448d7047296263f73308c926c</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-02T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Athletes and Activism: Matthew Futterman / Sports Journalist, New York Times</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-02T05:20:41.840Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/ethX0QYS#PCrKRNzWE0sljHgULrRF9A</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>From concert halls and theaters to clubs and restaurants, many venues shutdown under the pandemic, depriving musicians and fans of the magic live music brings. But despite the lockdown, world-famous cellist Yo-Yo Ma picked up his instrument and began to play, sharing music remotely from his home to the world. Soon #SongsOfComfort became viral, providing a platform for artists, professionals or amateurs to express themselves. We asked Yo-Yo how music can help comfort us in these challenging times.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. A world-famous cellist Yo-Yo Ma performed live at home to share his creation online. We asked him how music can help people amid pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-24T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/6E0ijJZJ#EL5LxyUh7bl20dU50HfwiQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-24T04:45:32.872Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-24T04:29:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>f565a37d8f59febaa24c3a5a467fb0eb62359399346fdde44ddf4289b02722ee</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-24T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Music Can Give Comfort During the Pandemic: Yo-Yo Ma / Cellist</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:46:14.914Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/39sThAYR#omNom5zciuibWc3rgaoF9g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>The US presidential election and the chaotic aftermath have shown how deeply divided the country has been. And it looks like it will take a long time to fill the ditch. Yo-Yo Ma was born in France and immigrated to the U.S. in his childhood. He has played for successive presidents and seen the transition in the country. Our host, Del Irani, asked Yo-Yo Ma how he sees America. How can he find hope in the U.S.? And what role music can play.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. She asks Yo-Yo Ma, a world-famous cellist, how he sees America today which is deepley divided and how he can find hope with music.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-01T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/WR000ZyA#opmEycpmGBzxdLxjAM5B7w</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-01T04:45:31.337Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-01T04:29:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>32bbef0f62b743427637b4ed50f69c0f5e7efdd1f82c627bb71ec1b866db4709</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-01T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Has America Changed?: Yo-Yo Ma / Cellist</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:48:32.562Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/v0NzAISa#m_M_B3Z0hmgcRyDqgsp0HQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>020</airingId>
    <content>2020 has become a historic year for women. Senator Kamala Harris will be the first woman and person of color to serve as Vice President of the United States. Women also made significant gains in both the House and the Senate. Still, the number of women who will hold seats in Congress is only about 26%, far from equal representation. How can we enhance women's participation in politics? And why is it important? We asked Debbie Walsh, who has been helping women run for public office.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Debbie Walsh, director of Center for American Women and Politics, talks how we can enhance women's participation in politics.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-15T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/EA0QyJjI#JscEf0TsM2ioe7QgL3nIWg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-15T04:45:26.181Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-15T04:29:22.641Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>a5cecc4898d1ffc80e61fa3ad1e035d763c26b69fc3ece9936f1a95655bc9baa</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-15T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Can Women's Political Participation Be Enhanced?: Debbie Walsh / Director, Center for American Women and Politics, Rutgers University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-26T02:51:32.578Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/GE1lDQKB#fvU9QoO18zuzBzinZtKAQQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>021</airingId>
    <content>The year 2020 could go down in history. As the pandemic spread and the economy screeched to a halt, in the U.S., glaring income inequality and persistent racial disparities came to light. Then followed the contentious presidential election, further highlighting deep-seated divides. So, was 2020 the worst year ever? What can we learn from it? For our last episode of the year, we asked the renowned author Walter Isaacson for his insights and what history, and its great figures can teach us.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Walter Issacson, author, ex-chaiman and CEO of CNN, and ex-editor for TIME Magazine, talks about how he remembers the year 2020.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-29T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vxsVWQzY#YevyWUQle1TN0-CatnWfOA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-29T04:45:32.940Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-29T04:29:20.114Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>4385be52b7f901fe4fbe47a11d02770065205970eac1d47ecee57dab081183d2</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-29T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Will 2020 Be Remembered?: Walter Isaacson / Author, Professor of American History and Values at Tulane University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-29T05:32:08.784Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gYZU3LAT#F3OWDjAFwvb43e4OgaHY5Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>022</airingId>
    <content>As COVID-19 vaccinations begin across the U.S. and the new president soon be inaugurated, what can we expect from 2021? Walter Isaacson, a well-known author of bestselling biographies, is our first guest of the year. Recently he volunteered for the Pfizer/BioNTech clinical trial, where new technologies were used to develop a vaccine, innovations created by scientists he is writing about in his new book. We asked Mr. Isaacson what we can learn from our history and these scientific breakthroughs.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Walter Issacson, author, ex-chaiman and CEO of CNN, and ex-editor for TIME Magazine, talks about challenges in the year 2021.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-05T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/3h9lGCpT#KD8Zscr3XkcsK0gJ2c22vQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-05T04:45:18.353Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-05T04:29:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>0da2f3890e14e407705d628f3d81a1251d0c62edbe2bf2a00952f29c93e5530d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-05T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Challenges in 2021: Walter Isaacson / Author, Professor of American History and Values at Tulane University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T07:18:02.343Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/URgEHAiK#8PYMScL5uQfKQJQZeYLVHg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>023</airingId>
    <content>The U.S. has long been a leader of democratic nations; a pillar of strength to its allies when facing communist countries or those with authoritarian leaders, although there are arguments concerning some of its foreign operations. But the events on January 6 may have lowered America's position. Some even say it was the darkest day in U.S. history. How will that day be remembered? What did it all mean? And how can the U.S. redeem its democratic standing? We asked Harvard historian Jill Lepore.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Jill Lepore, a Harvard University Professor, analyzes why and how incidents at US Capitol happened after Trump's tweets.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-26T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RAxUVb7Z#s7A3ehIGYT0UlucRCX_9kA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-26T04:45:29.118Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-26T04:29:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>2b278102d01c6df9122e2b8912486852b0ce8f7440a8a8c5c3a1abc9c940f98b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-26T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Will the Capitol Riot Be Reckoned with in US History?: Jill Lepore / Professor of American History, Harvard University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-26T21:44:37.358Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Na5AVILD#DTJKaPXYJPi9gEMxz4mgEA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>024</airingId>
    <content>The first 100 days of a new administration is seen as a benchmark measuring a president's early success. President Joseph R. Biden Jr. is moving aggressively to implement his agenda such as the vaccination plan and economic relief package. Many goals require support from Congress. How can President Biden push through key policies and win bipartisan support to unite the country? We asked Capri Cafaro about the path President Biden may take.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. This time, Capri Cafaro of American Univ. and Fmr. Democratic Leader of the Ohio State Senate about the path President Biden may take.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-02T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/TE1GzYaL#lM4QJzHuvlhY1xiEyJtGaw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-02T04:45:28.622Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-02T04:29:23.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>521e1151c3c2e1da52c7e7ac64b9efeec80195df38523e2b1cc7b61d52aacce6</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-02T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>How Can the Biden Administration achieve Its Agenda?: Capri Cafaro / Professor of Public Affairs, American University/Former Democratic Leader of the Ohio State Senate</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-02T05:23:14.520Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/oQojDYyZ#WyLComNlDi_pBMae5uKXaA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>025</airingId>
    <content>For the last several years, a troubling trend shows global hunger is on the rise, with about 690 million people undernourished. And the coronavirus pandemic adds to the numbers. In 2020 the World Food Programme won the Nobel Peace Prize for its efforts to combat hunger. While this helped their mission, they still face many obstacles in their quest to eradicate hunger. We checked in with Valerie Guarnieri to see how the WFP is promoting food security under the pandemic and what is needed to reach their goals.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. Today, Valerie Guarnieri, Assistant Executive Director of World Food Programme, talks about how they are combating hunger in the Pandemic.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-09T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/nhN1SAZD#6d1Gn9sAXrW0gjIcSjAqaA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-09T04:45:27.740Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-09T04:29:25.135Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>eb9e1bf1e3753fec6d5fccfe86a8ed892b2ef2c90eeb27297825743ad9e706d1</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-09T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Combating Hunger During the Pandemic: Valerie Guarnieri / Assistant Executive Director, World Food Programme</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-09T07:21:29.001Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/dhJAADoY#gsVqCAPqlrU2hUl_eaiGTA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>026</airingId>
    <content>President Biden faces many foreign policy challenges. During Donald Trump's term, the U.S. pulled out from an array of international accords and institutions. While Biden proclaims, "America is back," it may take years to regain the world's trust. And just 10-days after the inauguration, Myanmar's military led a coup, potentially shifting power in the region and strengthening China's influence. We asked former NSC member Charles Kupchan how the Biden administration will shape their foreign policy.</content>
    <description>An experienced anchor Del Irani has a cutting-edge dialogue. Today, Charles Kupchan, Professor at Georgetown University talks about US foreign policy especially on China and Asian situation.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-16T04:45:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/oJAymZoS#Flxh8_AeC8bjxDxpFbHMHw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-16T04:45:28.283Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-16T04:29:20.012Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2085</seriesId>
    <sha256>24016703bdde5ca35129d078942ec331b8de8640b5cd2d79de5930d3b760f854</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-16T04:30:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>President Biden's Foreign Policy Challenges: Charles Kupchan / Professor of International Affairs, Georgetown University</subtitle>
    <title>DEEPER LOOK from New York</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-16T05:50:25.847Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/g48UlJpJ#fzlcCalX0_rcnq2cmUMtMQ</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>