<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="episodes-toc.xsl"?>
<episodeList>
  <lastUpdated>2021-05-12T17:10:05.277Z</lastUpdated>
  <seriesId>fb3ddf5a1a053dcd</seriesId>
  <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
  <episode>
    <airingId>013</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, an essential part of any makeup kit: makeup brushes known in Japanese as "fude." The very first of these brushes, now known as some of the best in the world, were created in Japan in 1981, and were inspired by the traditional "fude" used in Japanese calligraphy. We dive into the story behind the Japanese "fude" brushes that caused a revolution in the world of makeup.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the story of the revolutionary makeup brushes known in Japanese as "fude."</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-18T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ihlkWbJI#RM2xN_54nqD5qaBEcbbEbQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-18T16:00:33.029Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-18T15:44:20.062Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>f3519f5e6dd970759d28dbce8f1f9e4d0c8ae8ca3b4fb4f71646da2956b33485</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-18T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Makeup Brushes</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:54:32.286Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/6hV1SYrb#oGCO1NnMaGbXzLGZKpokAw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>014</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, we take a ride on Japan's world-beloved compact motorcycles. Over 100 million of these revolutionary compact motorcycles have been produced to date. They were developed by Soichiro Honda, whose company, named after Honda himself, became world-renowned in a single generation. Join us as we ride into the unknown tale of this brilliant engineer's trailblazing compact motorcycles.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, we take a ride into the unknown tale of Japan's world-beloved compact motorcycles.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-02T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/qslwVZDQ#tQy23hW7VGCp5vUPE5BpKQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-02T16:00:26.405Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-02T15:44:20.008Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>35f3ecb6c0d2ba90012631b79a78ea20d9d7d0814f6c7fa229fca79c43c93f1f</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-02T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Compact Motorcycles</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:51:54.972Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/r4VDiKaD#yTSDQiOOwXhboOYV0aotaQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>015</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a product used in over 20 countries and regions: stay-tight fasteners, nuts used with bolts in railroads, bridges, towers, and more. When normal nuts experience vibration, they sometimes come loose. But stay-tight fasteners, developed in Japan in 1974, overcame this problem. Learn the dramatic story behind the nuts, including a surprising spot that inspired their creation: a shrine!</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, stay-tight fasteners, nuts used in railroads, bridges, and more that don't shake loose.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-09T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/P00yDByD#S2stOnzJoPi1BRBtVPSIDA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-09T16:00:22.583Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-09T15:44:20.028Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>8b2984254d7fa333e1d6a8052a9fce41a452a2d987726ac911cfd93da7877221</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-09T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Stay-Tight Fasteners</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:56:53.971Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/pEUzBAqR#oj7th-ZpGPknF7AycuHdIA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>016</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, one of the world's most famous video game characters: Pac-Man. The iconic yellow ball with a mouth that gobbles up dots and runs away from ghosts was born in Japan in 1980, and holds the world record for "most successful coin-operated arcade game." Discover the backstory behind this iconic character, including how its shape was inspired by none other than pizza!</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, one of the world's most famous video game characters: the yellow ball named Pac-Man.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-16T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/2Nk13ara#2a-Bp01wJITcspf_vriyJw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-16T16:00:27.940Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-16T15:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>ffe8aaac7e851114773ad468794e23353575960fb2ec7a053fdc92879da4558a</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-16T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Video Game Character</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:41:57.554Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Z0cHVabD#1D4TKYgDlEw8hOl_7Zk2lw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>017</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, pedal assist electric bicycles, which give you a helpful boost of power when you pedal and help you enjoy relaxed cycling even on steep hills. The first pedal assist electric bicycles were produced in 1993 in Japan, and these revolutionary inventions are now used and loved worldwide. We pedal into the little-known, behind-the-scenes story of how these bicycles were invented.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, pedal assist electric bicycles, which give you a helpful boost of power when you pedal.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-30T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/YcUhkCiI#fA9FNh4ZZM20UEdd3BWEaw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-30T16:00:28.445Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-30T15:44:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>3b6b8ef047014c4ab2a3cbc24f11cb44932c8e9d1bf141b19e2171656c22f5c8</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-30T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Pedal Assist Electric Bicycles</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-30T22:58:35.877Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/1MERxADb#KFpxdg0u73inkHFxKRcgvA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>018</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, cooling gel sheets, which can be applied to the forehead for cooling relief when you're feeling feverish. These sheets were developed in Japan in 1994, and were inspired by none other than a certain pub dish! The sheets are now sold in some 20 countries and regions, and about 400 million are used per year. Join us as we discover the little-known story behind Japan's cooling gel sheets.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, cooling gel sheets, applied to the forehead for relief when you're feeling feverish.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-06T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/RJsESSaC#9Nh9EmikeRg6LZBoPzrTaw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-06T16:00:32.415Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-06T15:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>b1069f3ab49e32a0eb52b333a30cc40d7a80fb1bf31b8f628fc36c84ae188813</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-06T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Cooling Gel Sheets</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-06T17:16:10.792Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/SksCQQzQ#LOWOW2PMWBdllx48rTHjPQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>019</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, fiber tip pens, invented by a Japanese stationery firm in 1963. These water-based pens improved on the firm's oil-based pens, whose ink feathered and bled. Thanks to early user Lyndon Johnson, 36th President of the United States, they became a hit. Some 2.2 billion have been produced and sold in over 100 countries and regions. This time, the little-known story behind fiber tip pens.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, water-based fiber tip pens, invented by a Japanese stationery firm in 1963.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-20T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/vMkFQaJZ#vocD0zbacoFnvLRAgaLbvQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-20T16:00:44.611Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-20T15:44:20.098Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>875a3237d8fb3a663f032669ba2e8991eec77b03ba3f971b1c05ebc54bef898b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-20T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Fiber Tip Pens</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-20T16:32:40.199Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/NUwxTITZ#SAECRqAJUjXGFRBJ_N7hZg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>020</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, durable timepieces that don't break when dropped: shock resistant wristwatches. These unique watches were created by a Japanese firm in 1983, and are now available in 138 countries and regions. Over 100 million units have been shipped to date. Discover their surprising inspiration -- a child playing with a rubber ball in a park -- and more in the little-known story behind this invention.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, durable timepieces that don't break when dropped: shock resistant wristwatches.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-03T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/TaIknbhI#vfGy4Z0zJ2YBob1uqg9hkQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-03T16:00:29.853Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-03T15:44:23.018Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>162984653b0de750e25f44d4ce7302048b8a56765b9ec75b74af5e21650ba49d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-03T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Shock Resistant Wristwatches</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-04T23:47:19.128Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/WS50xR7a#x5DPWD99dxeZS5iKF-Oypw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>021</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the food you can eat anytime, anywhere, with no need for bowls or plates: Cup ramen. Invented by Momofuku Ando in an attempt to spread his instant ramen worldwide, Cup ramen has been sold in over 80 countries and regions to date. And an incredible 40 billion cups have been sold! This time, slurp up the secrets behind this hit cup-based Japanese invention.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the food you can eat anytime, anywhere, with no need for bowls or plates: Cup ramen.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-17T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/r00R1AaT#9spQWDashKOwUdLQL4FmoQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-17T16:00:32.176Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-17T15:44:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>27557204c9d24d9de32df122c0d3c2c5c45071492147266bf6cc878b61ecbeae</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-17T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Cup Ramen</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-17T17:06:50.793Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/KpESnBbI#MqixP0FIPtJvZzTfoG7rXw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>022</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, probiotic drinks, now consumed in 40 countries and regions. They were created by Yakult founder Minoru Shirota, who succeeded in cultivating strong lactic acid bacteria that could survive digestive fluids. With the philosophy "a healthy intestinal tract leads to a long life," Shirota spread his probiotic drink far and wide. Join us and learn more about the story behind these drinks.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, probiotic drinks, which aid in stomach health and are now popular around the world.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-24T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8NUknBgS#FNUuapNs12l0yNXlL84NWA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-24T16:00:28.938Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-24T15:44:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>189ff85e6e2bfab0c4f98d5f348a994ea20d5785650c7e49deca8c3ed99a4d35</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-24T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Probiotic Drinks</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-24T17:05:46.038Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/MdNwkDSD#vwV0bypxjyhRU7ZjSebS8w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>024</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, umami seasoning. Umami, one of the 5 basic tastes, was christened by chemist Kikunae Ikeda. Ikeda traced it to the glutamate found in kombu kelp dashi stock, an essential part of Japanese cuisine. The umami seasoning invented by Ikeda became a long-selling hit, and is now used in over 100 countries and regions. Discover the little-known tale of this hit culinary invention.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, umami seasoning, a long-selling hit now used in 106 countries worldwide.</description>
    <endDate>2021-02-10T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/8JB3WSrY#HbmzPCfmKH74FqDGL52Eig</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-02-10T16:00:27.185Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-02-10T15:44:20.036Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>af21d515a10886313786990cc5a6e86030d6bc37cc80cb148948e2052a40ed12</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-02-10T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Umami Seasoning</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-02-10T19:52:55.507Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/E45inDZC#BnU81cQQ709AzPoGvBb_jQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>025</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, blue LEDs, or light-emitting diodes. The world's first blue LEDs were created in 1989 by a research team at Nagoya University. These LEDs, now used in lightbulbs, smartphone screens, automobile headlights, and more sparked a lighting revolution. Discover the little-known story behind this Nobel Prize-winning invention.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, blue LEDs, or light-emitting diodes, which sparked a lighting revolution.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-03T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/c9RmmJRJ#Arl0RHOQVuE6YhPN2Nvgeg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-03T16:00:25.972Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-03T15:44:20.002Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>fc7bb0cb88798c38f7d58b397a35237a4651ac117d9cffa21cb723fa0e7f5cec</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-03T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Blue LEDs</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-03T16:38:21.485Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qshynKwC#m0OCeGPqFWGbzirC80XaZA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>026</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, spinning top toys, which have sold some 450 million units in over 80 countries and regions. Created by a Japanese firm in 1999, these tops, called Beyblades, are beloved by children worldwide. There was even a world championship held in Paris in 2018! This time, we take a spin into the story behind these toys, and learn how their creators were inspired by rock-paper-scissors.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, spinning top toys called Beyblades, which are beloved by children worldwide.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-10T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fsx20CQL#u8WcCghEGBDV0w1F1uML_A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-10T16:00:28.170Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-10T15:44:23.006Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>8c7d701018024d3e5a721acc06a4bb61fe75437a7d3c82acddda59c1455ed68b</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-10T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Spinning Top Toys</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-10T16:27:56.190Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/Cgp2FCjC#-z3unVXTXfR2pdkY6dC2bw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>027</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, home bread makers. These bread makers, first released in Japan in 1987, allow you to bake fresh bread at home by simply adding the ingredients and pushing a button. With over 10 million units shipped to 26 countries and regions, they're beloved worldwide. This time, the little-known story behind the 3 years of hard baking work involved in their creation.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, home bread makers, which let you to bake bread at home by simply pressing a button.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-17T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/GpZ1wIbS#N_PtQNy_Q12Ney6FJfg8Iw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-17T16:00:29.038Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-17T15:44:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>1ab4fbf6d85d18eee84fe00830b839df88d7d784eb3a0923766fc812ce8a973f</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-17T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Home Bread Makers</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-19T11:28:18.540Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/OpdzSSCL#9lMHPypY32Cu-Kuoqj3yKA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>028</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, glow in the dark pigments, which absorb light to glow in the dark. A version of these pigments that contain no radioactive substances was invented in Japan in 1993. They're now used worldwide in products like watch faces and emergency signage. We learn the little-known story behind the pigments' creation, including how they were born from a company in danger of closing down.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, glow in the dark pigments, which absorb light to glow in the dark.</description>
    <endDate>2021-03-24T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ukJhESwD#fqxJrcx8OEUgXG3EcPpmcQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-03-24T16:00:32.160Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-03-24T15:44:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>ca7f296788335500e96284e4ea31409bdea34e32e430882b1660dcf97bcf25bf</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-03-24T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Glow in the Dark Pigments</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-03-24T18:38:23.544Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/HssxgKpS#qeBm7bp07DqJNtq17WunUQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>029</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, emoji, the ideograms like smileys, hearts and food that help add fun to text messages. Now used in messages and emails worldwide every day, the first set of emoji was created in Japan in 1999 for the relatively small cell phone screens of the time. Dive in and discover the little-known origin story of emoji.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, emoji, the ideograms like smileys, hearts and food that help add fun to text messages.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-03T05:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/zlAjzKJQ#IXDiMZfPvSzw0BieqaZl-A</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-03T05:25:29.390Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-03T05:09:20.103Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>1360eef60390a185090cc9c533c39bcae9784d5809bf5c5f60a928994f761f5d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-03T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Emoji</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-03T09:33:08.480Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/gdVWETYI#4u3MrCosHPzeEt8b8dRXYA</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>030</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, we look at miniature video cameras, used worldwide. In 1989, a Japanese firm created the smallest, lightest video camera in the world, which was the length of a Japanese passport. It helped people all over capture precious memories, like their children's growth and important vacations. We look into the little-known story behind the creation of these video cameras.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, miniature video cameras, and the Japanese firm that helped shrink them down to size.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-03T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/PMVGlb7D#X-3KjjHXCCPWEKiZoDzFdg</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-03T05:40:26.048Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-03T05:24:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>daed266f8c2b818b9264b66e559e4e974fb1be6e5c9dff0e15dda7c40549ab20</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-03T05:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Miniature Video Cameras</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-03T07:24:40.593Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/TYFwHDDL#cqI-OLtEcC1lSEc6K0HLYg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>031</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a well-known type of 2D barcodes called QR codes. These codes were invented in 1994 by a Japanese car component manufacturer. These days, they're used throughout the world in factories and stores, on travel tickets, for cash-free payments and more. Learn the little-known story behind these barcodes, including their unusual inspirations: the game of Go and skyscrapers!</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the 2D barcodes called QR codes, invented in Japan in 1994 by a car component maker.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-10T05:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/KMBkVL6J#PDLHFDc38XiDd1rLyQlyIA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-10T05:25:27.796Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-10T05:09:20.116Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>1c8ce196778dcde72a11c5c40ef729a81f8c753dee1da14d19811dfdcaa9cc3d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-10T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>2D Barcodes</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-10T10:51:57.927Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/PVk22Kra#jZ69TqT5uWYevgJjzMwiMg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>032</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, an invention that makes dirty water clean: water-purifying powder. This powder was invented in 2002, and is now used in some 80 developing countries in places like Asia and Africa. It employs polyglutamic acid, which is found in natto, Japan's sticky fermented soybeans! We discover the tale behind this powder, including its inspiration: a huge earthquake that hits Kobe, Japan.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, an invention that makes dirty water clean: water-purifying powder.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-10T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/jFhUgLpY#BhLf_DM-sBW7s6lzMiA4Aw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-10T05:40:20.899Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-10T05:24:22.388Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>b2401f91a6b2788420c7d7d2df25fc5126e75f15daefe0fb03c57f484fdfe7c9</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-10T05:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Water-Purifying Powder</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-10T08:36:06.939Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/qNl2SLob#kgZ23BGNbm1jTPDCvSonZQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>033</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the worksheet study method known as "Kumon." Invented in 1958 by math teacher Kumon Toru for his son, the method involves self-study with math problems printed on worksheets. Using the sheets, learners improve their academic ability in small steps. Today the method is used by over 4 million students in 57 countries and regions. Dive into the little-known story behind this method.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the worksheet study method known as "Kumon," created in 1958 by a teacher for his son.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-17T05:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/ng4iUSrL#yCBKrNme5pzcBIx3bKMpOw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-17T05:25:32.866Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-17T05:09:20.131Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>09b735f48e41be3ccfbc7f3512a5caa4d0e21993c0f863a25bf91e6b52dad12d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-17T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Worksheet Study Method</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-17T12:28:22.834Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/VoR2QDDZ#J6GIE5DRJhRaBHTH60jXLg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>034</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a method of growing produce using a transparent film: film farming. The film is made from hydrogel, a moisture-absorbing material used in disposable diapers. Sow seeds on top, and they germinate and create seedlings, leading to vegetables and other produce without soil! We dive into the little-known story behind this unique Japanese farming technology.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a way to grow vegetables and other produce using a transparent film: film farming.</description>
    <endDate>2021-04-17T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/fNxAjZ4L#07_TyI-kCu9mP672OEWu_g</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-04-17T05:40:33.333Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-04-17T05:24:20.004Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>e581a9eb60b92e316729f2f0800b7802aae5023ec983378b403da73e5083c79d</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-04-17T05:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Film Farming</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-04-17T10:19:46.782Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/4tomCTgQ#m_Y3kqbz1Fb-iecYHTui5w</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>035</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, robotic exoskeletons, machines that turn humans into cyborgs! They were invented by professor and business founder Sankai Yoshiyuki, who created them for people who have trouble walking, such as the elderly or those who have suffered strokes. We dive into the little-known story behind the development of the world's first robotic exoskeletons.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, robotic exoskeletons, machines that turn humans into cyborgs!</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-01T05:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Qb5Tiaaa#d80u6eotLU47yNvfRXz8tw</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-01T05:25:29.131Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-01T05:09:20.100Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>ba1e2e36a0ea6507f7ea0306be29c7d977edb13f69b1d94d73eb198ff97dd2ea</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-01T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Robotic Exoskeletons</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-01T07:16:51.187Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/9lp3VALJ#z5O0wWD4oD3hCPyd8q1Q6Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>036</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a surgical microscope stand used in neurosurgery. Invented by an optics company in Tokyo, it features a unique piece of tech which keeps the microscope in focus even when it moves. Discover the little-known story behind this invention, partially inspired by equipment used to observe outer space!</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a stand used in neurosurgery that keeps the microscope in focus even when it moves!</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-01T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/mk1jhCgb#0vRvC71Cir3wcgyOtg2D1Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-01T05:40:21.525Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-01T05:24:23.001Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>243263883f1c696bae06882149ed9aeafaa959af3b27de61a0f23d9dcfa59171</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-01T05:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Surgical Microscope Stand</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-01T06:47:01.230Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/UTQU3BSY#rM2fBTDVgWKHoik_sxBxuw</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>037</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, a product used and loved in garment factories worldwide: automatic thread trimmer sewing machines. Just press a foot pedal, and the threads attached to stitched pieces of cloth are automatically cut. From high-end brands to fast fashion, these machines are used by garment makers around the world. This time, we dive into the little-known story behind their invention.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. Today, a product used in garment factories worldwide: automatic thread trimmer sewing machines.</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-08T05:25:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/b2xwQChL#JpWicfSANjR-jE1SQJGJQA</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-08T05:25:27.297Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-08T05:09:22.950Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>cdbaae344a0ea4f252d7005a6a7694e9e39abcb937ffe12f4dabca22face4ded</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-08T05:10:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Automatic Thread Trimmer Sewing Machines</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-08T05:53:58.470Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/e24yGLyS#NzYDfTgXdoLgiVmFrCLaXQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>038</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, an invention installed in museums around the world: dinosaur robots. Using cylinders that expand and contract with air pressure to replicate realistic movements, these robots make it look as if the dinosaurs are really alive. We discover the little-known story of how Japanese inventors made these robots look so real.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, an invention installed in museums around the world: hyper-realistic dinosaur robots.</description>
    <endDate>2021-05-08T05:40:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/HshWibib#Omfl6_66eLZ-z1j0t6xDKQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-05-08T05:40:24.145Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-05-08T05:24:20.068Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>8d4d954c7c2a714c9b7b683c8f0223e4af9e7e720cf499d7232b388d884927c0</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-05-08T05:25:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Dinosaur Robots</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-05-08T07:43:31.128Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/z9wUDLAb#ZLAP--0AgnerNIZ_gL6H_Q</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>041</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, bottled green tea: green tea sold in bottles made from PET plastic. Loved in over 30 countries and regions, it was developed by a Japanese beverage maker in 1990 using special techniques to keep the tea tasting great when bottled. We dive into the little-known story behind this drink, which is expanding worldwide among health-conscious consumers, and learn about the latest versions.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, bottled green tea: green tea sold in bottles made from PET plastic.</description>
    <endDate>2020-11-25T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Jd4k0ZJY#mm2aGkeDku1lPcEfMQBCPQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-11-25T16:00:30.191Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-11-25T15:44:20.055Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>10894c36721e15a4db888ed709565fe3563f76552dd852a1663b6c39e89c9cab</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-11-25T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Bottled Green Tea</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-25T00:54:53.649Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/3QNRGCxD#ac9FPsvmWPhOHdMMQgOEYg</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>042</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, personal information protection stamps: rubber stamps that make mail addresses unreadable. Just stamp, and a unique alphabetic pattern renders the underlying text illegible. These stamps were invented in 2007 to help protect personal information. We discover the story behind these stamps, now sold in over 20 countries and regions, and learn about the latest models.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, rubber stamps that render text unreadable in order to protect personal information.</description>
    <endDate>2020-12-23T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/JdoTwarL#nlcBfe0gc75G3Q7UYK_jLQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2020-12-23T16:00:28.962Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2020-12-23T15:44:22.666Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>351dc665ad0a1bf48bd98c87efdf342a9ae82e3c1092f88bd54954b9530cf4f9</sha256>
    <startDate>2020-12-23T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Personal Information Protection Stamps</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2020-12-23T22:59:31.233Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/BRsw3Taa#6oG01-i_JC77FXSc32eQLQ</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>043</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, planetariums, which realistically reproduce the look of the starry night sky. In 2014, a Japanese firm succeeded in creating a planetarium projector that displays each of the approximately 9,500 stars visible to the naked eye in incredible detail, including accurate coloring. We dive into the story behind the creation of that top invention and learn about the latest models.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, planetariums, which realistically reproduce the look of the starry night sky.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-13T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/Wclw0JZb#AKzf52_RVDJHZpDsGpFCFQ</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-13T16:00:27.407Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-13T15:44:20.003Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>ea915712992a5d301dfe39ead1cc5644ea2c74b46983c8536f2076fce343364e</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-13T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Planetariums</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-13T20:10:47.656Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/aAcylTxb#x-iAxrNcPsDcLvH_7tzH4g</raw>
  </episode>
  <episode>
    <airingId>044</airingId>
    <content>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the story behind the handheld digital pets known as Tamagotchi. Released by a Japanese toy maker in 1996, these toys let owners "raise" an on-screen digital pet, feeding it, putting it to bed, playing with it and more. We dig into the little-known story behind the creation of these handheld digital pets, a giant hit in some 30 countries and regions.</content>
    <description>The behind-the-scenes tales of hit products and creations from Japan: this is Japan's Top Inventions. This time, the story behind the handheld digital pets known as Tamagotchi.</description>
    <endDate>2021-01-27T16:00:00.000Z</endDate>
    <link>https://mega.nz/folder/MXATFKbT#MyOowi_wAciYjve28idr2Q</link>
    <recordDateEnd>2021-01-27T16:00:28.469Z</recordDateEnd>
    <recordDateStart>2021-01-27T15:44:20.099Z</recordDateStart>
    <seriesId>2072</seriesId>
    <sha256>c89b679c5053dadb53eee1dfcaacefd26df090d2feaccfa1b1ffb353a0f7540a</sha256>
    <startDate>2021-01-27T15:45:00.000Z</startDate>
    <subtitle>Handheld Digital Pets</subtitle>
    <title>Japan's Top Inventions</title>
    <uploadedDate>2021-01-27T16:51:32.687Z</uploadedDate>
    <raw>https://mega.nz/folder/5zYjFQBJ#xn7V5UiHw1VK6ZkVqaYR1A</raw>
  </episode>
</episodeList>